No matter your profession,
...learning to use a new application to
do your job can be a painful experience.
Yes, the software you’re currently using
has all kinds of weird quirks and problems,
...especially if it’s PowerPoint or Dreamweaver.
Man, have you ever used Dreamweaver?
It’s awful.
It’s just awful.
But the thing about these problems is that, over time,
...you learn to overcome them,
...and eventually, you develop quite a bit of speed.
Things are fine.
You can work well enough with what you have,
..and yes, some of it is a little annoying,
...but life's not perfect.
And then along,
...comes some game changer that
everyone keeps talking about.
Now, if the app is Dreamweaver,
those people have a point.
I just can’t stress how much I hate Dreamweaver.
But often the process of moving to
the new thing is really, really painful,
...and you just end up with a whole
bunch of new problems to overcome.
This all boils down to one question:
Uh, it’s a two-part question.
Now, in the world of composition,
...the industry leader, Sibelius,
...is the ultimate trial by fire.
Understanding it is a bit like learning to
drive a new route to work while blindfolded.
Your experience and intuition aren't gonna help you.
Instead, you need to rely on brute-force trial-and-error
by simply crashing into everything around you
...in order to piece together a mental
construct of what’s going on,
...with your primary guides being
abstract causality and pain.
It should be renamed 'Pavlovius'.
So, for all of us who’ve had to endure the
process of divining the mechanics of Sibelius,
...we don’t want to do it again.
We’re survivors.
Yeah, it’s a nightmare to learn.
It took me years to get good at it.
But, despite the awful interface,
...it is actually quite powerful, and eventually,
...EVENTUALLY,
...you get to be pretty quick at it too.
It's fine.
Leave it.
It’s fine.
But it’s not fine.
Not anymore,
...because there’s a new app on the scene.
A direct competitor hell-bent on
running those Sibelius folk out of...
...town...
Who are you?
'I’m Jankman!'
'And you’re going to be seeing me a little later!'
'Hello everybody,
...and thank you for tuning into
today's, uh, livestream about Dorico 3.'
This is Daniel Spreadbury.
He’s pretty much the spokesperson of Dorico.
And to begin looking at what he
and the rest of his team have built,
...let’s go back a few years to 2012,
...when the majority of that team were
working on a different notation app called,
...um,
...Sibelius.
Right, I’ve already spoken about this once before,
...so let’s recap quickly.
Sibelius was bought by a multimedia
company called AVID in 2006.
Daniel Spreadbury and the rest of the Sibelius team
were based in Finsbury Park in London at the time.
But a few years after they purchased Sibelius,
...AVID ran into some financial trouble,
...with their share price tanking at the end of 2011.
So, as part of an emergency cost-saving measure,
...they decided to let the Finsbury Park team go,
...and began recruiting a new and
much cheaper team in the Ukraine.
Then, three years later, the Ukraine team
seems to have not worked out,
...and Sibelius started advertising for yet
another development team in Montreal.
As Tim Carrol, AVID’s vice president
for audio products, explained:
...or to put it another way,
'It turns out we needed the people we fired.'
The closing of the Finsbury Park office
...caught the attention of Yamaha,
who saw an opportunity.
You see: AVID’s revenue has been
slowly declining for years now,
...with its two other money makers
Pro Tools and Media Composer
...facing increasingly stiff competition.
Sibelius, on the other hand,
...is still solidly the industry standard for notation,
...and has a pretty firm footing
in the education space too,
...which makes it difficult to displace.
And since it integrates with Pro Tools,
...it’s attractive to those who
write music for movies and TV,
...or who want to convert their scores
into highly-produced audio tracks.
However, for those bought into the
Sibelius/Pro Tools ecosystem,
...there is some cause for concern:
Are AVID destined to continue this trajectory of decline?
And, if so, given that they were willing to
massively halt Sibelius’ development once,
...would they do it again?
Is Sibelius safe?
Well, Yamaha are also asking these questions.
They own a company called Steinberg,
...who in turn own Cubase, a
direct competitor to Pro Tools.
And since they’re obviously always
looking for a way to give Cubase an edge,
...when AVID decided to ditch
the Finsbury Park team in 2012,
...they saw an opportunity.
Here, offered up on a platter,
...was a group of people with the experience
to develop a rival notation program
...which could integrate with Cubase,
...and, together, could be poised to
step in as the new industry standard
...if AVID's fortunes continued to deteriorate.
Dorico was never going to suddenly
take over from Sibelius.
No, there’s a longer game being played here.
So, before we go any further,
...you might be wondering why I’ve not yet
mentioned the other two major notation apps,
...Finale and Musescore?
Well, with regards to Finale,
...which is still Sibelius’ main rival,
...I’m saving it for last,
...and I don’t want to give the game
away by talking about it now.
Regarding Musescore, well,
...that’s bit more of an interesting one actually.
And if you haven’t already heard the news
about this, I guess you’ll be pretty surprised.
So, after I created my video about
Musescore in March 2019,
...the open-source community set about
fixing all the issues I had mentioned.
I was quite impressed and honored by this,
...and over time, I found myself regularly talking
to them about the specifics of certain fixes.
Eventually, I started submitting proper designs too.
And as I got more involved, I discovered
that I got along really well with the team,
...so one thing led to another.
We started holding hands,
...we dated for a while,
...and on 5th November 2019,
...finally decided to tie the knot
...and I became MuseScore’s new Head of Design.
I know.
What a match!
So now that I’m now actively working
on the design of MuseScore,
...I feel there are two obvious
questions I should quickly address.
First, what does this mean for the Tantacrul channel?
Well, in terms of output, nothing.
If I do cover my work on MuseScore here in the future,
...it’ll only be when I think the subject is
interesting enough for a general audience,
...and I’ll largely be documenting my design
work over on the MuseScore channel instead.
So, for anyone interested in following that progress,
...the link is in the description.
The second question that I imagine this will raise
...is whether or not my involvement with Musescore
will bias my appraisal of Dorico or Finale.
I mean, it’s a fair question,
...and it’s probably worth describing
my own motivations here.
I joined Musescore so I could put
my money where my mouth is:
To design a notation app to be
the way I think it should be,
...and the last thing I want to do in pursuit of that goal
...is to start engaging in cringeworthy
‘Us and Them’ corporate tribalism,
...of the Steve Ballmer variety.
'Steve Jobs goes to MacWorld
and he pulls out this iPhone.'
'What was your first reaction when you saw that?'
'500 dollars? Fully subsidized? With a plan?'
'I said that is the most expensive phone in the world.'
'And it doesn’t appeal to business customers
because it doesn’t have a keyboard,'
'...which makes it not a very good email machine.'
If I start failing to recognise the
good work of those around me,
...how good is my work gonna be?
So, I’m going to proceed exactly as I have before:
When I see something I like, I’ll say so.
And when I see something janky,
...I‘m going to mercilessly mock it, as always.
And as you watch this video, you can judge for
yourselves whether you think I’m being fair or not.
And with all that said, let’s get back into it.
The Dorico team have a tendency to irritate
those who currently work on Sibelius,
...and it's not hard to see why.
Nearly every article about Dorico or
interview with one of the team members
...will mention the Finsbury Park incident,
...although, to be fair, it’s hard to see
how that subject can be avoided.
But that’s not all.
'Sibelius' seems to come up a lot when team
members describe the design of Dorico too,
...with the sentiment being:
‘Look at how badly they do things!'
I’ve linked to a few examples of this in the description.
The funny thing about this though is that,
...since they ARE the old Sibelius team,
...then they’re to a significant degree
responsible for this badness,
Bear in mind, by the way,
...that this is the team who brought us
the awful ribbon design with Sibelius 7,
...a legacy that the current Sibelius
team are rather unfairly saddled with.
So with that said, what is this video going to focus on?
Well, I’ve spent the last 8 months using Dorico properly.
And like my previous music software videos,
...I think it offers up a lot of interesting lessons
about the challenges of creating music software,
...and I’ve made sure to focus on
aspects I’ve not spoken about before.
For those who can’t read music, this video should
still be pretty straightforward to understand.
For those interested in my overall assessment of Dorico,
...I’m going to be putting it head-to-head
against Sibelius to see which is better.
And as I go through this video,
...I’m going to answer the crucial question:
Which would I pick to write music in?
So as I mentioned earlier,
...Dorico spends a lot of time and effort positioning
itself as a more elite notation program than Sibelius.
And they reinforce this message constantly in
interviews, tutorials, press releases and blog posts.
The look and layout of the app
tries to convey this message too,
...sometimes literally.
I mean, the very first thing you see
when you open Dorico is the tagline:
‘Advanced Music Notation System’.
The UI is dark by default,
...which reminds me of a design adage:
‘Use white if you want to look easy and non-threatening,
...use black if you want to look pro.'
They claim to be intuitive and simple to use,
...so I was curious to see what they’d done
to improve upon the Sibelius model.
And to help me answer this,
...I decided to try something I’ve
not done before on this channel.
In October 2019,
...I sent out a call on my Patreon, YouTube and Twitter,
...asking experienced musicians
to help me do some user-testing.
After receiving hundreds of responses,
...I chose 25 people who had never used Dorico before,
...and asked them to, one, download
and install the trial version,
...and, two, try writing a few bars of music
...using whatever instruments and
styles they were comfortable with.
'I am quite comfortable using Sibelius, '
'...I've never used Dorico before, '
'...though I've been really excited to try.'
'So now, again, I'm stuck at this
point where I need more bars.'
'This is killing me.''
This is the ultimate test for any application:
The first-time user test.
It doesn’t indicate how good an
app is once you’ve learned it,
...and we’ll definitely get to that later,
...but it does directly test how intuitive it is.
And for anyone interested,
...these sessions typically lasted about an hour.
So, why did I focus on this type of testing?
Well, firstly, this is a video about design,
...and I wanted to show one of the tools
designers use to validate their work.
Secondly, the first-time user test is extremely important
to pass for any app competing in a crowded market.
Why?
Well, because when people
decide to install your free trial,
...that’s your opportunity to convince them
...that it’s worth making the jump from what
they are currently using to what you are offering.
And every complication,
...every bit of jank they encounter along
the way during this crucial period
...is more likely to convince them
that it’s just not worth doing.
And in Dorico’s case,
...considering that it’s aggressively
targeting Sibelius and Finale users,
...a bad first-time experience is
really hurtful to their chances.
Also, this is the best test you can use to
determine if something is well-designed,
...because every time an app requires you to consult
the manual to figure out how to do something,
...especially when other apps
already make that thing easy,
...it's not doing a particularly good job.
Now, the experience of those I recorded largely
matched my own first-time experience,
...which is... mixed,
...and in places, pretty painful.
So, strap in people,
...because, even though there’s a
lot of good stuff to discuss later,
...we first need to talk about the setup process.
Okay.
Are you ready for the pain?
Right.
To begin using a trial of Dorico 3,
...you need to create a Steinberg ID,
...by entering your email and a password.
And right off the bat, we have a usability issue.
The title says:
And at the bottom you have what
looks like a 'Confirm' button.
Now, most people foolishly
understood this to mean that
...you should enter your email here
...and your password there
...and press ‘Create Steinberg ID’.
Lovely.
And you’ll need to fill that out again.
For what it’s worth, most participants
did this step before speaking to me,
...so I only saw it happen 4 times.
And out of those 4 times,
...3 people made this mistake.
And once you’ve registered,
...they email you a code, which
just about everyone copies.
"I cannot... paste in here?"
Then, after hitting the redundant 'Continue' button,
...you are taken to this doozy:
...with the following options:
Watching people encountering
this step was pretty amusing.
"What?"
"The- There's no choice."
"What kind of trial is this?"
"It just rubs me the wrong way, there's just- this thing,"
"I'm not a fan,"
"...because that'd be- the first thing
I'm gonna do is unsubscribe."
Then they send you an activation code,
...which contains hidden curse words,
...and you also get your download link.
I should probably tell you at this point that
you are nowhere near 'one step away',
...you’re like 20% way through this.
So, the download link doesn’t actually download Dorico.
Instead, you get the ‘Steinberg Download Assistant’,
...a landing page that finally
allows you to download Dorico,
...along with the orchestral libraries that come with it.
And when installing the download assistant,
...it asks you whether you want
to install something called
...the ‘aria2 download manager’,
...a download manager which they explain
makes your download assistant work better.
Anyway, once that’s all set up,
...you can finally click on Dorico 3 to download it.
Once installed, you click on the Dorico icon to open it,
...and it tells you:
'No license found',
...which is one of those messages that makes you think,
‘Oh no, I’ve done something wrong!'
And there’s a button, which, when pressed,
...opens a program called the ‘eLicenser’,
...which it turns out they installed on
your machine without telling you.
And if you’re on Windows, they also
auto-created a desktop shortcut too.
Uh, okay.
Looks like you got some spring cleaning to do after this!
So, you go back to your email,
...grab your activation code and enter it,
...then you press 'Activate License',
...only to be told that the eLicenser is out of date.
What!?
But, h- hold on. I just installed it?
How did I mess this up?
Now, a few people didn’t know what to do at this point
...and it’s worth mentioning that this was
experienced universally by every person I spoke to.
And it took some of them a long time to realise
...that the only solution to this problem
...is to follow the address mentioned
in the error message here:
And they don’t even make it a link.
It'd be nice, you know?
If there was a link so I don’t have to type it out.
So, then you download the
latest version of the eLicenser,
(thanks for nothing, Steinberg Download Assistant!)
...and then you install it, and...
Oh, what now?
So, guess which application is causing the issue?
That’s right,
...it’s Dorico.
The program that launched the eLicenser in the
first place is now preventing it from working.
What’s the opposite of 'seamless'?
'Seamful'?
Okay, so that was a trainwreck.
At this point, I should mention that
I started off interviewing 28 people,
...and 3 of them dropped out specifically because
this installation was too awkward for them.
Of the 25 remaining people, only
3 described it as straight-forward.
Okay, to be fair, this is the Steinberg
team in Hamburg’s doing,
...not the Dorico team in London.
At the moment, this tacked-together series of mishaps
...is hobbling the first-time experience of Dorico.
Anyway, let’s leave all that behind and open Dorico, uh-
...and we're brought to the Steinberg hub, which is...
...fine.
A bit disorganised and fugly.
I particularly love this vile green button over here.
This is a classic UI trick:
If people don’t notice an important button,
...just make it more horrible!
And Dorico, c- can we talk-
Can we talk about this?
Coldplay?
You’re angling to be the
creme-de-la-creme of notation apps,
...and you’re leading with Coldplay?
Oh, and it's that song:
...the one where they discovered arpeggios.
Who is your audience for this?
I mean, if you had a pop song by, I don't know,
...David Bowie,
(let’s just create a little Venn diagram here)
...I can see there being a lot of
crossover with Dorico users.
But if we were to change it to:
...and:
I think, uh-
...let’s just push those out a bit.
Yeah, well, that feels about right.
Coldplay.
Seriously.
You may as well as led with 'Chocolate Rain'.
But all that aside,
...now at least, we’re in Dorico,
...although we’re still not really done with the installation
...because next comes the audio setup.
Now, like many other composers
who write for live ensembles,
...I’m a diehard fan of the orchestral
emulator ‘NotePerformer’,
...which I could go on about at length.
NotePerformer can be easily set up as the
default sound library in both Sibelius and Finale.
But with Dorico, it’s a different story.
So, first you go to the Play category,
...and press this '+' button under
the empty 'VST Instruments' panel.
Then I can pick 'NotePerformer' from the dropdown,
...which in turn triggers a pop-up that’s been
built specifically to explain what to do,
...because there’s no way you’d ever figure it out.
So, I have to go to ‘Play’
...and choose 'NotePerformer'
from the Playback Template.
And what’s this hieroglyphic?
Is it a... sound wave or something?
That’s meant to be a factory?
‘Hey guys, the deadline is today and
we need a factory icon pronto!'
yeh, no problem
livid to me
i’ll just make the dor
and the two tings and
and de thing and
and ant
and
Next, I have to go to a completely different
place to make that template work by default.
Even then, if you press 'Play' it might not work,
...so it tells you specifically that you
have to rewind it to the beginning first,
...and then press 'Play'.
This is a novel way to fix usability bugs.
Just don’t fix them, and provide an inbuilt
pop-up that tells you how to work around it.
By the way, I’m making this seem way more
straightforward and linear than it was.
I spent a lot of time working all these out,
...especially because the ‘Play’ option up here
...is only available when you’re in the ‘Play’ category.
A really opaque clutter-saving technique.
So what would be the ideal here?
Well, how about when Dorico is opened,
...it searches for NotePerformer,
...and if it finds it, it triggers the following pop-up:
...and then simply provide them with an
option to set it as the default right there too.
And as for that last step,
...the one where I have to rewind to the start first?
Since none of the competition does that,
...I think Dorico should fix whatever they
need to fix to stop that from happening.
They can’t claim to be an intuitive app
...if they require four steps to do
what Sibelius can accomplish in one.
And just to finish up with this,
...for anyone thinking of installing the trial version,
...I should probably issue these two warnings.
First, Dorico by default likes
to hog all the audio for itself,
...preventing other apps that make
sound from working properly.
This caused me quite a few
headaches during user-testing,
...because the act of booting up Dorico
caused our video conference calls to crash.
"I don’t know if you can hear me or not
but I can no longer hear you."
Not cool, Dorico!
The setting to turn this off is in 'Preferences',
...'Play',
...then scroll down to turn off
this miserable little tickbox.
You’re welcome.
Secondly, if you try to open Dorico
before your sound library is installed,
...it will default to something called ‘Dorico Beep’,
...which is a basic sampler that is so distorted
and set to such an insanely loud volume
...that it might take your head off if you’re not careful.
Watch this poor unsuspecting soul pressing 'Play'
in Dorico for the first time with headphones on.
"Coldplay's 'Clocks'."
"Alright..."
"And I'm gonna press 'Play'."
"Oh, jes-"
"Holy [REDACTED]!"
So, next up,
...our testers needed to set up their score
...by choosing the instruments they wanted to write for.
Now, all the major players provide an 'Instruments'
pop-up which allows you to do this right away.
Makes sense.
But the Dorico team have altered this idea a little,
...by introducing the concept of ‘Players’,
...which are meant to represent the
actual people who’ll be playing the piece
...with each ‘Player’ needing to be
assigned their own instrument.
This is reminiscent of an old app
from the 90’s called 'Igor Engraver',
...which had a similar list called ‘Musicians’.
There are good reasons for doing this:
First, it provides a framework that allows you to assign
more than one instrument to an individual player.
For example, if you have a percussionist in charge
of multiple instruments, you can set that up here.
This is also a structurally useful tool.
By creating this identifiable list, which is a set,
...not of instruments but of the people
who are holding those instruments,
...they've unlocked some very powerful
score-creation and layout possibilities,
...which we’ll get to shortly.
But the drawback of this system
is that it creates a complication
...that makes the process of setting up a score
...more cumbersome and difficult to understand.
First, it forces new users to have to engage
with the awkward concept of having an
...‘Empty-handed Player’ in their project,
...which I watched stress a few people out.
"I didn’t understand it and it got in the way,"
"...and it’s only when I’m watching this video
back that I understand where I went wrong."
Another problem I saw was the following:
After you choose an instrument,
...this Instrument panel closes.
Oh.
What do you do now?
Well, a lot of people look at
these hieroglyphics down here:
'Person'
'People'
'Mecha-Rainbow'?
uh
'CD rack'?
...and understandably steer clear of them.
So instead, a lot of people clicked on
this pretty inviting '+' button here,
...since it’s the thing that best describes their intention:
‘I want to add something’.
The problem is, that by doing this,
...you’re actually assigning this
player another instrument,
..which is a concept first-time
users don’t yet understand.
"What happened to the... violin and piano?"
"Because it seems like I only have trumpet on my score."
"Yeah..."
"Currently I'm doing something wrong."
Another issue this creates is that it makes the process
of setting up a non-standard orchestral ensemble
...much slower than Finale or Sibelius.
With Finale for example, when
I want to start a new project,
...a dialog appears where I can
quickly choose all my instruments
...by pressing this 'Add >' button,
...which are automatically arranged
into a sensible default ordering:
Woodwinds at the top, strings at the bottom, et cetera.
With Dorico, the concept of needing to add a
player first before assigning them an instrument
...slows things down.
And since this dialog keeps
disappearing after you add players,
...you very quickly find yourself wondering,
'Is there a way I can add multiple players
and not have to do this one-by-one?’
And then you look down here and...
...you’d be forgiven for thinking that this
is the option that allows you to do that.
Nope.
This is something called a ‘Section Player’,
...which refers to a section of musicians
all reading from the same staff,
...like a string section.
So, this is a further complication.
We’re no longer just looking at a list of players.
It’s a list of players where one of them
is itself a group of more players.
So if you want to add multiple players
who all play different instruments,
...that’s what the Mecha-Rainbow is for.
The icon is meant to be an
ensemble seating chart, by the way.
Uh... Congrats if you figured that out.
But even this is inflexible,
...only allowing you to choose
from a few types of grouping.
"I'm gonna try and do a piano quintet."
"Okay, I guess it doesn't give quintets by default."
For the orchestral piece I wrote in Dorico,
...I wanted 2 alto sax and 1 tenor sax,
...which I could kind of get,
...along with a bunch of additional
instruments I didn’t want.
So, I added this list,
...then deleted all the unneeded instruments,
...then added the missing second alto sax player.
No big deal, but it does feel quite
slow compared to the competition.
And by the time I’d finished,
...the instruments were arranged
completely incorrectly too.
So I had to drag them around
into a sensible order manually.
Not to mention, after I’d finished adding instruments,
...look at the state of this score!
So, again, unlike Sibelius which automatically
tries to pick a sensible default layout,
...I have to now go on the hunt for the settings
which allow me to change the staff and paper size.
Here’s another minor annoyance
...that can be illustrated by watching this user
coming to grips with instrument setup.
He’s now trying to delete some unwanted players,
...and this annoying dialog keeps
popping up each time to ask
...whether he wants to delete the player
...or the player and the part layouts.
But the thing is:
...he’s only trying to delete an 'Empty-handed Player',
...so any parts assigned to them are going to be empty.
It feels like a fairly unnecessary and semi-abstract
question to be presenting him with at this moment.
Here’s another user engaging with
this dialog for the first time,
...who opted to only delete the player, because
...the options being put in front of him aren’t clear.
"Yeah, there’s no music written yet, so that's fine."
"I can delete that one."
As a consequence,
...he now has an orphaned part over here that’s
going to cause some confusion down the road.
Oh man, I haven’t even got to this panel yet.
Right, let’s mosey on over here.
So this list, on first glance, looks like the same thing.
But no,
...let me quickly explain what it is.
This is the Layouts panel,
...which is a list of the scores and part scores
that have been auto-generated
...as you were adding players over here.
This is also a concept from Igor Engraver,
...which has been reimagined in Dorico.
And let me be clear here:
This idea is great.
The Dorico team were right to take inspiration from Igor,
...but their version does involve
some very unusual behaviour.
For example, if I click on the 'Flute' player over here,
...we can see tickboxes in the Layouts panel on the right,
...which are showing the scores
where the flute is being applied,
...and in this case, the ‘Full score’
and the individual flute part.
And if I want the flute to be added
to anything else, I can just tick it.
For example, I’ve now added the
flute player to this oboe part.
Okay so far.
But now if I click on a score in this list,
...the arrangement reverses.
Now the score is selected and these
instruments become tickboxes,
...which basically means that there are
two reversed ways of doing the same thing.
It’s really strange,
...especially because the panels
are on either side of the screen
...so it’s not visually obvious
they’re connected in any way,
...and you have to keep ping-ponging back and forth
to understand the relationship between them.
And this setup has some other
weird knock-on effects too,
...like if you arrange the instruments
into a sensible order on one side,
...the other side doesn’t follow suit,
...so the connections are all over the place.
Look!
...over here!
Uh... All the way down here.
The shame about this is the options
being provided are really powerful
...because you can create as many
variations of parts as you want.
Like, if you’re writing for piano trio,
...and the cellist tells you they want
to see the piano in their part score,
...you can just click on the piano and
add it to the cello score right away,
...or click on the cello score and add the piano.
Whatever.
But as I said earlier,
...when you arrive at the app for the first time,
...all of these,
...all these bizarre icons and interrelationships
...smack you in the face at once.
It's baffling.
And don’t even get me started about this down here:
Flows,
...a way of creating sections,
or movements, or variations.
I don’t want to get into it too much right now.
It’s another nice idea which, when clicked on, reveals:
Oh no! A three-way relationship!
AAAAAAHHH!
And what I found particularly strange
about this whole Setup page is that,
...despite having an entire section
devoted to setting up your score,
...it’s missing some really essential stuff like
...staff and paper size,
...which you remember from a moment ago,
...you’re definitely going to have to edit
if you are creating an orchestral score.
Oddly, if I expand one of these,
...you can see the page size referenced
but you can’t actually edit it.
Why?
You can look but you can’t touch.
So if you want to change these settings,
...you have to right-click here
and choose ‘Layout Options...’
...to open this dialog box.
If you change the layout size,
...you have to then close the dialog
and navigate to the score itself
...to see the effect of the changes you’ve made.
This is particularly jarring
...because Sibelius does this much better.
Look, I can change the staff size here
...and the score updates accordingly.
Overall, the interconnectedness of
this system is not obvious at all,
...and the only way to learn it is
to watch a lot of tutorial videos.
And just so you know,
...as a designer, you generally want to avoid that,
...especially for core functionality.
For this kind of stuff, every time the
user needs to consult the manual,
...it is kind of a failure of design.
This system is very clever,
...but also inelegant and quite cumbersome.
And as a result, Dorico is not
an app that suddenly 'clicks',
...it’s an app that slowly dawns on you over time.
So, regarding score setup,
...are these pain points unavoidable?
Does the inclusion of all these clever ideas mean
that the app has to be naturally harder to learn?
Well, I'm sure it won’t surprise you to
find out that I think the answer is 'No'.
I think some of this information could be sequenced
so that the user isn’t hit with all of it at once.
We have a structural problem to solve first.
This interconnected ping-pong layout is hampering
the ability to provide other useful settings,
...and is also causing the Players
panel to be over-complicated,
...especially the way you have to
keep re-opening the same dialog.
When you have to keep doing that,
it may as well be a dialog.
So, let’s remove players from here,
...and instead, when a user starts a new project,
...you show a dialog that places the Instruments
on the left and the Players on the right.
Now anyone coming from one of the competitor apps,
...which is the audience Dorico is targeting by the way,
...will know exactly what the deal is.
You can select instruments and add them quickly.
And each time you do this, a new
player is automatically created,
...allowing us to discard the confusing
concept of an ‘Empty-handed Player'.
And if you want to add more instruments to the same
player, or change the instrument they are holding,
...you can drag them into these slots.
This would allow you to change instruments later too.
And regarding the ordering,
...you’ll notice that the instruments have
been organised sensibly by default,
...and you can still drag to rearrange them if you want.
And once you’ve finished, you can close this dialog,
...and then you’re left with just
one list, which is the list of parts.
Why would I do this?
Well, let me demonstrate.
First, if you click on a part,
...now the appropriate score appears in front of you.
And if you want to edit the
number of players in that score,
...they can be immediately accessed
from this subordinate list,
...where the relationship between
players and parts is much clearer.
Moreover, now that you have this pattern,
...you can use tabs to expose useful common settings,
...like staff and page sizes.
The difference is,
...unlike the existing dialog box,
where you change these values,
...the score updates to reflect them immediately.
All in all, a much friendlier system.
The information is sequenced sensibly,
...options are exposed when you need them,
...and crucially, you can see the effect of
the changes you make to the settings.
Not to mention, because we’ve decluttered the page,
...it’s less likely to make your head spin
and you can see more of the score.
There are a few more bits of hooking-up to do,
...like making the players dialog easy to
find, and connecting it to flows, et cetera.
Those are fairly straight-forward
to solve using similar solutions.
I think you get the idea, so let’s move on.
Now, finally, we'll get to the part where our
testers were ready to write some music.
Everything we’ve been looking at so far
was contained in the ‘Setup’ tab.
But in order to write music, you now
need to move to the ‘Write’ tab.
And when you do this, the app
changes significantly for the better.
Gone are the esoteric, interconnected lists,
...and instead appears what looks like
a pretty sensible and intuitive layout.
This was my impression when I first used Dorico,
...and the people I tested largely agreed.
Here’s one person describing the layout
after seeing it for the first time:
"Okay, this looks-"
"This looks nice and simple."
"First impression is pretty good."
"Uh... I got my note input on the left-hand side,"
"...other stuff on the right-hand side."
"They seem nice and clean. I like that."
If you’re a designer, it’s exactly what you want to hear.
He doesn’t exactly know precisely what
he’ll find on either side of the page,
...but he has a pretty good idea
of the general organisation
...without having to think too deeply about it.
This side is concerned with writing music,
...this side contains markings and techniques
that you can apply to that music.
And when you select stuff on the score,
...you can choose from a few
contextual options down here.
This time around, there doesn’t appear to be any
interconnected functionality on either side of the score.
Any linked controls, like these two parts,
...are situated beside each other, which helps,
...and the connection was obvious to everyone I tested.
And there’s some lovely visual and
organisational subtlety here too.
In this panel,
...they’ve laid out the most common note
durations, accidentals and articulations,
...with clear separator lines
that makes it very easy to read.
I also really like this panel on the right.
Each collection of elements
is represented by a clear icon,
...and the contents of each section is organised
in a way that makes it really intuitive.
And it works in lots of different ways too.
For example, if you’re the kind of person who
likes to click on something first, and then apply it,
...you can.
Or, if you prefer to select the destination
first and make your selection afterwards,
...you can do that too.
And the impact this design finesse
had on first-time usage was evident.
No one failed to figure out how
to apply things to the score.
And with a few exceptions, people generally
didn’t get lost once they got to this page.
I also really like how many extended techniques
and modern notation concepts you find here.
Not only is it convenient, but also
educational for new composers,
...and I wouldn’t be surprised if many people
ended up discovering and using these techniques
...simply by virtue of exploring this app.
There is one quite painful issue
I’d love to see addressed,
...which is how hard they make it
to add bars when you get started.
You see, when you start a new project,
...you get what looks like one bar.
What you don’t realise is that this isn’t really a bar at all.
It’s infinite,
...and no matter how many notes you
add, you can never get to a new bar.
Moreover, you can’t create a new bar despite
there being a very clear option for it.
So, the trick here is to add a time signature first.
Unless you figure that out, you’re going nowhere.
Why they don’t disable this button when
it doesn’t do anything is beyond me.
Better yet, why not just ask them to
specify a time signature at that point.
Half of the people I tested had this specific issue,
...and I can’t understand why they don’t smooth it out.
Now, this complaint might make
experienced users groan,
...but it’s a first-time user trap.
It is logical,
...but you only see that logic when
you're on the other side of the problem.
And another consequence of this is that
when users first try to enter some notes,
...the fact that this really is an infinite bar
...causes the subdivision marking
to function quite poorly,
...and results in the user accidentally
entering the wrong note values.
It’s an awful first experience if you don’t think
to enter a time signature at the outset.
Now, in saying all of this,
...I shouldn’t gloss over the fact that
this initial state you find yourself in
...is actually a very permissive system if you
want to write music that’s free of any meter,
...which, for many composers interested in modern
techniques from the 20th or 21st century, is a big deal.
And what’s more, it’s been built to work this way,
...unlike Sibelius, where any free-metered
solution always feels like a hack.
However, I think the option to write
free-metered music should be opt-in,
...and certainly not the default.
But definitely kudos to the Dorico team
for building a system that facilitates it.
If you're interested in learning more about this,
...I’ve put a link to a relevant
tutorial in the description below.
Okay, I should probably address this
faint grey rectangle you see everywhere.
Oh, you know what? Let’s not right now.
Uh... Let's just pop it down here and we’ll get to it later.
So with all that said, what’s it
like writing music on the score?
Well, regarding basic note input,
...it works in a pretty standard way:
You click on a note value and enter it on the score,
...or you can enter notes using a
computer keyboard or MIDI keyboard.
In addition, they provide a marking above the stave
that describes how the beat is subdivided.
So far, so good.
But once you look a little closer,
...Dorico’s system does some very strange things,
...and it can’t simply be explained by listing
out each feature in isolation because
...here, again, they’ve linked
together certain functionalities
...for reasons that are initially tricky to understand.
It all seems to hang one or two hard rules which
seem like lines in the sand that they refuse to cross,
...with the rest of the interaction model being
...a collection of workarounds that solve the
awkward consequences of those rules.
Let me show you what I mean.
So, the most obvious rule
...is that notation should always
appear ‘correctly’ on the score.
Now, right away, we can see
why this rule is so compelling.
Who’s going to advocate for incorrectness?
And to give an example of how this rule is realised,
...let’s select a quarter note and
place it here before the strong beat,
...and you can see that now Dorico
is creating two tied 8th notes,
...which is... correct.
Now, the second rule is more a
consequence of the way Dorico is built,
...and I’ll need to do some explaining
before it will make sense.
You see, Dorico has a particular way of
storing notes that differs from Sibelius.
With Sibelius, there’s a strict
structural hierarchy going on,
...with notes belonging to bars,
...bars belonging to staffs,
...staffs belonging to instruments, et cetera.
Dorico isn’t structured this way.
Their note durations are stored independent of bars,
...which is why they can achieve things
like allowing tuplets to cross barlines.
...something Sibelius frustratingly does not support.
To illustrate this, here’s a few bars in 6/8.
If we place a dotted quarter note here,
...watch what happens when I use a shortcut
to move it to the right by one subdivision?
Now, we can see that Dorico has applied the first rule:
...altering it so the notation
conforms to standard convention.
And what we’re looking at now appears to be:
A quarter note, a tie, and then an eighth note.
But if we click on one of these elements,
...we can see that they’re actually all linked together
...and that Dorico isn’t classifying them that way.
It’s still representing them as
one dotted quarter note in the UI,
...which means that it considers this
highlighted group to be a single duration.
And now that I’ve explained this,
...I can articulate their second interaction rule,
...which I’m going to call ‘duration is king’.
These aren’t individual durations tied together,
...they are one duration.
And if I click on any of them, only that
overall duration will be reflected in the UI.
And I suppose, again, this seems very logical.
But when it comes to writing quickly,
...these two rules have some
really annoying consequences,
...where Dorico’s corrections
actually become obstructions.
And remember that question I asked
at the beginning of this video?
'How much suffering is involved?'
Well, that’s what I’m about to show you now,
...a bunch of seemingly insignificant
issues that really add up
...as you encounter them hundreds, if not
thousands of times in a single score.
Okay, so here I’m copying this little flourish,
...and I want it to be placed on
the last eight note of this bar.
In Sibelius,
...I can do this by clicking on that rest
and changing it to a smaller subdivision
...so I can quickly select this last
rest 8th note and paste it here.
Then I just need to clean up those first two rests again,
...and then I’m done.
With Dorico, I can’t do this because
...you guessed it,
...it’s really sloppy to allow multiple 8th-note
rests like this in finished music, so
...they disallow it completely.
Instead, we need to choose a workaround.
One way is to add a dud note first,
...and then select the final rest,
...paste in your music,
...then go back and delete the dud note.
But the solution Dorico recommends
is to simply paste the flourish here,
...and then use the shortcut:
'alt + cmd/command + right'
on Mac to shift it over two spaces.
But again, this is slower,
...and depending on the particulars,
...usually requires a little bit of thinking
and additional problem solving.
Another major pain is how ties are handled.
So, because the Dorico team wants us to understand
how the app internally handles note durations,
...if you select a tie, you automatically
select the notes it’s connected to,
...which is... okay.
But, they’ve decided to go all in with this idea
...by completely preventing you from selecting
any of the notes or ties individually.
And because of this, you keep coming
across these little mini puzzles.
Like, I want this note to cover these two rests,
...so... right,
...these add up to a half note, so...
Okay, a dotted half note will do it.
Like a Grade 3 refresher test.
In Sibelius, I can just select the last note and extend it.
This is particularly useful when
you end up in a situation like this.
In this case, I want to extend
the duration to fill that last rest.
Yeah, a dotted half-note isn’t going
to get you out of this one, is it?
At this point, the only thing you can do in Dorico
is to fiddle with this duration toggle down here,
...and use a shortcut to extend the
length of this duration by that amount.
Yes, they have the answer,
...but it’s a slow answer.
As for ties, you can’t delete them
without deleting all the other notes too.
Why do I care so much about being able to delete ties?
Well, because being a composer and not an engraver,
...my score is an evolving document
and I change my mind a lot.
Here in Sibelius, if I want to have this as a separate note,
...I just select the tie and delete it,
...then change the note.
In Dorico, no such luck.
You could learn another shortcut:
Holding 'alt' and 'shift' and pressing the left arrow key
...to reduce the duration,
...and then you have to just rewrite the note.
But, this isn’t good enough because it compounds the
work you have to do if there are multiple tied notes.
So, recognising this,
...Dorico created another button called the 'Scissors',
...which, when you press it, deletes all the selected ties,
...which feels a bit like a nuclear option.
Look, if I want to split this group of...
...urgh, I mean... this single duration in the middle,
I need to Scissors all the ties away,
...then re-add them here.
Then re-add them here.
In Sibelius, I delete that.
Done.
Now, I’m all for consistency,
...but this particular refusal to allow
users to select ties and delete them,
...comes across as obstinacy,
...and I sometimes wonder if the Dorico team weren’t
suffering a little from ‘Let’s Be Different’ syndrome
...to distinguish them from Sibelius and Finale.
I don’t know.
It just doesn’t feel like a feature.
It feels like a pain.
A scissory pain.
Here’s another consequence of
Dorico correctifying your score.
Say you’re writing a piece with very
specific dynamic instructions.
For example, offsetting dynamics played over
long durations on multiple instruments like this,
...which is common in spectral music.
Well, best practice is to split the tied notes
into unconventional groupings when needed
...in order to specify exactly where
the dynamics begin and end.
Left by itself, the system I’ve described so far
would make this impossible to achieve.
So, recognising this,
...Dorico created a new button called 'Force Duration',
...which allows me to lock the duration
so it won’t be automatically corrected.
Here, I’ve copied and pasted
the dynamic timings that I want,
...and now I need to set the
durations to match those timings.
And wait until you see how much faff is involved in this.
First, I have to use the scissors,
which removes all the ties.
Then I split this so I have a quarter note on the 4th beat,
...where the fortissimo dynamic is positioned.
So, I click on the first note
...and press the 'Tie' button twice to extend it.
Bear in mind that if I press it again at this point,
...it would recombine everything
in this bar all over again.
So I now need to make this quarter
note stay here and not go away,
...so I select it
...and then apply the ‘Force duration' button here.
Finally, I press the tie button a few more
times to link it all back together again.
When you are familiar with the Sibelius workflow,
...this is difficult to be satisfied with.
With Sibelius, I just change the durations
to be the way I want them to be
...and reapply any ties I lose along the way,
...and I just tidy up any loose ends afterwards.
No special modes needed.
The tidying up doesn’t bother me because it’s faster
and I don’t need to formulate a game plan in advance.
And this brings me to one visual
criticism I have of Dorico:
This panel,
...with its collection of buttons that are styled identically
...but which work in very different ways.
Generally speaking, it’s a good idea
to differentiate things visually
...to indicate differences in function.
To give a blunt example:
Switches turn things on and off,
...checkboxes are conditions,
...and buttons are usually reserved for actions.
You can be more subtle than this
...by having different sizes or arrangements,
...but here, well...
This first button is a condition that alters notes
before or after you place them on the score.
This 'Rest' button is a condition that
can only be applied to the score,
...but you can’t convert a note to a rest afterwards,
...which is weird.
This 'Chord' button is an on/off setting.
This 'Tuplet' button is an action that can only
be applied to something already on the score.
This 'Grace Note' button is a condition
that applies to the selected duration,
...but often doesn’t do anything,
...and then turns off for reasons I can’t figure out.
The ‘Input Mode’ and ‘Lock to Duration’
buttons are on/off settings.
Input mode deactivates Chord mode,
by the way, so watch out for that.
Then there are our old friends ‘Force Duration’ and ‘Cut',
...which are actions that can only be applied
to notes that are already on the score,
...although ‘Force Duration’ can be unapplied,
...whereas 'Cut' is one and done.
The 'Tie' button is an action that
only applies to notes on the score.
And saving the best for last,
...there’s ‘Select’, the on/off setting
that makes these buttons not work.
In testing, I watched people flounder around
with this panel over and over again.
Why?
Because it’s a disparate collection of
on/off toggles, conditions, and actions,
...which are all identical-looking
...yet which work in completely different ways.
The communication sets up expectations
that contradicts the actual logic.
And speaking for myself,
...even though I’ve been using
Dorico every day for over 8 months
...and have written a full orchestral piece in it,
...not to mention the fact that I’ve
watched a gazillion tutorials about it,
...and read god knows how many
forum posts and articles about it,
...this panel still manages to wrong-foot
me nearly every time I use it.
Here, I’m selecting a dotted rest,
...which causes the ‘Rest’ and ‘Dot’
buttons to be highlighted,
...which makes sense,
...but trying to alter the duration doesn’t do anything.
As a result, you end up with two different
durations selected at the same time.
Worse, I can turn off the 'Dotted Duration' button,
...which doesn't make any sense because, again,
...Dorico prevents it from having any effect.
If I press the rest button,
...Dorico resets everything.
Now, if I deselect the rest,
...the rest button turns off as expected
...but the dotted note button turns back on,
...remembering a previous state
before I selected the rest.
It's mad!
And although there’s logic behind it,
...it doesn’t work very well in practice.
This whole console is rife with
confusing behaviours like these,
...which feel sloppy and inconsistent.
They are communication errors.
Watch how much this one user struggled with them.
"So I have, uh..."
"So I have this 'Select' feature, and go right here, yeah."
"So I can add a note."
"Why can’t I put down a note?"
"Do I have to-"
"Ah, I have to turn on this feature, I think, "
"...and this feature."
"What?"
"Come on."
"Now I have to click this feature again."
"What does this do?"
"No?"
"I think I..."
"...goofed something up?"
"No?"
"No, no, no."
"I just want to write something
in the left-hand down here."
"Why do-"
Okay. After seeing all of that,
...I guess you're going to come to
the conclusion that I hate Dorico,
...but that's not the case at all.
Let me now talk about some things I really love.
So, in each video I release about music software,
...I try to include new aspects of interface
design that I haven’t mentioned before.
And Dorico, I think, is the perfect app
...to help discuss an aspect of score-creation
software that I find very interesting,
...which is how interactive notation actually works.
So, as you probably know,
...for all the major players,
...notation is displayed using vector graphics,
...rather than a raster format like PNG.
That is to say, they are drawn as a series of
2D points connected by lines and curves,
...rather than as a series of finite pixels.
The advantage of this is that,
like text in word-processing apps,
...notation can be scaled up or down
without any loss of quality.
...making it ideal for printing.
However, notes aren't stored as
a single vector objects like this,
...because if you wanted the
height of a note to be altered,
...the only way to do it would be to stretch the vector,
(which would warp its proportions and look awful)
...or you’d have to create hundreds of nearly
identical-looking versions of the same thing,
...all with slightly different heights to
try and account for every possibility,
...which would be ludicrously impractical.
On top of that, beaming needs to be very flexible,
...moving in a direction that complements
the direction of the note sequence
...and needing to be able to cross staves.
So, to help achieve this,
...elements like this note are
made up of individual parts.
You have the parts that don’t scale at all.
(in this case, the notehead and the flag)
And then you have a rectangle drawn in code,
...which is the only part that
actually gets bigger and smaller.
So if we place an 8th note here,
...the flags have been removed,
...and a vector rectangle is drawn
from this position to this position.
Incidentally, if you look closely
at the notation in Sibelius,
...you can make out all the seams where
these parts connect to each other.
Another problem with notation is the wide variety
of different sizes and spacing rules that exist.
For example, let’s look at this sharp accidental
...which is centred horizontally
to the notehead it applies to,
...which is a very simple rule.
Flat accidentals, however, don’t work like this,
...and have an ascender that rises
far beyond the height of a sharp.
If you were to apply the same centering rule to this,
...it would look completely off,
...especially if we have another note down here.
Now it’s ambiguous which note the flat applies to.
One solution would be to apply
an offset to all flat accidentals,
...so it’s always a certain number of millimetres
higher relative to the note it applies to.
Okay, that works,
...but you run into a problem when the user
changes the staff size to be bigger or smaller.
Then you’d need to calculate the offset
given the percentage change in size.
And this becomes even more complicated
if the user decides to do something like
...widen the distance between barlines.
If this was limited to only a few objects,
...it wouldn’t cause too much of a headache
for a developer to implement.
But with notation, there are hundreds
of commonly used elements,
...all with their own unique spacing rules.
For example, look at these different articulations.
Here, we can see the common
baseline they’ve all been aligned to.
But if you flip the notes around,
...the rules can’t simply be flipped with them.
Now the distances are completely different,
...and there’s no longer a unified alignment.
Not to mention, this marcato symbol
doesn’t flip at all by default.
Trying to specify
...what would probably amount to thousands of
different offsets to get everything looking right,
...and then forcing the program to calculate how those
offsets should scale when the score changes size
...would be incredibly slow-going.
So, to help drastically reduce this complication,
...notation apps took inspiration from how
word-processing applications displayed typography,
...which is, if you think about it,
...another complex set of symbols
...with subtle spacing relationships.
And the biggest component of this
...was to utilise the technology that
packages characters together.
That is to say,
...the solution was to use fonts.
The first of these was called 'Sonata',
...created by Cleo Huggins for Adobe in 1985.
Sibelius’ default font, called 'Opus',
...was created by one of its
founders, Jonathan Finn, in 1993.
The advantage of using a font to display notation
...is that you can set the precise position of
each symbol relative to a common baseline.
If you look at this sharp and flat symbol in Illustrator,
...you can see there’s a common baseline for both,
...which means that there’s
no need for individual offsets.
The same goes for these articulations too.
This is the ideal for production,
...because engraving specialists can set the
exact positioning of symbols in the font itself,
...and when they are placed on a digital score,
...a lot of this positioning nuance comes for free.
The only problem with this system right now
...is that there is no consistency between applications,
...which all have unique fonts,
...which contain different systems
for how they store notation.
So, unlike ordinary fonts,
...where there’s a standardised
mapping that everyone uses,
...which means you can simply
install one and use it elsewhere,
...choosing a font in a notation app today
often requires a lot of specialised fiddling.
So, with all this in mind,
...I want to talk about two of Daniel
Spreadbury’s most notable contributions,
...not just to Dorico,
...but to the wider notation community.
The first is called the 'Standard Music Font Layout',
...or SMuFL,
...which was setup to overcome the existing disarray,
...where each app has its own rules specifying
how notation should be arranged in a font,
...which prevents them from being usable elsewhere.
SMuFL makes use of unicode
...to assign each notated element
a specific, unchanging number.
The main advantage of this
...is that you can have thousands
of symbols all in one font,
...which overcomes the problem you see with Sibelius,
...where Opus is actually split into 18 different fonts
...because they kept running out of space.
This system is now used by quite a few notation apps,
...including MuseScore.
Daniel Spreadbury’s second big contribution
...was the first SMuFL font, called 'Bravura',
...which is available for free
under the SIL open font license.
Incidentally,
...due to this, Bravura is also packaged with MuseScore.
I personally love Bravura
...because it gives Dorico a unique, striking appearance.
The main inspiration for it
...comes from a notation system called 'Notaset',
...which was popular before programs
like Sibelius came to the fore.
The Notaset system was a clear set of
plastic sheets covered in musical symbols,
...which engravers transferred to paper
by rubbing them carefully with a spatula.
And although there are other fonts
inspired by the Notaset system,
(like Maestro, which comes with Finale)
...Bravura has a much thicker,
almost inky-looking appearance.
This is due to Daniel Spreadbury wanting
it to look like older printed music,
...and you can see this idea clearly
when comparing it with Maestro.
Maestro has lots of sharp angles,
...whereas Bravura’s edges are rounded
...to mimic the appearance of ink pressed on paper,
...which spreads out slightly before fully drying.
The difference is particularly noticeable on rests,
...and also note flags, which are much thicker.
There are still some who prefer
the sharpness of Maestro.
I just love the blunt, no-nonsense approach of Bravura.
I did find myself wondering how
it would hold up when printed,
...so I thought it would be interesting to
compare Bravura against Sibelius’s font Opus.
And the difference was actually
more pronounced than I expected.
I guess the best way to describe it
...is that Bravura really does look like a
throwback to older printed sheet music,
...whereas Opus looks like it was created on a computer.
I’m not against sharper, digital-looking notation.
Far from it,
...but in this case, Opus also seems to be
going for an old-fashioned printed look,
...and it's nowhere near as convincing.
It’s not just the font that makes
Dorico’s sheet music look so pleasant.
The team have also paid an
enormous amount of attention
...to the rules that dictate how every
aspect of the score should be laid out.
And, they implemented a ton of best practices,
...largely informed by the book ‘Behind Bars’,
...written by Elaine Gould who works
for the publishing house Faber,
...known for their beautifully laid-out scores.
It’s also worth mentioning here
...the myriad of engraving settings in Dorico,
...where they’ve gone to the significant trouble of
...showing clear visualisations and written explanations
...so the user knows what each option does.
This was one of the things about
Sibelius that drove me nuts.
The second you start looking through engraving options,
...you’re almost instantly lost.
What does that do?
What does this mean?
Regarding the appearance of your score,
...Dorico wipes the floor with Sibelius.
The notation is clear, legible and beautiful.
Also, shout-out to Dorico’s Print page.
This is one of those cases where the
layout they decided upon really works.
You click on the part you want,
...the preview updates.
Then you select the pages you want printed,
...and voila!
Extremely handy.
Okay, so one or two more pros and cons,
...and then we’ll limp to the finish line.
I mean, I've been talking about
this for almost an hour now,
...a- are you not-
...are you not tired of hearing me talk about Dorico?
Ah.
A- Alright. Anyway, let's just get through this.
If you want two instruments to be combined
on a conductor’s score to save space,
...Dorico can do this automatically.
...and it’s on a different level to the competition.
I mean, with Sibelius,
...achieving this is the hackiest of hacks.
You have to use a plugin which creates
a new staff for the combination,
...which means that if you make any changes,
you now need to do it in two different places,
...otherwise your parts won’t
match the conductor’s score.
And funnily enough,
...when you read through the description of that plugin,
...you’ll notice a special thank-you being made
...to none other than Daniel Spreadbury himself,
...who provided support to help it see the light of day.
And since this plugin has existed since 2012,
...that means Sibelius have had
an 8-year head-start on Dorico.
8 years
...with all this information at their disposal,
...and they still allowed Dorico to steal a march on them.
I think it’s pretty clear at this point that
Sibelius is massively under-resourced,
...and I sometimes wonder if their office is just a
single goldfish swimming around near a keyboard.
Oh and by the by, this combination set is one of those
things that illustrate the power of the Layouts panel,
...which allows me to create a second main score
...so that I always have one that’s condensed,
(which I call my Final Score)
...and another working score.
(where I can make everything really
small so it’s comfortable to compose in)
Then, I simply toggle over to the Final Score
to see how everything is condensing,
...and make any necessary engraving changes there.
This is the score that will eventually be printed.
It isn’t easy to figure out this workflow,
...although, I suppose if you’re
watching this, then you know it now.
I mean, it has occurred to me that
this is the ultimate Dorico tutorial.
Where’s my check, Yamaha!
The combined scores feature isn’t perfect yet
...and you’ll most likely need to spend some time
fixing the engraving to get it to be legible.
To do that, you’ll need to use the Engrave mode.
It’s fine,
...although, again, impossible to intuitively figure out
without looking through quite a few tutorials.
It’s also another example of the team
sticking way too rigidly to principle.
In this case, the rule is:
All cosmetic alterations to the score
MUST ONLY be done in Engrave mode.
This seems sensible enough when you say it, but...
...practically speaking, it can be a bit weird.
Like, if I create a hairpin and
I want to move it left or right,
...sure, I can do that in Write mode,
...because, strictly speaking, this is a writing operation.
But if I want to move it up or down,
...that requires Engrave mode.
I find this happens a lot,
...and it’s pretty frustrating to have to keep shifting
gears in and out of different modes all the time.
You can’t just get lost in the process of
score-creation without having to snap out of it,
...in order to remind yourself of
Dorico's organisational principles
...before deducing where to go.
In Sibelius, all positioning can be done by
...simply clicking and dragging it directly on the score.
And you know what?
It doesn’t hamper the writing process one bit.
It’s actually one of my favourite things about the app.
I really find myself wishing that both apps would
just emulate each other a bit more in this area.
One other thing I’ve noticed about Engrave mode
...is that it doesn’t come packaged
with Dorico Elements,
...the cheaper alternative version
that targets non-professionals,
...which I find kind of funny
...because it prevents users from making basic
corrections to elements when they become misplaced.
Want to move a hairpin left or right?
Sure thing!
Want to move it up or down?
That’s a pro feature, son!
Then there’s Play Mode,
...which feels like the part of the app
most in need of improvement.
The ambition is to create a DAW-like interface
...that allows you to manipulate settings
like velocity or expression with precision.
Its support for VST plugins is getting better,
...and its piano roll and MIDI interface are...
...getting there.
You just have to interact with it
to see what I’m talking about.
If you’re familiar with apps like
Cubase, Reason, Ableton or Logic,
...it’ll be obvious right away how far this has to go.
However, with recent releases, it has improved
...and I’d be surprised if we don’t see
some big ideas turning up here in the future.
But, like the rest of the app, there are
some really weird issues here too.
For example,
...they’ve removed the 'Solo' and 'Mute'
buttons that used to be available here.
And without them, I can't quickly
isolate an instrument to hear it.
So, this forces you to use their mixer.
And if you’re using NotePerformer,
the mixer is really no use to you
...because it lumps multiple instruments
together on one channel.
Look.
I’ve created a new orchestral score
...and it only seems to have two channels:
‘Flute’ and ‘Trombone’?
What?
Also, I really don't like this mixer.
It’s clumsy-looking, and the pan controls are awful.
On my high-definition laptop,
...if I change the panning value,
...I can’t get it back to 0 because it
doesn’t stretch across enough pixels.
And there isn't any shortcut I can press
to make its responsiveness finer
...so I have to use this ‘+’ button to
bloat the whole thing up instead,
...which means I now have to look at it more.
Urgh.
It really is a joyless thing with its
...‘Yeah, that’ll do fine’ appearance and its
...Sega Genesis buttons.
It’s kind of hard to put into words what I dislike about it.
There's-
There’s a drawing I sometimes do
to help me explain things like this.
I’ve been drawing it for years since I was a kid.
I use it to, sort of, visually explain
the concept of jankiness.
Ye- yeah.
That's it.
This is what I think of Dorico’s mixer.
Oh, and that reminds me.
How did I forget?
I completely forgot to talk about the jank!
Yeah, we’re not done yet.
We’re not limping anywhere.
It’s in the thumbnail!
I need to talk about the jank!
I ͞n͡e̴ed ͢t̷o̶ ta̷l̵ķ áb͞o͟ut ̴the ͞j̢a͠n҉k҉!
I̸̼̮͍̣͓̞̥͈̝͌͗̈̃̿̍̀́̉ ̸̝͂͑̀̏̒̀̕ ̶͉̕͝n̵̮̙̘͓̐̈́ȩ̴̨̝͍̰̩͎̘͔̥͖̭̓ê̷̘̤͉͔̟̩̹̳͎͂̾̿̃̽̐̈̔̎d̷̢̛͇̣̣̞̅͆̅͛̌̃̆́̿͗̏̽͝͠ ̴̝̗̬̱̤̗̱͈͙̙̩͇̞͐̇̓ ̷̩̑̌t̴̢̩̲͍͍̫̳̽̊̇͆̔̊͐̄̏̉̓͂̕̚ȯ̸̡̡̗̙̞͓͎̮̮̩̪̥̫̪͍̥̓̽̽̈̈́̽̐̽̌̀̅̒͘ ̵̠̗͈̘̥̱̼͔̩̠̬̣̓͂̔͂̌͊t̵̨̛̘̞͔̲̭̯͍̣̫̘͙̆̀̀́̒̊̑̋̇̐a̵̛̫̰̬̗̠̟̺͐̆̈́̈́͆̀͐̾̓̕͝l̶̥͎̣͇̪̖̦̱̗̔̌̑̋͝k̸̟̬͔̃̋͒̉̀͒͊͌͘ ̵̙̺̟̳̫̖̟̪̫̩̅̎͑̒̄́̋̿͋͐͐͘a̷̛̬̺̝̲̙̖̟̺̹͊̋̑̽̔͋̑̈́͘͜͜͠b̸̲̩̪͙̲̹͎͖̆̋̍́͗̄́̒͌̿̔́̍́̚͝ ̴̡̛̬̬̘͚̺̞̟̭͂̂̍͛́̅̀̆̅̀̓̅͂̈̋͜͜͝ô̸͔̹̟̲̣̗̜͈̠̥͉̯͚̺̌̈́̀̆̚ ̸̲̭̤̱̩̘̩̻̤̠̹̼̜͉͑͌͐ͅu̷̞̩̰̥̥̭̭̪͓̭͐̾́̓̈́̂̊̒́̈́͑́̕͝ţ̶̪͍͕̙̹̝͇̹̫̱͇̳̼̬͖̏̇̈́̽̇̓̃͊͑̕͠ ̸̢̢̲̬̳͉̫͔͈͎̣̥̊̑̅̃͋̾͘t̷̢̫̰͔͙͉̱͇̹͖̤̙̪̮̠͆̽h̷̢̡͓̳͕̘̗͖̞̬͑͌̿̒̑̚͜ ̴̹͖̱̀͂̓̍̓̑͛́̓͜e̸̩̬̮̝̯̫̙͎͙͎̜̥̓́̇̊́̏̋̂̾̿̈́̓͊̀̽͊ ̶̺͊̔̾̌͋̽̇̅̿̓̕͠͠j̵̺̰̬̲͇̺̔̊̈̎͒͠͠à̵̢̼̭̝̹̓ ̶̼̫̯̭̱͔͋̽̒̌͊̇̍̃͒͜͠ͅn̶̢̠̳̆̅͋͗̓͋̔͐k̷̢͎̜̺̥̣̫͍̻̭͑̐́̐͘̕͝!̶̡̰̹̝̭̠̭̝͔̲̮͈̩̲̺͍̃͝
I̴̢̛̩̩̗͚̙̘̖͙̻̫͆̌͐̒̅̕ ̴̛̿̊̎̿̂̿͠ͅ ̶̦͈̳̙̫̼̹̬̞̂͌̌̋́̾̓́̅̃̃͐̄̚͝ͅͅͅṈ̷̢̞̝́́͂̂̀̈̋́̚Ę̸̧̡̳̗̦̥̭͔͎͈̘̯̬͚͓̉̅̈́̎́͒͑̃̒͠͝ ̷̡̧̜̥͇̗̱̱̖̻̠͐̎͂́̿̂̎̿̕͠E̷̢̛̮̹͖̳͍͕̬̭̭͚̭͓̗͗͒̒̎̑͛̓̂̃͝D̶̗̹͉̠̽̒̈́̀͒͐͐̀̀̀̔̾́͘̕ ̶̨̢̡̨͇̘̰̱͙̖̘̭͇̳̀̇̐͜ͅT̵̠̲͚͖̟̝̭̤̤͓͔̯̤̬͉͛͛̌͗͗̏͘̕͘͝Ơ̸̧̛̠̮͙͇̹̦̲͚͇̖̯̰̩̽͌͋̒͐͜ͅ ̴̡̞͕̮̣̼͛̓̕s̴̞̝̥̿̏́̈́̓͆͒͂̂̊͘o̶̘͚͋̂̓̿̅̽̑m̴̘̖͉̪̗̤͙͍̲̦̖͎̭̤̱̀e̷̩̫̻͐̀̀͊̍̀͛̅̍̀͐ ̸̢̭̱͖͕͍͚̑͆̔̄͊̏͑͑́̃͘͝A̷̛̭̤̥̘̿̊̉̏̃̑̂̈́̓̍̑̈̔͘͘͠B̸̼̻͚͂̐̂̐́̓̈́̏̈́̓̇͊́̑O̸̩͓͙̓ ̴̧̫͎͉̯̣̫͙̭̬̥͕̟̮̎̑̍̂͆̽̐͊̒̎̕͠͠Ŭ̷̢̢͚̘̳̤͍̟̥̱̀́̑͒̐͋̄͗͊̎̓͛͛͑̕Ţ̴̻͖͈̞̠̀̋̾ ̶̛͔̍́ ̵̮̯̥̥̤̲̼͔̯̮͑͜ͅT̷̢̻̳͖͐̏̉̈́̀̀͌̏̀͐̈́̑̂͊͠H̴̞͉͈͙̺͈̙̪̒̂̎͊Ĕ̵̛͇͖̭̉͒̒̈́͑̈́͌̉̀͑́̔̃͜͠ ̴̨̝͎̄͆̐̈́͗̅̋̄͐̍͝J̸̢̲̭͈̥͙͓̳̥̹͎͍̮̘͚̩͂̐̉̎A̴̱̮̜̤͋Ņ̴̛͖͚̞̫͖̮̊̿̈͊͒̂̂͂̀̚͠͝ͅ ̷̢̘̤̱͈͙̟̳̮̝̝͉̭̄̿̾̇͒̓̊͂̍K̷͉̜̘̳̻̩̠͓̳̤̏͌́͘͜͜ͅ!̷̮̱̻̖̦̜͔̆̉̐̋͂̿̾͆͋͌͠
I̴͚̝̠̜͙̣̔̎̔̓̿͌ ̵̛̣̹͇̮̤͓̲̳̂͒͜ ̶̧̢͕̥̪̮̫̘̝͔͖̥̦̪̦̻͔͊́͂Ņ̶̡̰̰̩͕̘̜͈͉̤̖̭̥̝̜̗̇̐̑̆͊͒̃ ̵̨̢̭̞͓͇͎̟͎͇͇̪̞͍̳̲̬̮͍̓͛̀́̅͐̋͘̚͠͝Ẽ̸͓͉̌͗͋͛ ̸̠̀̒Ḙ̵̡̢̯̲̳̹̲͖̏̆̽͗ ̵̼̺̈͜D̸͔̒̆̃̎̀̕̕͘ ̷͕̗̘̭̞̩̘͈̝̩͇̍̍̂̅̏̆͜ͅ ̴̨̹̯͕̯͉̖̞͙̤̼̍̿̌̈́͊́̊̄͊͌̀͘͘͝͝͠͝T̸̢̘̹̬̈́͐̇̊̓͋̔̐̕͘O̴̧̻̪̗̭͖͈̱͎̦͚̲̭͓̣͔̼̐̔̌̍̉̏͛͜͝ ̵̮̘̞͉͙̟̫̰̘͐̀̽̽̃͛͑̂̌̆̎̑̔̕Ṱ̸̨̝̘͕̯̮̞͓̣̝̈̈́́͜ ̶̧̧͕̱̤̣͉̣̦̠̩̫̗͕̃̈́͛̾́̎̓̔͝ͅͅ ̸͎̟͎͕̺̝̼͎͒͗̋̌̔̇̔̽̏̽̈̐̐̆́̓̽̚̚A̸̲̼̽͛̀͊̉̔̍͆̈̇͑̀́L̸̨̧̺̳͎̳̭̬̪̥̥͇̬̐́̂͌̀̐͊̓̌̀̈̓́́̑̀͋̿͐ͅ ̷̦̳̬͌͋́͜Ķ̷̙̗͖̲̻̦̤̗̳̥͎͈̈́̽́̆́̂͗̀̾͘͜ ̴̤͖͇͍̖̲̮̼̩̣̼͉͍̮̮̖̝̿̽͐̒͛͒̀̏͐͒̊̊̕̕͠͠b̵̧̢̻̟̳̼̬̻̗̤̫̳̯͐̃̉ͅó̴̡̼̘̙̬̹̞̳͊͛̓̐̾͛̀̍̿̍̈́̊͒̕̕͘͠d̴̛̫̙̣̱̘̰̩̯͚͔̳̩͙̹̈́̅̋̾̽̋̿̂̍̈́͑͒͊̚͠ͅÿ̸̖̫̩́̊̆̊̔́ ̷͉̥̓̑̊͂̉͆̐͋̒T̶̗͙͔͕͓̹̓̀̓̐͠Ĥ̷̥̭̝̤́̅̾̏̅͆̕ ̸͇̊́̓͛͑̓̈́̎͂̔̚̕͘̚͠Ę̵̧̛̭̤̫̞̜̞̯̮͍̤̲̤̳̹̤͆̐̅ ̶̛͍̪͉͕̥͇̬̫̲̻͉̻̞͗͂̽̈́͆̆́͌̉̍̒̊̑̋͛̚̕ͅͅJ̷̹͔̦̅̋̎͐̚̕ ̶̞͈̥͇̲̞̻̖̯̞̹͉͎̖̞̩̒͐̏̋̌͗̀̄̓̈́͆͌̇̄̄̕͘͜͠ ̷̱̹̬̈̆̎͛̒͒̎̋͐̕͝Ḁ̶͙͔̲̠̖̻̮͚̥̥͔̌ ̶̢̡̡̛̝͎̗̹͔̖͇̝̖͖̭̗̯̣͍̓̉̾͛̋̓͛̀̓̚͜ ̵̡̻̞̠͙̭̭̺̞̣̣͎̘̤̟͖̯́̽̾̔̒̃͋͋̌̏̕N̶̡̛̛͔̦̠̻̬̫̠̙̺͎̗̔̉̂̏̒́̓͛͝ͅĶ̷͐͑ ̷̨̳̞̩͍̯̣̤̗͈̫̱͖͇́̅̒͛͆̈́̈́̒̽̂̈̊͒͗̏͘͜!̴͔͍̠͎͔̥͆̍̀͂!̵̭̩͂̿̑̀̈́̿̐́̕̕͜͜
I̵̡̡̢̡͕̰̦̫̯̥̗̟̞̘̳͂̈̐̋̅̓̀̊̀͆͐̚͘͘͝͝͠ ̴̡̧̧͇̪̭̻͇̩̉͐̓̀̆͗͒̈͛̽̌́͆̄̓̚͜ ̴̦̞̘̎́̾̕N̷͙̤̲̗̗͇͉͇̺̞̋͑̈́̀̎͗͐ ̴̺͕̭̮͇͎͖̝͓͐̈̑́̑̊E̷͖̖̣̱̗̔͒̑͌̒̋̈́̕͝ ̵̮̳͍̖͕̖̅̍̉̓̌̎̾͗͘͜ͅͅĘ̶̥̗͚̺̩̮͖̈̔̉̓̓̀̆̾̋̃̂͛̚͠ ̸̡̢̢̧̨̛͚̼̩͙̩̹̙̳͓̙̠̦̃̓̓̆̅̿̓̑̍̉̏̀D̷̢̢̳͉͓̱̰͕͕̝̝͚͎̀̓̑̅͆́̇̆͛͒̀̅̈́̋̓͝ ̵̧̢͚͎̮̩̬͇͎̱̉̈́̑͊̿͋͂̓ ̵̬̰̞̘̠̫͙͇̺̟̱̪̌̉̀̄̂̓͋̐͐͗́̀̕ͅͅT̷̨̧̡̛̮͚̲̦͖̭͔͔̮͓͓͕̱͍̋̆̾͋̔̇͊̉͋̍̐Ǫ̴̜̦̰͚͖̯͍̝͎̻͂̅͂͒̌̉́̊͊͘͝͠ ̷̬͊̆͒̆͋̚T̵̙̣̩̦͙́͛̿̔̋̊̀̿͑̀̚͜ ̸͕͍̟̄̅̒̃̿̐̓̈́̽̚ ̶̞̝̭̯͓͈̊̂̂ͅĀ̷̙̰̯̙͐̕ͅL̴̩̻̳̬͈̼̻͚̉̂̊̂̃͋̾̋̕ͅͅ ̸̧̱̲̮͈̞͕̠̩̮̊̈́̈̑͑̄̋́̌̌̀͊̀͝͝ͅK̴̫̘̩̰͈̻̝̯̤͚̗̏̏̆̊̒̀̍̀̿̅͊̋̉̾͘ ̴̟̯̗̼̗̩̠̜̩̰̦̦͖̯̥͔̇̈́̍͆̑̔̌͂̀͒̇͆̚͝͝ͅĄ̷̢̢̱̫͖̰̹͕̂͐́̌̏͂̕͠ ̸̨̛͖͇͕̻͕̦̺̮̺̯͐͝B̴̛̝̗͎̹̬̭̦͈͓͓̣̦̱̈́͊́̌̃́͂͐̃́͜ ̴̛̛̹̹̩͔̠̬͍̞̏́͑̒̓̕ͅͅO̵̠̪̺͎̱̖͑͒́͂̄̑̉̎͗͝ ̶̛̺̤̘̜͙̤͈̏́͆̐̈̈́̔̾͌͝ ̴͚̳͊̈̾̚ ̴̩̫̤̤̝̥̮̠̝̞͇̪̗͊̒̕ͅÚ̴̯͙̰̬̖̬͠T̵͎͉̻͖͔͈͐͋̊̈̂̈́̈́̔̆̿̕ ̶̛͔̻͈̲͛̔̃̈́́̀̿̽̂̌̍̚̕ͅõ̶̹̺̦̮̳͕̩͗̑̐̔͆̏͗̄͌̾̎̿̐̈́͜͜͝͝ņ̶̢̫̣̝͉̙̥̩͎̦͔͕̙̳̇̌̋͛̔́̌c̶̨͍̣̖͉͓̗̒̀̀̔̌̍̾̈́̅̀̒̚̚͝͠ͅe̷̢̨̡͇͉̯̣͙̪̟̬̋̓͐̐͗̓͜ ̸̨̧̡̙͎͕̗͚͇̞̺̹͛͐͛̕̚ͅJ̵̨̨̨̧̨̧̛̮͍̬͍̥̹̙̥̓̌̋̿͂́̈̉͐̎̈́̃͂̕̚ ̵̢̰̐̍̌͊̚ͅ ̷̠̒͌̓̃̄͊̉A̷̛͔͈̜͎̣̹͖̫͐̿́̓̏͗͆̈́̐͐̾̒̊ ̶͇̰̪̼͖͍͔̟̙͛̈̈́̈̇̀̌̂̚͜͠͝ ̷̧̻͍͕̲̳͙̖̜͇̬̜̻̩͕͓̇͜Ņ̵̨͖̯̮̫̠̭̤̭̋̋͑̓͊̅̈́̚͜K̴̡̧̹͚͔͔͇̻̤͔͚͂̅͆͑͋́͊͘ ̶̡͓͖̻̝̹̳̰̰̺͈͚̼͇̪̮͎͛̾͗́͝!̴̺͐́̒̽͂̿͗̽̇̍̄̕͠!̵̧̡̮͈̘̰̳̹̳͚̋̐̿̆̏͛͜
̶̢̬͚̲̫̫̱͚͗̏̐̿̀͠͝ ̴̢̢̦̲͎͈̝̻̞͔̙̃̓̓͗̃͝ ̵̲̘̥͉̝̮̘̝͒̎̊̿͐͑͜Ĭ̴̯̺̦̞͙̈́̑͗ͅ ̶͚̲̹̼͇̺̺̖̄̋̔́̆͌̏̅ ̵̡̛́̓̃̑̓̽̊͛͒̎̕͘ ̵̦̹̝̤̬̭͍̳̳̑̈́̃͒̓̍̔̎̆̕̚̚͜͝Ń̶̡̡̧̛͕̪̞̳́͗̊ ̴̨̛̣̞̗͉̳̞͉̟̜͚̪͔͑̾̐͒͆̒͛̀͑̚ ̴̢̨̛͇͖̘̜̜̞̯͉̥̝͕̰̣̠̀̎̊̋͆͑͗̒̿̿͋͛̚Ȩ̵̡̻͍̣̯͚̣̞̦͖̘͉̔̾͗̾̌̈̿̂̆͊̈́̅̏͘͠͠ ̸̦͕̜̭̤̹̱͈͚̐͂̀͛̈́͛̆̇̌̌ ̸̧̛͍̗̐̀͆̈́͛͒̿̈́̌̓͂̒͒͘͘E̴̡͎̘̗̘̣̹͕̬̪̐͗̑̔̈̉ ̶̳̝̟̠̹̭̋͌̐̿̚D̸̢̮̞̮̺̲̣̖̲͇̬̲̟̪̆ͅ ̶̧̡̢̧͔̪̘̻̣̱̱͈̟̺̻͉̏̓ ̸̝̻̫̰̅͘͜T̷̲̣̮̯̟̰̱̓̈́̄̌͝O̶̖̠̻͓̾̽̈́͋̌́̈́̆̓̎͌͜͠ ̵̡̧̡̡͕̰̱͎̘͕͔̮̻͉̤͉̆͂͆̕ ̵̡̛̛̬̥̤̤̟̭̎͐͋̊̔͒̽͋̔̈̂̕T̶̨̮̠̖̱̼͇̏̊̑̀͒̉̐̑̽͐͒̿̑̕ ̷̧̛̖̥̙͂̀͗̆̍̅̆͗̊ ̷͔̣̖̥͇̹̬͛͑̃͋̀̈́̓͘̕ͅ ̸̨̻̗̦̫͔͎͎̗̖͈͖́͒͒͜ͅA̴͎̲͓̎̾̋͑̑̉͒̈̎͊̋L̵̛̛̛̰̲͈̉̾̔͆̋͐ ̵̡̨̛͓̟̥͕̗̙͓̝͓̒̅̊̒̑͝͝ͅK̴̨̢̢̡̧̛̞̭̪̗̱̤̘̝̬̤̝̒̈́͆̑̔́̄̆͒̿̕ ̵̬̘͕̣̈́͑̅̃̈́̈̈́̓͘͠͠ ̷̡̝̬̖̰̗̦͚͈̻͉̟̹͍̹̌̌͐̎́A̷̪͍̫̯̅̅͗͆͋͂̊̐͘͘͝ ̴̢͎̣̯̲̟̱̝͈̤̘̲̂̈́́͋͗́̃͘͜ ̸̡̯̻͕̥̪̪͇̺͚̺̈̐̿̃̿̓̀͋̂̕̚ͅͅB̸̼̰̠̘͇̘͖̩̄̓͊͆̾͆͐̈́͌̏̿̾̍͜͠ͅ ̸̛̠̹̺̞̙̳̳̆̉̐̚ ̶̢͔́̓̎̿͂̏̃̐̄͝ ̵̨͉̪̖͇̼̩̖̅̀̃̓̽͑͑͆́͊̕͠Ȍ̵̧̨̞͈͓̘̙̟͉̫̙̲̱̪̣ͅ ̷̡̧̙̠̪̗͈̮̯̖̩̜̜͕̮̊̄̀͗͋̋̒̂͊͊̕̕ ̸̧̛̮̺͉̽͑̾̀̊̊̂̎̂̕ ̴̡̗͓͈͉̟̦̤͔͍̘͚̩̔͊̍̌̽̄͗͜ͅU̶̢̡̢̙̱͕̦̞̗̲̯̺͓̓͗͒͂̄͌͑̎T̵̮̾͊̒̓̊͂̐́̊̈̐̑̕͘͝ ̵̱̪̗̺̐̈́̌ ̵̦̥̬͖̰͚͚͚̯̬̪͍͐̋̌̍͋͗̈́͐̐̈́̏̔͐͝Ţ̷̨̤͙͖̞̜͉̪͚̔͛̎ ̴̡̡̲̱͍̲̘̣͋̋̍͘͝ͅÈ̸̹̳̯̪̤̳̆̇̈̈́̋́͘͝H̵̢̛͇͖̯͖̖̳̝͆̕ ̴̨̢̡̲͈̠͍͔̫̃̈́̚͜͠t̴͍̭̣̐̅̿̈͊͛̈́̓̇͂͑ö̷̰́͛͛͑̒ ̵̢͉̲̭̓ ̶͇͙̠͖̝̪̲͓̩̝͑̂͑͆̓l̶̙̹͍̤̮͖͎͙̖̦̣̜̟̀̆̀͛́̽̿͋̉͂̚̕͝͝ḓ̵̾͛͐͒̉̿͐̈́̋ ̸̛̳̍͋́͒́̄͠ ̸̧̬̬͚̹̙̙̼̝̭̺͔͇͐!̵͔̹͔͈͓̬̦̻͖͚̮̯͑͑́̑͐̅̃̔͜!̵͎̝̔̎͜
̴̡̙̟̮̮̻͍̯̬̔̓̏̅͐̃ ̴̬͓̹̬̘͇̱̅͆̓͘ ̶̡̡̝̞̬̺̥̠͓̱̹̤̳̈́̄͗̈̓̉̚I̵̜͓͉̼̯̳̬̼̾̍̏̀̉̇͐͆̓̀́̚̚͘ ̷͚̥̆̌͆̍̿̅̂ ̷͔͇̰͙̆̋͂̑́͛̐̌͛͝͝ ̶̧͇̍͐̋N̴̨̛̖̦̥̞̹̟̝̱̙͚̑̒̈̇̀̍̑̓̌̐ ̶̘̮̮̟̪̬̝̄̅̉͌̏̋̍͊͐̃̿͐ͅ ̵̮̺̯̍Ḙ̶̲͓̤̟̪̣̮̤̤̟̿̓͌̈́̃̎͝ͅ ̶͔̟̈̆̽́͘̚ ̷̢͚͙̳̜̦̤̏͜Ë̵̡̮͇͓͔͈̺́̎̃̅̆͐̾͛̿̔͝ ̸̦̐̓͋͘͝Ḑ̶̱͇̖͍̥̮̗̫́͑͗͐͛ ̴̨̗̙͈͈̦̗̩̥͓͇͓͊̈̊̍̑̈́̅̋͒̈͘͜ͅ ̴͓͍̄T̸͈̠̘͙͖̻̮̝̼̠̫̏͆̓̄͋̈̏̄͌͘͠Ò̴͖͇͍̞̳̀ ̴͈͎͍̠͖̪̥̥̠̳͆͒̋͠ ̶̢̧̬͍̰̼̗̯̈́̒̏́̋̉̐͊̂̆͝͝͝Ṱ̷̨̝͓͙̦̦͈̭̬͋̎̍̌̓̀̿̈́̓̆͐͂͗͋ ̶̛͇͕͉̦̐́ ̸̨̢̝̪͉͈̖̯͎̯̦̏̏̏͊̄̉͐́͌͑͌̆͑͠ ̵̺̞̜̗̮̱͓̜̌̀͑̎̋̕ͅẢ̶̱͎̬̼͈̙̭̻̦L̸͈̳͓̝̔̂͌̔̽̚͝ ̴̘͔̦̯̼̹͇̆͑͗́̈͛́̽̎̅̕͠ͅK̴̡͈̘̘̖̳̭͖̅̾̂̏͆ ̴̟̭͎̰͕͆̾̈́͑̈̾̉́̔ͅ ̸͈͍̲̤̱̙̪́̃̃̂̈́̃̇͂͊̓́̓͊Ą̶̢̬͙̖̭͙̫̤̲̬̀̀̃̽ ̶̘̥̠̝͐ ̵̧̭͚̱̼̇͋̊̇̏̉͗̅̚B̴̢̻̮̜͈̬͓̠̲̹̯̘̻̽̽̓̓̄͑͊̌̇̋̌̈́͝ ̴̢̬̫̤̤͚̹̟̈͂̕͜ ̸̢͔͔̥̙̂̉ ̶̧̛̜̼̩̰͙͖͎͚̖̝̓͛̽͂͊O̷̼͎̼̪̬͌̓͊͛̔̚͝ ̴̨̛̪̤̺͕̳͉̟͇͓̰̣̝̒̌̊̍̄̋̈́̔ ̸̢̧̨̲̻̯͎̠̮͈͕̳̿̅̈́̏͗̀́̉̍̀̌̇̌ ̸̨̣̳̪̰͓͎͔̻̣̭̘͐́͆̔̽̋̀̽̔ͅU̵̪̩̱̰̗̱̟̬̤̎̀̑̊̇͘Ṫ̴̝̲̮͓̮̆̇̿͜͝ͅ ̸͕͎̻̹͔̄̈́͒̀̆̓̌̈́́͋͘ ̷̡̦͔̫͈͛̒̈́̂͠T̴͔͇̤̼̗̣̞̖̳̥͔̋̃̆̅̆̃̾͛̈͋̽̔͘ ̸̧̛͈̹̭̮̱̼͚̞͚̏̂̀̋̇̍͋̊ͅE̸̙̺̋H̷̦͔̞̮̓́͒͌̀̕͝ ̴̱̳̪̜̫͍̋̉̇͝͝J̶̛̛̻̗̭̬̫̱̠͚͛̃͋͒̈́͛̑̂̔̌̌͝ ̵̛͎̜̟̈͋̿̆̊͊̇̀̄͌̌͘Ä̵͉̮̭̠͈̙̲̰̜̅͘͝͝N̴͓̫̙̙̮̺̞̉̄̐̔͗̾̓N̴͉̞̼͒̎̀̐̎̒͋̍͝K̶̥̩̠͊̎͊ ̵̹̦̳̫̝̺̞̾̈̔̇͝͝ͅ ̷̡̡̛̝͍̺̓̑̈́̈́͛̓̽̚ͅm̵̢̛̛̥͈̹̝̮͖̯͙̫̗̈́̈́̉̇́͑́̕͜͝e̴̦͇͔̣̾̆̒̽̂͆̈́͊̎̔͊͊̅
w̷͚̘͓̬͛̈́͊͋̾͆̎̄͛̅̕͠͠͠h̴̨̛͉̞̗̱̑̄̈͛́͆͌̓̈́̂͛̇͂̚͠͠a̶̢̨̞̪̦̣̹̞̦͇̣͈̦̺͐̈́̃̋͋̀̊͗̕t̴̟̟̠̟̩̪͈̳͖͎͔̥̺͔̗͆̈́̇̒́̂̕͜ ̷̡̢̠͔͉̭̹̠͖͛̓͊̊̅W̸̧͈̲̜̲̮̮̰̫̩̞̜̍̐̀͗͘͝͝H̸̺̱̟͉̪̫̟̖͉͗̍̿͗͜Ǎ̴̗̭̹̦̥̜͍͖̼̓̍̎͑́̈́̿̆̈́͘̕̕͝T̸̡͚̬͖̥̾͊̾̅̕͠ ̴̢̢̤̖̲̥̞̟̩̈́̄̋̏̇͛̃͛̓͊͋̋̀͛̆w̶̞̭͖̥̻̼͇̰̹̬͌́̔̃̽͗̊͛͝h̶̡̡̼͕̜̖̝̼͇̫͎̮̥̰̟͎̬͘a̷͚̤̖̞̬̺̫̿̽̀̇̉͝ţ̶̦͉̙̳̭̯̠͚̫̹͙̃̃́̀͋̽̍̍̊́̒͠ ̸̨̧̼̼͕͓͓̠̥͙̝̪̻̫̿̂̆͊̈́̀́̌͗ͅW̸̧̢͍̤̰͈̲͕̘̾͐̍̇̓͌́̆͘͠Ḩ̶̢̧̥̰͖̫̭̤̻̝̮͓͖̞͒̌̇̅͒͝͝ͅA̶̧̨̠̘͓̮̝͔̝͎̅̎̋̓̓̔̈̊̇͊̐̇͝͠T̷̨̡͈̹͖̳̳̹͙͇̟̉̄̓͠ ̸̨̛͊̇̌̓̌̇̕ẘ̶͎̈́̽̀̅̊̊͆̚̕͝͝h̴͙͖̖̼̮̬͖̙͂̂̒̃̓̊̅̚a̸͖͍̮̲̰̜͈̤̯͆̍ͅt̸̡̳̣̘̫̱̻͖̓͗͑́̌̿̚ ̷̱̹͚̟̥̲̳̮̳̤͖̣͚̦̳̩͌́̂̈́͛̓̿́̈̑́̕̚͝ͅW̴̡̨̢̡͔̟̹̪̼̝̙̼̠̊̆̿͂̋̌͜H̵̢̢̧͇̙̫̝͇͈̹͎̭̍͑̈̅̚͜ͅA̷̺̞̜̟̖̤̘͓̠̤̔͊̓͆̂̏͋͛̍̊̓͘͘͜͠͝ͅͅT̸̢̢̬̥͔̟̮̪̹̥͈̩̩͛̋̀̇́̃͒̋ ̵̢̡̢͇̤̲̬̞̪̪̰̺͕̯̳̏́͂̓̒̽̂̚͜͝ͅw̸̡̺̯̠̲̖̻͉͍̙̮̑͋̐͌ͅh̵̠̼͈͔̥̬̰̖̗̹̐̑͌͂̄̄͠͝ā̸̛͚͇̯̪͍͈̟̊̑̊̈̂̓̋̿͘t̷̪̟̣̬͍̺͈̥̻̓̈́̆̈́͐̌̆̑́̉͌ ̷̗̞͕̤̎̊́̿́͐̓͋̈́̏̓̒̏͆̀̃͘W̸̢̡̡̮̦̺͚͕̱̚ͅḨ̵̹̟̱̜͔̙͈̠̭̯̔̽̂͊̌̏̽͒͑̚Ȧ̶̢̨̛̻̫̩͔̼̮̋̀̊̈́͂͊̕͘͝ͅT̶̛̩̙̬̬̞̺̒̑̎͊̒̐̃̑͑́̓̂̓̏͘͠ͅ ̷̧̢̛̩͈̩͖̬̥͉̘̭̄̐̀̏̀͂̓͗̄͋̋w̸̩̱͎͛͒̈́͒͊́͑̈́h̴̥͗̽ă̶̞̙͚̯͍̩͓̗̯̩̺̫̹̖̰̎͐͛̿̽͒ṫ̶̛̙͚̭̠̣͈̍͊̔̾̃̍̚ͅ ̸̯͔̩̞̣͙͎͓̹̪̲̀Ŵ̵̧̧̡̯̞͎̥̫̪̻͉͈̹̑̈́̂̌̀̄͆̓͜H̴̨̢͕̟̙̘̖̥̲͐͆͆̕A̶̡̮͈̦̪̜̬̦̲̯͍͙̱͚͖̔͆͛̅̃͑̓͜T̷̢̧͍͖͓͔̰̫͈̣̙͔̱̲̠̥͌̐̓̎̈́̾̿̈́͗̕̚͝͠͝͠ ̷̢̛̱̣̱̝̬̺͙̟̜̯̺̭̰̲͉͒́̕ẅ̶̧̨̭̯̭̘̱͇̼͚̬̟̮̝̞́̀̅ͅh̴͓͇̫̣͌͐̋a̷̢͓̚ẗ̸͈͖́̏̈̽͌͐̐͂͑̚̕ ̴̯̟͕͍̖̜̲̂̅ͅͅW̷̛͓̺͇̏̀́͂͌̆̏̑͌̆͌̌̉̈́̕͠Ḩ̶͍̫̣͈̥͆̓̀̕Ą̴̮͓̳͇͇͙̦̰͎̲͚̂̑͆͊͊̈͌̔̍̐͘̕͠T̴̢̢̹̥̲̦͙̩͊̈́͗̓̚ ̶̧͈̦̞̗̤̩̲̰̰̮̹́͌̀͒̄͑̾͆́͂̈́͒̋̄̚̕͜D̶͇̭̱̤̦̺̤̳̩͍̟̼̘͇̩̘̊͐͂͆̌̆́͝A̷̡͙̙̯͔͖̫̘̘̟͎͚̼͊̈́͂̈́̏̌̊̀̾̂̉̿M̴̙̰̞͗͐̊͐̋̀̑̅̂̔̉̓͝͝͠N̸̢̨̈́̿͊͛ ̷̡̛͕̲͈̱̮̣̝̀̑̓͋̆̋͑̾̃͂̓̍̚Y̶̭͍͖͈̝̱̜̱͚̯̯͆͑͆̇́̒̊̀̈́͌͂͋̃͑͘͝Ȅ̷̲̍̎̅̈̐̎̒͝͝!̷̡̧̡̛̲̫̳͓̞͓̗̫̙̣̦͕̪̐̒̈̃́̽͂̌̾̎̑͠!̶͍̳̺͖̲̬̞̬̬̣̝̯̞͐̒̓ͅ!̸̛̜̜̬̉̌̈́̑́͒̈̔̕͝͝ͅ
Ḑ̷̧̛̳̟͕̱̥̝̞̘͚͎̱͓̩̝͎̘̭̬̜̙̫̩͈̝͕̼̟̲̩̹̼̼̥͇̝̪̙̱̺̜͖̼͋̎̌̋̐̌̈́͌̽̎͌̈́̈́̓̌͌̀̓̇͑̅̎̉̂̓̀̅̅̈́̏̅͂͛̉̈́̈̒̍͐͌̀̽̔͂̚̕̚̕̕͜͝͝͠͝͝ͅã̶̡̛̛̩̹̬̰̙̝͓͇͎͚̼̙̙̟̲͍͎͔͙͓͔͎̮̗̫̩͚͎̺͔̀̿̒̈́̍̀̓̐͂͂͑͐̀̀̌̈̈́͆̽̉͊͂͊̃̃̓̽͛͊̄̉̄͆̚̕͝͝͝͠ͅ ̸̢̢̢̛͚̪̲̯̱̰̩̥̼̙͙͔̜̩̣͎̺͚͔͔̻͓̠͖̐̔͗͛͜͜͠͝ͅͅͅm̸̢̧̢̧̞̮̰̻̦͍̳̙̞̼̯̟̘͈̩̘̟̗͕̰̦̗̦̞̬̱̞̪͖̲̞̭̫̪͔̣̣̮͌̈́̅̀͒̈́̓̀̄͂̑̀͑̿̈̀̈́̋̿̒͋́́͗̂͊͐̀͊̍̄̒̽͗̇̕͜͜͠͝͠ͅͅŅ̶̡̧̨̧̛͕̖͖̖̭̣̫͚̦͉̺̗͚̗̥̳̜͔̱̤̰̰͙̠̯̟͇̺̠̮̩̿̽̓̽̑̎̊̃͂͋̇́̿͑̾̊̐̉͜͜͝͝͠ ̵̧̨̙̫̹̠̝̟̦̞͔̦̙̝͚̺͔̮̗̤̻̟̣̥̜͇̫̺̯̤͈̞̦̰̹͚̘̻͚̼̣̘̹̜̲̯͍̲̠̉̔̏̽͊̾̽̓͌̐̃̏̋̾̌̑̃͆͋̿̈́̒̌̈́̕̕̚͝͝ͅͅͅÝ̶̨̨̧̢̢̡̡͖̦̦͇̱̤̬̫̫͈̥̪̖͓͕̦̺͇͍͔͖̹͈͔͔̯̞̜̜͖͇̝̫̖̺̬̜͍̰̙̗̓̋͌̎̈́́̾̎́̑͑̐̾̏͘͜͜͜ͅͅͅ ̸̢̛̱̩͚͍̩̗͔̲͍͓̠̯͈͕͉͉̖̠̗͍͎̞͙̗̤̤͕͉̟͖̣̹̰̝͗̽͛̃͂͌͆̂̀͐̓͗̂̏́̄̅̔̒́̄̉̎̇̍̂͐͂͌̋̎͌̋͂̈̑̃͐̀͋͘͜ȇ̶̢̡̡͍̩̟͍̲̥̻̙̱̝͖̫͚̞̟̰̼̈́̃̌̆̀́̉͐̌͐̿̈́̈́̽͋͠ͅ!̴̧̛̛̛̖̰̥̯̦̺̫̝̻̣͙̹̤̩̜̼͎̓͊̏̈́̽̊̎́͑̑̀̎͋͐̃̒̀͛͗̄͌͌̎͑̌̓̊͌̈́̍̑̈́͆̈́́̋͊͂̈́͛͌̾́͆̃̕̕!̸̡̡̡̢̲͖̩̹͓̤̲͎̣̬̼͎̳̫̙̰̩̼͓̞͚̯̘͙͈̝͓̞̩͚̼̯̞̻͕̖̠͎̠̪̹͙̤̠͖̲̠̮͑͌̔̔̌͌̍̐͐̽̽̔͘͘͜͠͝͝͝ ̶̧̢̧̧̛̬̺̫̰̪͙͇̰͕̼͔̦̩͔̭̹̮͙̜̩͎̲̖̺̲͉̹͇̹̥̝̣̲͙͍͍̺͓́̀̇̒̑̾͑̔̽͑̓̑̽͂̀̀̇̈́̆̌̏̋͛̊̌̈́̎̽͆̽̀̈̓̍̕͘̕͜͝ͅ ̷̧̧̧̡̳͙͉̫̦̺̝̥̫̣̱͇͕̭̱͚̤̙̙̯͙̼̺̞̜̭͙͎͇̺͈͕̮̥͉̙̝͍̩͇̳͓́̎̐̆̍̎̎̈́̈́͂̔͂̉̿̀́̈̿̓̉̅͛̇̽̒̍̔͘͜͝ͅͅl̸̨̧̝͍͉͕͈̘̙̯̼̖̰̰̜̙̻̫͈̦̤̰̮̽̽͌̾̈͑̎̎͒̄̐̀̉͐͐̈́̑̉͒̂̎̐̿̂̎̆̀̄͛̋͐͐̍̅̓̓͋̓͘̕͝͝Ę̷̡̧̛̛̛̺̺̥͈̥͉͙̦̠̠̪̰̘̲̖̘̹̻͉̭͍̤̖̬̣̝̖̻̪̙̼́́̐̾͛͐̌̐̽̽̆̐̀̈́́̎͌͂̂̓̈̀͒͘̚͝ ̸̤̰̼̽̐̒͑́̍̐̔̊͊̅̿̈́̋͊͋͂̂͒͑̆́̿̎̐̄̉̇͌̈̓͋̈́̃͊̆͘͘̕͝͝t̷̢̛̳̦̼̝̤̪̠̝̼̖͍̯̩̠̘̮̲̟̘̣̰͇̖͎̫̫̥̯̯̣͔̠͍̪͉̮͎̯͚͍̘̙̪͕͎̫͍͓̊̂̀͗̄̋͆̄̒͋̑̓̿̉̄̓̔̏̽̎̀̏̐̈́̿̓̒́̄̓͊̈́̓͘̕͜͜͝ͅͅͅ ̵̡̢̨̡̨̢̨̖͓̮̗͈̦͚̗̱̝̳̙̰͙͈̜̭͖͉̝͇̠̫̩̱̼͔͚̹̝̻͎͙̼̥͓̪͈̤̻̍͆͌̊̋̈̓̏̈̒̈́͊͆́̽͜͜͝ͅ ̸̨̡̧̢̨̢̧̯̭̝̹͍̹͖͍̱͓͍͚͇̮̪̪͈̥̹̭̹̻͔̜͎̟̜͚̺̦̪̼̺͙͎͉̻̣͈̼͇̆͗̉̋͋̈͂͜͜n̴̨̢̡̨͇̞̘̻͍̤̥̗̦̣͙͓̩̱̰̣̭̰̲͕̼̲͉͕͕̙̻̟̒͜͝ͅͅ ̶̛͈̟̗͍̄̽̃͐̈́̓̓͑̓̒͊́̈́͝͝ ̷̢̛̛͎̜̗̘̯̥̱̰̎͌͋̀͌̂̌͛͋̽͐̋̓̀̈́͂̋̍͐̉̓̆̈́͋̈̄́̊̅͑̉̓͒̀͌̎̏̔̽̓͂͘͘͘̕͘͠͠͝͝͝ ̷̢̡̮̗͓͖̼̮̗̹̟̩̝̱̞̫̣̖̙̪͕̯̲̻̦̺͕̹̯̤͍̏́͊̈́͋̆͌́͋̄̈́͌͛̔́̚ͅͅE̵̡̢̡̧̨̟͚̼͉̦̝̞̬̖̟̰͎̣̬̬͔̜̖͈̮̬̰̭̦̹̱̳̣̞̞̻͓̟̩̞͔͖͕̦͙̟̰̱̰͒̅͊̓́͆̒̅̆̾̒̍̂̈́̀͌̓̈́̀͛͋̎͗̈̍͑̌̋͌̉̍̊͆̽̕̚͝͝͝P̵̧̝͍̻͍̣̗̻̬̦̻̮͎͓̘̖̗̜̱̠̃̋̈́́̽̑̈̈́̂̀͒͒̉̈̽͗͂̾̃̐̎̌̏̈̈́̐̊̋̿͊͂̈̀̊̀̅͌͆̕̚̕̚͠͝͝ͅT̵̨̨̧̨̢̡͔̺͕̙͈̻̬͖̬̫̺̺̫̯̹̰̳̦̠̜̭͍͓̰̘̝̲̗̙̼͖̹͙̟͓̺͚͖̗̜̲̲͋͝͝ ̷̙͖̬͓͉͗̃̇̿̌̉̿̍̄̿͐̿͑̏̿̑̊̆̓̉͛̈̿̉̔̿͑̒͑̆̀͂̔̇̀̂͌̕͝ ̴̡̡̡̧͇̦̫̩̠͙̤̘̞̩̜̼̺̜̻̗͈̝̥̥͓͔͍̺̙̦̜̜̩̺̼͕̙͎̩̜̠͕̜̼͂́͗̄̀̑͘͜ͅͅ ̶̢̢̢̢̨͎̲̖̯̺͓͉̳̰̰̥͕̱̱͓͇̪̺͎͚̻̣̤̗̱͕̻̼̫̜̬̫̣̰͇̤̮̤̯̣̯͙͉̳̻͑͒̀͌̑͊̔̀̑̌̾̔͊̚̕͜Ư̷̛̤̟̙̦͍̺̲͈̭̭̱̣̹̥̐̓͊̓̈́̄͐͑̏͂͗́͗̍̂̀́̽̅̇̽͛͐̉̔͐̌͆̒̾͗̾͊̎̓̋̎͛̾̌͗͆͐̈́̚̚͘͝͝͝͠͝͝N̷͙̱̥̬̓̽̑̃̑̀̐͑́͑͛̑̽̓̚͘̚͠͝ͅ ̸̡̧̧̢̛̬͉̞͚̱͓̦̗̲̟͖̗͎̲̯̤̦͙̱̪͇̱̗̠͇͎̺̟̭̗̲̗̫̣̖̱̲̙̖̟̎̉́̀̌̒̈̇̓̈́̏͌̄͑̆̏̈̅͗̐̈̋̓̇̄̈́̍̉̿̈́̅́̋̎̽̎̈̈́͋͘͘͘͘͝͝͝͠͠͝ ̷̧̨̰̤̱̠̰̬͉̙̣͎̺̫͍̽͊̌͆̂̌̆̐̆̕͠ͅé̶̡̢̡͇̠͇̳͇̪͔̲̮̤̰̪̫̭͈̩̬͍̙̻̦̘̙̙̺̮͔̠͍͔̝̹͎͔͎̹̫͙͈̋̈͑̆̾̾̃͘͜ͅ ̸̨̛̘̮̗͙̦̖̜͚͚̜͍͎̙̜͕̫̠̪̝̏̀͑̇̋́̒̂̈̉́͑͛͛̇͑͑̾̒̈̊̒͐̃̓̎̃̈́͒̋̉̊͂̍̈́̓̓͆̕͘͝ͅş̷̨̢̛̤͚̣̱̯̱̖͇̱̼̩̘͎͓̥̝̖͂͗̈̈̉́̽͑͋̽̒̃̔̾̓̐̋̒̌̎̂̅͊͊̃̈̍́͘͠͝Ť̴̨̢̢̡̡̢̲̥͕̪͇̱̣̙͈͚̮̩͉̙͍͉̟͓̖̰̦͙͆̽̐̌͆̓̀͋̍̓̆͒͋̚ͅŖ̸̧̨̢̥̗͇͎͈͇̞̰̣̞̹̻̱̝̺̟̩̤̤̩͍̺̭͙̣̬̼͂̇̈́̿ͅ ̸̢̥̗͍̠̪̹̜̗̒̀̊̊̉̑͂̔̉̚̚͠į̷̢̨̧̛̗̖͚̗̳̟̰̖͉̜̪̣͍̻͖̤͍̭̻͕̣͔̬̪̹͖̫͍͖̙̙̱̹͔̬͕͊̈́͊̋̏̅̀̇́̍̈̌̈́̽̄̓͊̋̈͐̎̌̑̋̀̍̄̍͒́̈́̃̾̍́̎̚̕̕̕͜͝͝͠͠ͅk̴̨̡̧̨̡̗̣̮̱̝̥͖̜̻͖̫̯͎͔̠̪̰̯̠̖̖̻̣̘͍̹̘͕̳̰͍̘̘̜͓̱̯̖̹͖̭̥̬̮͎͓̻̅̓̾̋̀̆͌̎̅͌̇̀̀͗́͊͐̒̀͌̔̂͛̀̑̐̃̌͆͛̐͌̀̏́͊̀̓́̍̔̈́͛͘̕͘̚̕͜͜͝ͅ ̴̢̧̢̲̹̬̦̰̬̳͖̦̪͓̼͚̱̪͙͈͈̣̮͉̪̜̗̀̚͜ͅ ̶̧̧̢̭͚̼̟̜̱̝̖̱̩̖̘̝͈̭̤̱͈̟͍͔̗̗̻̰͎̹̠̳̰͇̯̝̟̦͎̤͈̣̲̞̳͎̗̗̞͛̂̄̐̀̊̏̿̉͑̌͗̈́̅͋̊̆̿̽͗̿̿̀̿͊́͂̿̔͗͛̊̔͋̃̊̚͝͝ͅͅͅͅE̶̻̎̿̐̄̈́̿̄́̈̓́͒̍̾̓͂̆̍̒̆̓̈́̀̐͝ ̵̡̨̨̢̨̧̢̡̡̖̣̜͍̝͍̥̳̣̮͍̱̦̤̠̞͉̩̝̫͙̳͙̦̪̤̹̰̙͈̣̝̥̻̙̤͕̱̠̭̐̑͜ ̷̡̧̢̡̛̣͓͇̝͔̮̪̹̻̼̯̰͓͖̭̫̩͓̥̝̘̘̲̻̥͓͕̪̜̩̹̫̬̲̝͖͕̤̱͔̥̲͔͖͙̣̈́̓͐̋̍̀͆͌̈́̄́̊͐͌̀̋͌͂̂͊̌̂̓̈́͆͗̋͆̀͘̚͝͝͝͝ͅŸ̵͉̭̫͉͈̪̤͈͉͚̞̭͔͕̮́͆̀̐̀̾̿͆̈́̆͘͝ ̸̖̽̀̆̇̊́͊̋̓̓͊͒̊̎̔̍̆̌̌̆̒͑̈́̕̚͝͝͠E̷̢̧͔̤̪͙̪͈͈̬̥͖͔̤̤̬̣̗̻̩̥̫̼͙̞͕̠̗͇͎̥͈͙̫͓̰̫̳͉͕̳̬̭̣͓̳̞̾̓̀̒͂͑̄̆͆̈́̚͘͜ ̸̡̛̙̖̤̮̟͊̃̓̏̀̾̌̅̌̀̑̄̇̌͒̽̅̀̾͑̏́̊͊̅͋̌͐̕̚̕̕͘͜͝͝d̷̡̨͕̭͕̱̼͎̫͗́͌̎̏ę̸̡̛̻͖͖̼̲̜̯͖̲̘̗̱̩̦̭̯͖͈͖̙̖̠̥͈̠̤̳͉͎̝̦̣̭̼̭̤̥͕̥̓̀̔͌͆̅͊̽́̀̉̅͑̈́̀́͛́̑̇̊͗̇͊͑͐͊̔͑̅͗̑̚͘̕͘͠ͅ ̷̬͎̳̣͙̩̣̭̻͕̞̱̅̈́̄̌̀̈́̍͆̂͒̆̉̇̔͒̍̊̌̄̆́̃́̈̈́̿̍͑̽̕̚͝͠͠͝a̵̢̡̛̟̣̹̺͚̟̗̮̟̗͓̯͖̳̖̥̲̯̮̮̩̞͇͖͙͕͎̾̆̈́͊̾̑̏̐̆̋̆̕̕͠͝ͅ ̸̢̧̪͓͚̖̘͕̙̞̘͍͔̤̬̤̭̱̤̯̟͙̀́͂͑̒̒͋̀̒͋̀͆̈́͆̅͌͛͗́̃̍̾̏̒͜͝ͅḐ̵̡̨͖̟͈͉̗̺͍͓̜̙̙̬̙͙̖͔̰̯̞̰̗͚̩̬͉̲̠͚̙̒̿͒͌͛̆̂͒̐̂́̀͑́̌̂̌͒̎̍̒͂̾̓̀̚̚͝͠ͅͅͅ ̸̡̧̡̧̛̫̮̭̭͈̩̗̺̯̝͔͈̭͉̙̮̬̭͚͔̰̺̂͋͆̈́̾̂͂̓͗͋̒̎̂̀̌̎̊́̃̀͜͜͜ͅ ̷̞͍̱̣̫͎̲̣̪̝̳͙̭͉̺̓̈́͐̓̑́̔̓̎̆̍͐͗̈͂̌̒̉̀̏͑́͆̌̈́̌̍́̔͂̇̉̿͂̒̔̈́̌̂̉̄̓̾̀̕̕̚̚͠͝͠͝͝͝ͅw̷̨̨̧͉͕̗͉̘̙̬͚̯̟̦̻̙͇̹̼̯̪̟̖̞̘̮̯͎̰̗̭̥̩͓̻̩̼͙͎͙͎̬̹̜̺̭͙̳͚̗̙̌̋̈́̅̀͒͂̀̏̒̽̆̔̿̀̎̑̈́͜͜ͅͅ ̴̡̡̧̛̛̙̪̹̝̯͚͈̥̥̼̳͓̺̻̻̮̬̳̻̦̠͚͉̬͓̙̞̪̫͕͇̺̻̪̫̱̻̬̰̈́̒͊̀̈́͊͂́̂͗̌̈̽̊̀͆̌̓͛̈́͆̈́́͊̀̈̈̐͑̾̈̔̇̀͌͊̈́͛͒͆͂͌̾̌̕͠͠͝͝͝͝ĭ̴̡͍̠̬̓͒̓̒ ̷̢̧̢̡̧̧̛̪͍̱̭̹͇̳͓̺̫͍̞͇̦̖͓̖̣̹̭̣͈͚̰̤̫̦͙̟̂́̄̿̒̐̎̓́̈̉̒͂͗͊̋̎͐̈́̋̄̀͗̉̏̉͂̈̃͠͝͝͝ ̸̨̢̢̢̨̛̛̜̱̰̱̤̫̜̦͚̳̻͈̯̺͓͚̙̦̘̜̼͉̙̺̣͕͈͈̥̙͇̹̗̳͙̦̟̈̈̍͆̊̍͆̐͒͋̒͆̀͗̑̾̏͋̐͑͗̈́͑̊̀̓̆͛͛̉̆̀̌̒͛̑͆͌̾͐̾̕̕͜͝͠͝͠ͅͅ ̷̡̡̨̡̡̦͖̺͕͈̭͕̱̤͙̱͈͉͓̼̗̮͓̹̤̦̯̰̣̠͓͙͖͚̞͌̿̈́̐̀̂̎̒̎̿̀͗̉͂̓̚͜͜ ̴̢̧̧̡̪̞͉͔̭̘̗̪̼̟̗̟̭͇̬̞̞̙̹̻̭̜̽́̉̒͊̉̌̐̓̿̂̌̀̔͛̀̍͐̅̀̆̀̓̒̓̈́͋̄̂͋̅͗̽̊̆̐̄͋͋̓̕͝͠͝͝n̸̨̛̛̖̳̪͍̟̙̳̫̱̮̪͉̤̤̱̱̟̋̓͌͌̄̀̀̇̌̾̓͂͑̉́̊̓̂̔̀͒̀̏̑̈́̈́̉͂̇̽͂̂͘͘̚͠͠͝͝ͅs̶̡̢̧̡̢̧̖̞͕̤͓̬͖͉̖̻͇̮͍̞̯͓̫͈̬̘͔̥̬̦̹̦͖̟̖̹̈́́͗̓̽̿́̏̎̌̌̐̑̋͆̓͒͋̔͗̽͒͂̍̐̑́̇̽̈̀̂̄͗͜͜͜͠͝ͅͅL̵̡̨̡̧̛͙̟̙̬̠͖̟̻̮͙̗̯̼̤̙̲͉̥̻̱̭̮̠̝͕̝̱̝͖͍͔͔̓̑̑̎̃̽̀̈́̓̾̏̃͑̓̓͊̿̇̄̐̈̾̿̽̀̿͗̈̇̀̄̊̄̕͘͜ͅO̴̢̧̢̺̦͎͚̙͚̭͍͍̯̣̜͖̟̭̅̓̋̆͊̀̔̔͛̽̌̃̑̿͂̂̏̀̆̕͜ͅ ̶̨̦̲̩̻͙̹̮̾̍̓̇͌̚ ̶̢̢͉͎̮͎͚̻̰̹̰͖̱̙͉̬̺̫͖̭͇̣̻̯͔̹̯̯͔̦͖̘̫̦̫͖͉̪̟̎̔͌͘͜w̵̢̘͎̪̻̝̜̦̗̹̯͉̗̝͉̲̜̙͈̦̞̠̟̼̱̥͌͒̓͆̃̍̓̉̅̐̀̾͌͊͊̃̎̅͘̕͜͝!̶̨̰̺̞͍͓͔͈͙̗͙̠͚̼͉͚͔̰͉͉̖͐̏̽̾̐͑̾̆̽̇͌̉͗̓́̑̕͘͘͜͜͠͠͝ͅ ̸̦͖̰̻̥̥͉̝̪͖̲̌!̷̧̡̛̼͔̼͔͍̮̘̟͚̤̞̖̇̈́̅͋͌̃̾̑̎̍͛̓͊̓͗͒͆̍̑͋͂̆͒̓͊̅͗͑͋̕̚͝ͅͅ!̵̬̼͚͔̋̂͆̋̈́̀̀̔̔͋̈̄͋̇̎̉̋̔̾̏̇̌͂̀̑̇́͒̋̂͛͜͠͝!̷̨̧̡̨̨̧̢̛͚̭͍͖̫̯̦̰̤̬̖̠̖͙̟̖̤̟̣̭̜̖̬̱̯̜͉̦͙̖̼̱̯͚̯̭͈̪͐̈́͑̾̊̒̏̓́̎̃̊̀̀̏͆̃͂̎̏̂͂̈́̈́̐͆͆̈̑̍͗͑̈́̋̒́͐̚͘͘͘͘̕̚͜͠͝͠͠ͅͅ
H̷̨̧̧̨̨̢̢̛̛̛̛̛̰͚̥̮̦̘̩̘͓̠̜̰̜̯̺̮̠̭̩̞̝̯̰͎̙̠̱̣̜͈͉̺̮͇̖̳̹̖͈̻͚̰̩͈͙̖̗͈͎̫̝̺̼̤̫͍̟̩̹̻̥̗͈̰̳̯͓̗̘̻̞̦̤̰̣͍͚̦̪͍̭̖̟͎̬͔͕͓̙̪͚̻̭̪͕̹͙͕͂̊͗̾͗́͊̿̂̅̈̒̎̈́͌̈͑͊͆̆̓̈́̀̓̃͌́̄͛̋͑̓̓̅́̆̓̀̄͆́̌͆͊̔͒̈̾͐̏̈́̆͋̑͒̽̑̄̈́̅͌̏̃̏͂́́̈́͌͆̈́̑͒̈́̇̿̈́̊̈́́̽̽̀̈́̿̓̏̾͂͐́̃̅̑̓̆͂̎͒̄̐̈́̾̀̆̅͊̓̈́̇̓̽̿͆̅͋̅̈́͒̓̍̽̉͛̇̽̀̍̋̓̇͛͋͑̿̆͐̽̍̎͂̔̊́̔̍͒̑̊̾͋̅̌̈́͒̅̋̑̈́͒̀̾͆̎͒͆̈́̉̀̔̈́̆̉̈̊͊̍̃̈́́̊̏̂̃̚͘̕͘̕̚̕̕͘̚̕̕͘̚̕͘̚̚͜͜͜͠͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝Ḧ̶̨̡̡̨̡̢̧̡̨̨̨̡̨̧̡̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̱̺̺̘͔̩̯̬͖̖̩̬̻̭̳̼̼̦̹͚͇͈͕̺̗̳̠̫̹̰̘̖̖͚̪̻̱̯̩̖̞̻̠̫̞͙̖͉͚̟̦̬̯̹͎͇̫̙̫̹͚̙̠͓̹̠̯͕̰̭̬͓̻̗͎̫̗͓͔̩̘͈̭̙̦̺͚͖̜̤̗̜͕́̈́̈́́̋͑͑̽̀̍͑̀̇̀͌̇̑̌̒́̆̊̽̍̊̍̈́̓̀̓̓́̂̈́̋̈́̏̓̋̒͒̅͆͋̏̈́̓͗͛̀̃͑́͛̂̍͗̐͗̀̍̀̌̀͊̾͊͑̈̓̎͋̃̈́̈́̈́́͛̃̒̋͂͐͌͆̐̓̓̉̌̂̀̇͌̅͆͋̌͋͆̓̿̌̏̉̽͛͂̄͐̓̂͊͑͛̈͑̔͗̈́̒̉̍̉̒̀̏̅̏̅̾̾͗̐͂͐̂̒́͊̀̆̀͑̿̄́̇́͊́͆̒̑̀͆̾̈̓̽̌̆̍̀́́̈͊́͋̍̈́̎̈͆́͂̊́͐͐͑̏̃̋͂̾̾̿͒̀̓̂̈́̆͒̓͋̆̌̾̽͑͛̎͋̏̈͌̒̿̓́̏͊̍̾̍̋͛́̄͗̿̈́͋̿̏͋̃͒́̿̈́́͗͊̓̈̆̾̄̈́͐̈́̄͊͘̚̚̕̚͘̚͘̚̚͘͘͘̕̚̚̕͜͜͜͜͠͝͠͝͠͠͝͠͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͠͠͝ͅH̷̛̛̛̛̛̫̮̙̐̋̈́̎̌̐̀̀̓͆̈́̓̈́̋̈́̅̈́̀̊̔̉̐̆̓̓́́̂̉͋̐̍͂́́̃͌̑̓͐̋̂͋̑̂̔̂̈́̀̓́́͂̈́͐̊͒̃̌͆̓͑̑̅͒͛̐̾̋̀̄̏̾̾̍̀̒̃͊͛́́̈̅͂̌͗̓̆̔͗̾̈̊̌̒̈́̎̔̓̓̾̒͐̆͑̂̍̌͂͛̈́̆͆̿̀̾̈́̈́̀́͒̐̀̊̑̽͗̊̊͒͑͆̿̑̇̈̓̏̂̂̈͗̿͛̈́͒̽̉͋̅̆̑̂̍͗̅̾̀͐̏̅̃̋̂̈́͌͒̐͌̎͂̃̆̐͆͛͌̏̑̈́̏̿̃͗͛̿̇͆͊͌̊͒̿̒̆̄͑́̎̊͌̇̚͘̚̚͘̕͘͘͘̕̚̕̕͘̚̕͝͝͝͝͝͠͠͠͝H̷̡̡̡̨̡̡̨̢̨̡̡̡̢̧̡̛̛̛̛̼̯̯̹̥̲̬̲̘̤̤̦̖̯̤̘̠̻̼̹̲͈͕̬̠͇͎̥̲͕̼͈̩͓̻̫͚͕̙̤̪͚̖̹̩̺̪͓̦̻̯̻̹̜͈̲̩͖̥͎̝̭̟̻͙̟̳̫̺̜͓͚̣͓̞͓̠͍̭̗̥̰̥̖̞̦͔̺̼͚͙̻͎̻̪͖̲̙̯̣͚̣̹͙̟̫̖̣͕͕̤͚̖̼͇̥̲̰̟̠̫͈̹͔͖̳̦͚̫͕̣̩̙̠̝̹͎̖̥̙̙̲̺̬̩̖͍̱͙͇̯̹̩̬͚͙̻͎̰̳̦̟̣̯̭̜̿̽͐̌̓͗͗̇̑̀͌̐̒͗̌͑̒͗̎́̃̆̐͛͊̏̎͛̋͒̂́̌̈̈̉̌̑́́̆̄̽̅̅͛̍̈́̏̂̂̀̒̏̒̏̐͒́̾̿͌̌̑̀̇͂̋͗̃̅̀̉̀͑̒̑̓̾̊̄͆̉̅̊̑̉̓̅͒̈̾̋̈̿̄͛̔̽̈́͐̓̎̈̐̀͋̂͂́̑̄͛̊̄̇̍̋̈́͗̀̄͋̒̎̑͒̇̎̍̃̾̈́̋̈́͊͂͐͐̏̌̉̀̍̔́͋̑̆̒͌̅̉̌̑̈́̓͛̚͘͘͘̕̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͠͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅH̵̡̡̧̧̡̡̨̧̧̢̡̨̧̧̧̛̯̪͓͚̫͕̜̮͇̭̦̼͎̼̝̦̣̰̭̣̳̝͈̤̥̗̺̪̣̹͖̝̖̝̹̣̮͔̘̥̲̼̺̠͚͚͕̞̤͎̬̯̹̻͍̣͔͕̖͍̱̤̹̖̰̲̺̻̠̫̻̪̬̬̮̦̱̞͔͚͕͕̤̟̫̹̦̤̬̻̹̼̯͚͉͚͚̘̹̺͎͉͈̥̲̰̙̜̦̯̳̹͙̦̻̻̹̲̙̪̦̣̣̪̙̗͉̩̟̯͋̅̓͂͗͑͑̔̇̈́͒̈͒͂̓̀̿̓͌͛͒̿̍̅̾̓́̌̒̀̑́̔̾̾͂̂̾͋͑̂̍̑̓̌̽͊͂͗̈͛́́͐̃͊̅̓̆̀͂̌̑̔̊̊͋̇̈́̈͒͛̀͗̾̽̎͆́̉̈́̿̉̍̃͑̈́́̂͂̅̈́͊̀̓̂̀̊͗̂͊͊̿̔̾̌̉͊̅̎̏͐́̏̃̆̈́̋̓̒̾͂̾͂̆̑̋̅͆̄͋͗̑͋̀̐͛͒̓̀̆̽̈́̉͋̈́̈̀̂̋̉̿̇̉̍̄̊̓͆̊̐̽̅̃̾̀̌̀͂̒̐̄̈́͆̚̚̕̚͘͘̕̚͘͘̚͘̕̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͝͝͝͠͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅḨ̸̢̢̨̧̨̡̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̹̖̮̮͔̞͍͙͔̯̫̮̹͓̙̩̫̰̥͕̲̫̰̻̝̻̭̞͈̲͍̼͕̠̬̺͍͎͈̖̹̻͉̣͔̞̝̲̰̪̜͎̥̟̥̱͍̖̤̩̜͕̖̼̥̯̫̹̝̤̰̬̟̺̹̜̪͈̤̭̻͓̼̳̟̥̑̍͐̅͌̐̇́̂̾͂͛͌̇̏̋̇̈̂̅̍̎̅͆̀̆̔̌͐̿̇́̾́̿̈́̍̔̏̐̐͗͆̉͑͆̏̽͋̿́̎̈́̓͆̂͑͋͑̃̑̔͊̓̀̓̀̈̆̑͒̈̐̍͆̉̉̊͂͛́̾̀͋͒̾̊̏̏̓͒̀͐̉̿̈́̿̌̓̀̀̉́̔̿̔̈́̓̔̏́͌̈́͂̒̆̈́̃͋̇͂̉̃̂̒̑̂̈̑̔̀̇̀̐̄̃͌́̂͛̄̿́̽̀̋̅̈́̍͌͒̽̎̎͑̀̈́̆͑̄̀́̓́̈́̓́̋̆̾̀̐̈̅̊̐̊̎̆́́͌̊́̆̄͑̇͛̅̋̓̎̆̀̒̅̑́̅̓͂̎̆͆̔̏͋͆͗̀͌̈͑͐͊̀͊̏̂́̂̑̂̃̀̐̀̽̀̈͋́͂̽͊̏̔̌̂͆̆̐̐̓͋͂̈́̍͑͘̚̚͘͘͘̕̕̕͘̕̚͘͘̕͘͘̚͘͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͠͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅH̷̡̨̨̡̡̡̡̨̡̧̡̢̨̡̢̡̢̨̧̢̡̧̛̛̛̛̛̛̙͔̘̟͖͍̜̼͍̤̗̤̪̰̞̝̼͓̥͚̠̮̼̰͈̜̼͈̤̯̗̬̱͍̞͓͎̦͇͉̞͇̜̺̻̰̮̙͚͔̣͎͙̯̺̘̙̫̣̲̼̤̪̦̗̙̜͕̠̲̹̲̠̭̘͇̟͉̦͓͎̝̝̣̖̜̥̲̗̼̰̖̞̮̗̟͍̖̝͕͓̖͎̟̯̱̱̟̩͍̪͉̣͙̦̭̟̗̯̠̦̦̝͉͉̝͖̻̪̞͔͚̣̩̟͚̜͉̩͍̞̹̲͎̬̤͈̠͓͉̺̖̤͈̩̲̮͎̼̖͕̙͔̬̻͙͓̝̜̗͖̹͔̭̭̳̖̙̬̩͉̤͔̻̣̬̭̦͖̘̖̭͔͓̦̖̙͇̗̤̳͔̮̳͕̜͎̩͍̜̞̳̫͇̬̜͉̥̮̭̩̪̫͙͎̻̼̬̳̠̪̯̹͍̜͓͖̱̊̇̑̍̇̋͛̽̌͊́̑̓̓̔̾̆̀͊̄̈́̿̐̽͐̈̓̈̃̀̀̌̇̾̿̎̉̊̌̍̌̃͒̈́̑̊̆͆̑̋̽̓̂̈̀̌̄͑̃́̂̓̾̀̀͐̋͊̍̌͑͒͗̓͆̃̅̄̾̾̿͋͗̃͆͒̒͌͛̑̔́͑̑̇́̽͊͗̄̿̒̐̾̅̈́̅̃̓̈̈́͆͑̆͐̿̌͂̓̋͋̀̉̆̓̍͆̓͌͋̏̽̈́̀̒͗̉̍̈́̊̓̅̽͛̇̆̋͊̎̀͒͐̊̔̓̋́̅̊̀̆̏̐̍́̎̊̇́́̏̒͌̊̐̋͊̈́̀̓̀̄̅͆̈́̍̈́̇̏̏͛̈́̃̾̅̏͛͗̈́͋̊̏̉̏̍̅̿͒͌͛̍̽̈̋̎̎͆͆̑͛̾͐͋̎͂̋̍͂̃̉́̔̓̌̇̆́͐̓͌́̚͘̚̚̕̕̚̚̚̚͘̕͘͘̚͘̕͘͘͘̕̕͘̚̚̚͘͜͜͜͝͠͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̵̨̨̡̧̧̧̢̧̛̛̛̛͓͍̞̜̲̮̯͙̤̪͙̖͚̱͇͍̰̹̺̦̙̝͓͖͍̱̬̘̙̭͍̲̳̜͈̭̼͚̺͍̗̪̪̙̬̳̖͙̳̩̭͉̊̎̏̆̀͊̋͐͌̾̍̅̅̔̅̅͂̓́́̐͛́͐́͒͂̎͊̎͐̍́͗̈́̈́̀̂̆̐̌̈́͋̌͋̆̍̽̎́̿̐̒̽̒͊̋͒̈̊̿̃̒͛̇̔̉͑̂̉̂̆̈̂͒̈́̉̽̿̐́̉̈́̈́̈́̑͑͛̓̈́̏̍̀͒́̽̑͂̓̑̀́̈́̀̂̈̄̅̒͐̐̅͑̐̃̈́̿͊̀̈́̋͌̊͆̓́͒̂͘̕̕̚͘͘͘͘̚̚͜͝͠͝͝͝ͅͅA̸̡̨̢̡̨̧̧̨̡̧̨̨̡̨̢̡̢̢̧̢̢̢̧̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̞̻̲̮̹̣̼̤͚̥̗̥̠̹̯͚̯̘͍̫̝̦̗̦̗̩̗̦͈̹̟͇͕͔̠̫̦͖̘͎̣̮̣͍̥͓̙̥̲̖̻͉̗͖̻͕̖͕͉̲̙̣̜̙̝͓̗͙͇̥̤̦̫͔̝̲͖͈͙̪̠̖̦̖̗̠̭̲̗̱̱̥̖͖̹̜̰̗̝̝̬̜̥͎͍̖̬̫̟͎̱̞̻̹͓͓͚͕̗͈̹̣̟̲̞̖͔̦͈͎̤͖̰̯̫̙͔̼̞̩̲̝̦͓͍̦͚̙͓̲̱̜̼̘͓̼͓͓̺̯͉̥̮̣͖̞͍͇̼̫̺̯͎͔͈̪͇̬͙͈̰̙͋̍́̅̓̏̑̓̇̍̿͛͒̃̀̓̎̿͑̀̋̎͋̋̀̉̓̽̀͒̅̈́̓̀͛̊̑́͋̄͗̇͑͛̏͛̂͛̄̀͒͐̽͆͗̈́̔̀͗̽͐̈͊̔̔̾̑̿̂͑̃̓̿͒̀̾͋̈̓͊̏͗͊͋̂̅́̒͊̅̃̋̓͒̍̔̅͒͗̑͐́̄͋̔̊̍̊͂̓͌͗̔̑̇̊̏̄̂̓͋̒͆̉̿̔̉̄̂̍͒͛̓͋̈́̎̐̓̔̚̚̚̕͘͘̚͘͜͜͜͜͝͠͝͠͠͠͝͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅA̷̡̨̨̨̧̡̢̡̡̧̢̛̛̛̦̮̩̜̹̟̹̳͕̼̻̹͓̜̙̟͎͚̖̝͇̫̱̻̯͈̝̞̗͓̩̩͇̹̖͉̣͔͖͈̖͓̮͙͕͍̞̭̖͕͔̠͓͈̟͖͉͕̖͚̪̲̦̺͚̭̤̪̺͉̖̝͔̖̤͌͗̆̐͒̀̈́͊̓̈̈́͛́̑̅̌̊̐̀͌̽̄̄́̀̇̐̈́̊̽͛̉̾̓̈́͗̏̓͂́̀̑̎̇̐̐͑͆͒͆̅͛͑̆̾̀̓́̎̇̑͋́̓̎̏̀̇̏͐̀̌̍͊̒̽̒́̄͑͗̏̿̔̿͂̇́̇̎̊͑̽͑̍̈͂͐̽̄́̎̈̈́͛̑̎̋̾̐̌̉͒͐́̾̓̈́̃̈͋̾̂̀͆̐̏̈́͂͋́͛̀̓̇́̌͆̈́͑̊̍͌̈́̽̂̈́̄̓̈́̄̓̈́̈́͑̏̈̈͊̊̐̊̿̉͐͒̒̌̚̚͘͘̕̕̚̕͘͘̚͘͘͘͜͠͝͠͠͝͝͠͠͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅĄ̸̡̧̡̡̨̨̡̨̧̨̨̡̡̡̨̢̢̢̨̢̧̨̧̢̢̧̡̨̬̞͙̪͍̩͍̮͈̩̞̰̟̩̤̬̺͓̯̪͓͖̪͚̪̞̹̟̯̬̣͍̞̬̹͈͙̠̗̯̰̼̞̮̖̲͔̼̘̖̲̮͈̲̩͚̗̗̣̙͉̮͕͍͈͖̦̮͔͉̺͉̰͎̹̟͓̘̤͖͖̻͔̗̲̹̝͚̲͉̪̤̻͚͈͍̪̱̻͖͇͖͉͓̹̤̼̻̗͖͇̰̼̜̹̪̳͍̻͓̳̗̘͔͖̠͇̘̜̬͇̝̘̻̤̥͚̣̙̯̰͕̫̻̹̬̗̰͎̝̘̬̟͙̠̦̱̘̪͇̗̮͇̼̟̬̘̼̦̫͉̙͈̖͓̰̜͚͍͙̠͔͓̜̠̱̭̤̫͚̙̠̪̣̲̘̺̺̗̬͙͇̟̠̱̺̬̱̺̙̤̩͕̦̳̲̯̻͙̤̰̮̺͉͖̮̪̖̬̭͉̱͍͈̙̦̄͜͜͜͜͜ͅͅͅͅÀ̶̡̧̡̨̢̢̡̢̛̛̛̛͙̘͓͍͈̮̗͔̲͓̣̞̜͎̟͓̝̱̩̜̩̘̤̪͍̬̯̥̲͈͚̠͓̞͙̣̱͍͍̮̠̺̮̰̦̘͔̪͕̻̣̣̦̃͑̆̃̿̎̅͋̃̿̀̌̒̀̓̄͌̐̂̽́̿̌͂̑͐̄̐̈́̂̽͗͂̈́́̽̑̉͌̀̾̿̎̊̑͂́͌̄̑̂̑̂̃͗̔͒̃̃̌̆͆́͑̎̆͑̌̃̊̿͗̾̽̇̍̾͊̿̾͒̆̋͐̅̂̾̆̉̌̾̈́̔̔̐̾̌̈́̓͘͘̚̚͘͜͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝ͅA̴̡̨̨̧̧̢̧̢̧̢̡̧̡̨̢̨̡̧̛̛̛̻̱̝̜̫̯̬̺̫̪̲̩͔̫̣̯̣͈̺̝͔͇̼͎̣͉̤͔̩̠̝̬̪͈̝̥̹̫̳͈͉͎̝̱̻͔̬̜̤̦̤̤̪̰̺̣̱̗͈͉̬̜͖͓̠̲͖̜̪̗̜̤̗͇̝͇̬̫̫̲̱̼̹̻̮̬̩̳̝͍̝̝͕͓̺̬̫̪̺̞̝̰̺͚̳͚̩̠͈̝̮̻̖̦͈͈̬̯̠̟̹̝̼̙̠̝̤̤͙̻̦̟͓͈̰̙̣̤̼͍̪̗̻̞̺̱͈̳͍͍̹͖͚̰̹͙̩̤̬̭̬̫̟̻͔̻͔̮̩̦͉̳͍̯̱̭̗̲͔̰̗͍͚̰̘̰̫̬̘̜̟̲͕̙͉̼̲̠͉͉̼̪̥̩̳͍̱̱̭̬̲̭̗̤͚̫̼̥̲͎̜̤̼̭̥̖͍͎̤̦̫̾̀̽̾̾̃͌̽͌̈̋͛͒̓̔̈́́̂̔͐̉̔̌̌̃̓̄̂͂́͊̏̑̒̈́̿́̆̑͊͒̑̈́̿̍̈́͐̈́̀͐͂́͗̏̏͛͗̍͊̍͂͆̂̽́̓̀͐͐̒͑̉͗́̑̂̋͌̓̽̍͐̅̒͂̏͋̀͐̑̎̊̽̓͑̇̆͗̈́̽̎̀̂͋͐̀̓̓̓̎̏̏͌̃́̄̓͑̂̈́̔̐̾̾̐̽̓̅̈́̄́͆̑͐͆̈́̈́̈́͆̄́̋͗̃̒̊̈́̋͆̀͑̍̍̈̄̈͘̕̕͘̚̕̚̚̚͘͘͜͜͜͜͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͝͠͠͠͝͝͠͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̶̨̡̧̛̛̛̻̥̻̞̼̫̠̦̦̙͈̭͔̺͈̝̣̝̣͔̘̮̪͎̺͕̻̾̆̆͋̎͊̔̈́̓̃̓̾̀́̓̿̊̍̓̓͆̍͒̓̐̐́̇͐͐̇̃̌́͑̑̄͐͋̐̊͛̿̐̽̑͒̈́̓̏̓͌͐̏̉͆̿̂̊̏̄̿̒̉͗̋̈́͌͛̇̈́͂̽͒̅̊̀́̐͘̕̕͘̕͘͘̚͘͜͜͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͠ͅA̴̢̧̢̡̡̨̨̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̫̼̤͚̟̯͇̫̲͈̤̖̯̹͉̬͈̗͚̟̙̺͎̯͖̖̲̺̦̻̣͕̣͕̥̺̰͇̺̰̮͙̪̻̫̾́̈́̇́̑͆̃͌͑̅̍̃̌̔̾̐͒͐̓́͊̐̽̑̽͆͂̓̇̆̈̾̆̏̉̂̃̉̄͆̿͑͋̆̀͑͒͗͊̀̾̎͌̂̂̿̔̍̇̀͗́̂̓̎̓̀̀̍̐̎̑͑̄̈̉̂̽͆̿̄͊͗̈́̌̍̔̐̈́̄̐̃̅͂͂͂̅̔͐̃̍͋͊̅͛̐̍͋͌̽͋͐͋́̔̋̈́͌̀͋͆̂̿͊͋̀̔͂̋̓̈́̉̑̾́͑͛͋̑̌̋̌̃̽̒̏͛̀͐̽̓̌̌̊̓̃͗̍̅̾͒̽̿̍͐͗͒̅͑̈́͊̚̚̕̚̚̕͘̕͘̚̕͘̕͘̚͘͝͠͝͝͠͠͝͠͠͠͝͝ͅĄ̵̢̨̡̨̡̡̨̧̡̧̨̡̢̡̢̧̡̨̢̡̡̡̛̛͖̜͖̹̖͈͖̥͕̰̮̗̥̙͉̖̤̬̦̞̖͎̺͔̜̳̭̝̰̦͓̗̫̺͖̥̻̫̦̻͈̜͎̱͚͍̩͖̜̱͖͕̥̻̪̦̭͚͍̮͙̘͓͕̦̘̼̱̯͔͇̼̫̺̰̻͍̤͎̲̠̺͚̝̝̜̠̬̙̭̦̘̬̜̟̲̲͇͔͔̳̗̗͇͓̳̝͕̼̩̞͉̖̲̪̖̙̫̘̲͈͇͍̫̩̮̞͕̪̟͉͉̼̤͖̞̣̦͇̻̞͕̩̪̫̳̘͙͎̟̠̩͉͎͕̩̳̫̯̜͇͈͍͉̦̖̩̪̥̲̲̻̲̞̺͍̻͕͖͕̫̳̼̲̠̬̠̖̹̠͍͉̺̞̱̖̩͚͔̪̦͖̳̲̪̬̗̱͔͈̩̲͚̳̲̞̩̞̩͇̻͚̖͉̺̤̥̲͍͓̥̮̯̂͑̈́̊̆̆̂̌̓̐͑̈͐̌͐̌̈̈́͆̇́̋̀̈̏̐̆̀̂͊͐͛̈́̍͂̄͒̌͌̍̎͌̈́̑̏̎̍͒̂͛̓̆͌̓́͛̌͗͌̈̈́͗̓̐̂͗̃̓̿̍́́̑͘̚͘͘̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͠͝͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅA̸̧̡̧̧̡̨̨̧̨̧̨̨̨̧̡̧̢̧̧̢̧̨̡̧̡̨̛̛̛̛̛̛̻̝̪̼͇͍̭̭͖̹̝̱̭̫̟͇͇̖̯̗̙̗̮͙̰̹̼͚̹̩̼̜̙̹͈̺̲͙̥̠̝̙͇̼̮̱͎̖̫̹̭̬̺̖̼͔͇̘̝̹̙̼̥̮̰̯͔̰̼͎̗̩̝̲̝̙̖̱̦̻̱̻͍̭͉̣̲̟̙͈̟͕̭̫̲̫̜̜̼̙̖̖̗͈̟͍̬̻̻̠̖͙̙͖̙̺͕̖̖̪̺͖̼̜͚͇͙͈͈̱̣̻̙͈̬̤̟̰̜͓̞̠̩͕̞̬̜͇͓̼̹̤̺̠͙̣͖̞̺͖̫̞̞͍̹̪̞̙͓̭̯̲̲̣͕͇̱̣̦̪̻̣͓̲͉̪̹͓̫͚̩̩̝͓̘͗͊̐̅͋͛͐̆̇̂̊̋̂͊̐̌̓̈́̌́̉̈́̾̽̏̍̈́͒̿́͛̉͌͛̉͗̇͂̉̓̉̐̑́̈̂̾̽͌̃̉͆̀̑͊͆̾̀̄̏̏̀̃̆̌͋̀̀̃͗̿͒͒̀̊̌̀͆͌̏̿̎̋͋̿͗̆͑̓͐̈̋́̿̎̎̓͒̄̇́̌̈́͛̈̈́̌͊̽̄̏̔̏̊͛́̽͐̌͊͆̅̀̏̑̀̌̊̓͑̃͒̌̈́͊̓̆̂̈̓͆̏́̑͗̊͐͘̚͘̚̚̚͘̕̕͜͜͠͝͝͠͠͝͠͠͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅÃ̸̧̢̢̢̨̨̧̨̢̧̢̨̢̨̧̧̢̧̡̢̛̛̛̟͈͓͖̞͉̜͍͎̻̰̯̦͉͎̮̻̭̩̦̱̭̝̙̹̭̤̯̼̰͎̺̲̞͍̝̲̲̥͈̺̩̺̭͈̣͎̯̱̖̝̼͇̫̰̫̝͕̯̳̠͖̥͎͎̤̥̭̫̦͇̘̺̫̖͚͈̞̺̟͖̘͇̯̩͚͖̞͉̯͙̥̬͉̦͙͖̥̤͔͚̥̗̣̝͈̹̮̼͖̺̥͈̙͉̩̼͔͖̘͍̠̗͖̺̬̱̣̫͍̳͖̤̩͔̦̼̰̪͉̲̺͉̤̥̹͉̩̩̥̼̬̟̟̹̪͒̒̅́̏͂̄̅̂̋̓̌̆͋͑͗̌̄̐̓̓͌̏̆̉́͂̂̊͂͋́̓̀̊̿̾͌̅̅͊͊̍̑̈̂̐̉̾̀̏̓̾̑͋͗̆̈́́̓̍͗̏́̏̀̈́̈́̈́́̐̐̀̑͋̎̒͂̉́́̄͐̂̊̔̓͂͋͂̎̉͆̎́̉̾͆͑̍̂͑͒́̈́̄̽̑̉͛̋͂͂͐̀̒̈̕̚̚͘̕̚̕͘͘̕̕̕͘͘̚͘͘͜͠͠͝͝͠͠ͅͅͅͅĄ̸̨̢̧̡̡̡̡̧̧̨̧̡̧̢̛̤̼͚̟̟̺̰̺̞̜̳̩͖̭̙̜̣̹̯̳͉̳̳̘̯̦̲͖̭̩̰̘͇̖̱̙̤̱̘̝͎̮̟͉̮̹͇͇̦̤̟̞̺̯̟̟͍̦͖̖̯̬͍̤̠̭̘͚̥͓͕̥̱̟̲̥̮̹̤̞̲̪̼̤̯͍̤͚̪̰͇̳͔̝̹̹͈̮͍̼̹̯̣͇̦̯͙̳̰̻̘̻͕̦͙̩͇͉͎̘̝̲͙̯͈͍͈̱̤͓̻̱̱͖̱̘̬̊́̊̓̽̑͋̋́̇̋͆̀̐̅̽͌̉͂̓̓̐̍̿̊̆̉̌̀̈́̉͋͋̽̓̇́̎̈͘̚̕͘͘͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͝͝ͅͅͅÁ̸̡̢̡̨̢̡̧̨̨̨̧̢̢̨̧̧̢̨̡̨̨̢̡̢̡̛̛̛̻̯͖͇̬̤̪̞͕͓̬̫͍̟̠̪̯͖̞͕̤͍̝̘̻͍͈͓̟̯͚̖̫̜̥͓̩͉̬̲̘͖̺͓̼͚̭̥͖̘̞͇̣̼̣̙͕̱̯͔̹̮̥̝̼̩̫͉͎̩̠̙̭̯̖͙͎͖̦̗͎͇͍̫̰̲̥̭̥̜̘̗̘͓͙͇͓͇̯͇̺̠̭̤̥͉̻͍̞̯͈̳͔̖̙͙̼̯̜͍̟̳̥͓̜̗̱̞̰̲͉̤̜̝̭̖͖͈̹̞̝̮̖̭̝̗̩̥̭̠̳͖̫͍̺̜̞̯͕̱̰̯̟͚̘̰̼̩̞̫̫̮̳̟͎̘͎͔̝̱̙̳̖͔͎̹͕͓̤̞̩̗̘͕̣̞̬̥̯̱̘̩̳͙͖̼̙͔̻͕͙̞̯̣͇̯̦͖̠̻̰̜̘̹̻̩̽͆͑̾̑̋̅̋̍̉̓͆̇̂̓̈̂͋̒̆́͌̊̑̆̏̈̈́̆͗̌͛̎̒̑̎͒͂͊̑̌͐̒̍̿̿̃̐̓̈́̊͗̐̀̐͐̽̐̔̈́́̄̄̇͑̓͗͒͗͌͐͑̑̌̇̇̄̇́͒͗̍̓̎̒͑̂̂̃̀͆̒̀̊͐̋̂̓̔̈́͑̌̏̀̽̈́͗͘͘̕͘̕̕̚̕͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̶̨̡̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̲̱̩̗̪͇̜̫͇͓̼̖̯̩̲͕͙̦̤͙̙̝̺͈̩̳̗̼͙̻̭̭̗͚͍̀̈̽͑͛͋̉̎͊̈́͗̍̈́̆͌̃͆̿̾͌̾̉͐́̊͒̒̀̋͒͑̋̈̊̎̓̓́̎͊̔̓̅̃̏̆̄͗͋̆̉̓͗͊̆̆̊̍̌̐̊͛͐̉̈́̃̀̄̆̀̄̿̂͐͌̉̅̂͆̋̃͂̑̊̓̈́͒̀̊̂̽́͛̍̑͂͊̽͂̑͊͗̄͊͆̀̈́̐̍̀̽̆̍̈́͐̾͊̏́̋͗̆̈́͑͛̔̐͆̔̓̿͆̂̈̄̽́͌͌̇̍͗̀̌͌̈̉͆̇̋͑̎̓̋̈́̀̒̍̾́̀̃̈̍͌̈́͆̽͊́́̈͒͆̆̎͂͌̌̀̌̀̚̕͘̚̕̕̕͘̚̕̕͘̚̚͘̕̕͠͠͝͠͝͠͝͠͝͝͠͠͠͝͝A̶̡̢̨̨̧̡̧̡̢̨̡̛̛̛̛̛̛͚̭͔̲̘̪̥̮̝̦̼̰̜̠̩̻͓̼̼͎̘̱͎͖̺̦̼̹͕̩̜̰̮̻̠̙̙̞̰͈̩̺̠͓̯̩̤̺̭̝̝͓̞͙̗̝͍͕̺͇̰͖͉̲̦̹̳̤͍̩͉̹͎͇͙̰̬̗͚̜̫̝͚͉͚̳̖̲̥̰̰͚̳̙̰͎̼̲̭̥̮̲͔͓̘̭̱͖̝͉̱͈̮͈̳̤͍̭͎̝̼̙̺̪̗̰̠̬̜̖͕̠̤̗͍̘̝̣̥̹̠̙̦̼̞͙͇̦̥͚̯̣̞͔̣̲̗̙͍̖̺̖̪͂̎̈́̈́̋̿͊́͆̌̇̇͋̾͂͊̅̋̋̃̇͗̀͒̈͗̍̊̾̈́̓̃͊̋̋́̄̋͋͗͂̊͛̋͋͋̈́̃̐͌́̀́̊͋̌̓͑̈́̋͋̏̆̍͛̓̎̂̽͑̂́̊̄̑̈́̌́̓̾̈́̃̔̆̓͗̇̎͛͑̓̐̉͗͌͑̿̉̉̀̐͐͐͂͊̅̉̊͗͒͘̕̚̚͘̕̚̚̕̚̚͜͜͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͝͝ͅĄ̵̧̧̨̢̧̧̡̨̨̨̢̨̧̡̡̨̢̧̡̧̡̢̡̨̛̲̼͔͈̗̹̫̹̥̟͍̗͎̠̘͍͉͕̮̫̩̘̻̗͙̺̫̣̲̟̹̗̺͖̠͈̦̥̜̼̥̥̬̮̫̤͈̭͓̹̲̭̬̼̞̖͍̻̟̭̝̩̗̠̟̤͇̫̦̹̻͈̦̝̝͈͉̞͉̳̺̺̩̞̰̣͚͔̹͚̘͓͕̮̪̜̩͔͍͙̠̞͚̯͕̤̺͎͔͓̹͇͉̟͚̞̣͕̙̺̻̙͔͉͔̼̜̬̝͚͚͖̖̭͖̫̘̰͕̹̜̺͍̺̰̠͖̥̭̮̱̘̖̞͚̣̣̳̮͍̣̳̟̦̹̟̭͎̜̤͙̞̠̟̟̯̘̤̤̩̟͚̹͉̞̝̝̰̦̺̘͎̗̱͈̮̹̤̬̲͎̮̰̤̯̗͉̮͕̝̭͙̖͕̘̘̗͔̬̺̝̺̙̱̟̥̞͍͍͔͎̝̹͔̺̜͓̥͛̽̔͆̒͌̓́͑͐̔̀͌̒̃̒̈̍̐̽͐͋̆̓͑̊̔̌͒͐̽͂̈̽͆̉̾̅̈́̏̐̉͆̈͐̽̆̔͊̑́͒͆̑́͆͌̉͆̒͑̉͌̀̿́͌́̐͛̀͐̒͐̾̆̅͂̏̀̂͐̎͂͒͗̆̑͛̌̄̌͑̃̐̚͘̚̚͘͜͜͜͜͜͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅA̸̧̡̡̧̡̢̢̧̢̨̡̢̡̡̧̨̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̺̥̤̻͙̝̯͓̭̮̖̩̘̘̣̗̣̮̦̩̠̪̫̤͎̺͚͔͔̖̰̞͎͉̲̲̖͈̱̩̺̭͎̞͙͚̗͍̲͕͍͚̱̝̫͚̙͓̝̝͖͓͚̙̞͈̬͔͍̦̝̤͓̲̭̗͚͈̬͇̞̹͙̯͔̲̪͚͍͚̗͚̟̙̥̥̱̠̖̙̣͈̤͉̜̘̝̼̻̳͚͕̝̗̭̬̥̳̼͕̦̳͎͚̲̻͖̬̫̠̞̫̺̦̱̱͇͕̖̗̹͇͎̖̖̞̯̤̬͕̦̖͈̞̋͐̓̉̈́̌̊̿́̀̇̀̔̑͆̈́̆̎̏̇̅̓͋̽́͐͒̍̈̓͒͋̎̽̈̄̓̿͋̉̿͊̋̅̔͛̏͛͂̇̒̃͂̌̊͆̿̂̔̒̌̿̓̊́͑͐̈̓̾͗̔͐̃̋̃͑̇̍̊̈́̿̂̀̀̑̂̈́́̃̒̌̇̿́̊̔̊̔̽̄͛͒̐̈́͒̉͆͋̅̀͐̄́̉̆͌̃̎̔̊̋̍͑̉́͑͊̀͋̓̾͛͂̿̒̆̋̌̊̈́͒͂͗̐͊̂̇̉͌͆̃̾͗̍̈́̆̏̇͊͐̍̃͌̉́͌͂̆̍̾̄̽̀͛̊͌̎̔̓̆̾̀̒̓̓̔͂͆̈̾̾͑̋͛̈͌̀͋̋̽̊̋̅̚̚̕͘̚̚̕͘͘̕͘̕̚͘͘͘̚̕̚̚̚͘͘͘̚̕͘̚̕̚̕͘͘̕̕̚͜͜͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅA̵̢̨̧̢̢̨̧̧̛̛͎̘͕͎̬̺̱̦̻͓̪̩̹̪̣̜̪̼̰̬̮̖̗͙͈͎͔̤͓͎͎̖̘̬̞̬̠̠̥̙̰̬̳̲̤̩̰͍̯̲̥͔̦̙͚̭̱̟͔̩̝͓͍̟̲̱͈̬͓̯͚̥̭̜̪͚̼̠̣̖̥̦̲̻̹͕͖̞̜͍̺̲̩̬̤̤̻̦̱̼̪̱͓͖̘͙̪̻͔͑͆͌͆̀̾̄̾̎͑̇̌̀̀̏̽͊̂͐͌̏̑͊͊̅̈́̋̔̄̓͗̄̿͋͊͑̽̊̊̒̅̀́̿̔̉́̓̑͛͂͊̍̔̿̇̈́̆̈͐͑̋̀̀̊̈́͂͑̽̑̑̓́̇̆͊̅̐̑͐̈̂̀̀̎̌͒̈́̍̏͒̀̊̑̐̋̿͛̇̈́̉͋͗̌̋̑́͆̈̀́̊͂̽̈͒͆͋̒̍̑̀͑́̐̒̔̉̔̄̓̇́͘̕̚̚̕̕͘͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅA̷̛̖͉̭͎̜̳̝͉͖͇͕̟̗̫̝͗̽̾̈́̌͒̆̓͛̑͒̋̂͒̔̽̓̽̉̅̏̇͌͛̿̈́̄̍͋͒́̀͊͐́̀̌̏̒̌̇̑̐̿̔͠͝͝͝͝͠A̶̢̨̡̡̡̧̢̧̧̨̡̢̢̨̧̢̢̨̧̢̧̧̛͍̹̣̭̝̰̹̟̤̝̹̤̩̘̪̪̣̞̩̺̱̫͖̝̥͖͎̫̲̮͇͖̞̻̮̫͇͎̘͎͚̻̼͇̭̻̥̟̰̬͈̼̦̗̗͎̝̲̠͖̲̰̪͔͙͇̖̪̲̹̙̼̫̠̺̬͍̞͚̯͙̺̟͉̳͖͎̝̪̹̫̞̭̤͉̪͕͚͎͉͖͉̬͚̤̘̞̫͔̫͖̫͔̯̞̣̼̝̺̳͉̩͙̻̣̖͉̟̮̦͕̲̙̳̤̱͔͎͕̩͍̬̬̥̬̺̣͍̪̼̖̖̦͖͕͎͎̮̱̤̲̩͈̫͔̞̬͙̱͇͓͔͕͔̩͋͆͗͛̃̀̍̒̉͐̊͜͜͜͜͜͜ͅͅĄ̵̧̢̛̛̛̛̙̣͎̹͈̥͓̳̝̭͉̘͔̻̩̼̭͈̳͎̲̤̪̬̃̋̿͐͐̔͌̍̌̽̈́̇̐̅͛͊̒̀̈̇̅͐̃́̄̑̉͐́͆͑̈́̆̀͋͑͂̌̎̄̐̌̽̉̔͂͗̎́͗̉͆͛̂̓̇͂͒̏͛͆͌̊̑́͒̾̾͐̂͗̃̇̎͊́̔̑͆̈́̀͆̈́̂̿̊̆̈́̆͊͐̈́̃̓̂̈̎̏͊̅̀͗̇͐́̕͘͘͘͘͘͘̚͜͝͝͠͝͝͠͠͝͠ͅA̷̢̨̢̢̢̡̡̡̢̡̨̨̨̨̡̡̧̧̢̢̧̢̛̛̛̛͕̟̜̬̱̟̣͇̲̭̰̥͈͇̬̼̣̙̯̫͇̘͚̼̝͓͉͍͖͎͚͎̬̝̘͉̦͉̤͍̺̳͔̺̗̫̗̥͔̦̰̙̰̠̣͎̪̭̤̖̟̜̥͓̺͎̦̙̯̝͚͍̞̭͖̤̤͕̟̫̮͇̺͎̝̳͕̥̻̦̫͉̰͕̰͈̗̺̺̭̲̦̼͙̩̻̰̲̦͚̦̰̼͉͕̫̗͉͖̪̖̺̤͕̦͎̦̗̮͈̮̫̞̠̼̼̙͔̠̱̳͇̖̫͎͕͍͔̰̩̟̗͎͇̻̞͙̱̥̬͇̠͔̰̯̗͔̜̠͇͚̜̖̜̩͉̗̮̱͍͍̝̰̞̟̤̦͙͖̝̭̝͚̤̻̮̼̟̱̯̰̜̜̥̜̠̘̥͉̘̫͇̝̖̤̖͙̲̟̰͓͉͖͈͓̰̲̥͈͚͚͇͈͖̱̦͎͉̫̺̹̼̗͖̳̳͚͉̣͕̼̗̳̭̼͔̮̘͓̅́̓̀̀̊́̄̔̾̓͂̽̎͋̀͆̾̍̿̂̏̈́̀͑̄́̓̆̓͆̈́̅͐̀̈́̒̊̐͆̂̽̊̆̾̂̈́́͂́̊̎͑́̎̈́̿̾̀̉̅̽̆̆͐̈́̿̂͗͐͑͗̏̔͆̃͒̏͗̔͋̔͌͋͊̓̓̓̃̃̓̍̀̀̿̈́͂̿̒͌̍͛́̏́̔̈́̎͒́̔̊̃̽̈́̄̃͆̋͆̇̊̃̌̒̓͋͐͊̍͐̈̔́̾͛̓͘̕̕̚̕͘͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͝͝͠͠͠͝͠͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅA̴̢̡̨̨̧̧̢̨̨̢̡̨̢̧̢̧̛̳̹̜̝̤͖̙̩͉͉̭͚̟̱̮̦͔̺̟̰̖̭̘̖̬̠͎̜͔̰̯͎̫̜̥̮̰̻̺̥̫͍̰̘̰̦̫̠̙̩̰̦̜̲̤͉̩̝̮͔̺̩̼͈̺̺͈̫̲͕͉̻̜̦̩̱̱͔͍̟̞̭̯̭̖̠̹̻͇̻̦̞̯͚͇͈̥̻̹͈̥̬͉̺̩̥̰̲̭̞̬̹͙͕̼̗̭̘̯͈̙̭͉̻̮̯͎͎͚̹̳̳͎̤̜͉̠͑̅̎̓̈͑͒́͆̏̿͐̇̍̏̑́̿̅̊̂̌̏͗̃̊̈̇̿̏͋͊̕͘̕̕͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅA̷̡̡̢̨̨̧̢̡̢̢̡̡̧̧̧̧̛̛̼̯̹̟̪̻̻̯̱̠̺̯̳̰̤̤̝͖̯͕͓͕͚̘̠̙͕̲̜̗͚̦͚͙̻̬͍͖̘̯͙̞̭͖̭̖͖̝̦͖̖̪͕̯̣̻̝̫̱͈͕̳͚̰͖͇͈̙̘͇̮̠̳̗͙̣̣͎̠̹̼̝̹͙̗͚͉͍̲̣̩̱̖̰̩̭̥̞̜̹̣̫̝̲̻͇̰̥̰̤̳̩͖̗̖̝̻̖̣̯͚̘̲̘̹̖̥͓̳̯̼̘̩̩͚̗̣̘̳̹͓͉̰̱̱̹͔͕̘͇͈͍̤̣͈̥̳̪̣̦̮̭͚̥̬̞͉̗͔͖̱̜̣̦̻̫̣̬̦͙͚̫̩̳̰̠̻̦͇̗̝͍̖͇̮̲͍̜̱̤͓̳̩̝͚̞̟̭̻̣̰̺͙͓͇̯͎͉̼̪̠̞̍̂̾̀̏͌̔̌͒͒̃͒̑͐̑̑̒̆̾͒́̾̎̐̍̍̓̈́̏͑̈́̾̐͒̀́̊̄̀̈́̿͐͘̕͘̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅẠ̵̢̨̨̨̧̡̧̧̧̢̧̡̡̢̨̡̡̡̢̧̢̧̛̘̳̫̳̼̻͓͇̙͍̤̫͚̳̤̠̰͍͓͖̲̖̯̫̗͉̼̺̥͙̦͉͓͈͇͓͈͕̻̳̣̦̤̗̖̬̰̪͈͕̦̜͈͔̹̫̰͇̣̳̱̖̠̳͓̠͍̰̣̪͇̝̝̮̺͇̮͔̳̻̳̯̲͈̲̯͙̞͉̼̰̬̭͓̳̼̪̖͍̤̤̣̦͓̭̥̜͖̩̳͎̖̳͉̗̗̹̜̮͚̳̠̪̜̮͎̳̞̻̦̱͎͉̗̹̩̪̺̱̮̪̮̠̲̤̣̝̣͇̜̤̲̦͚͇̝̩͓̫͓͎̬͇̭̦̲͎̭̹̹͔̺̦̹͇͚͇̰̱̼̲̫̳̺̼̭͚̝͕̜̹̳̲̥͉͉͓̝̙̯̮̠̘̪̼̪̠͎̺̣̬͖͍͈̠̲̭̭̭̣͈͔͎̪̩͔̯̘͑̔̎͑͆́̓͗̀̀̍̃̎̐̐͑̽̓͑̑́͒̉̋̒̒̆̾͗͌͋́͊̔͛͋́̂͐͑̊͂̐̋̀͂̈͘͘͘̚̚͘̚̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͠͠͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̶̧̡̢̡̧̨̢̡̨̡̧̧̨̡̧̨̢̡̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̞͕̭̳̬͙͖͚̜̦̼̗̝̼̦̗̼͙͔̖͈̼̟̻̺͍͍̺̫̫̘̯̯̘̣͚͇̣̼̟͎̗͕͕̻̥͓̮̫̲̭͇͔̞͔͖̰̱̩̼̗̳̟͓͚̰̠̝͉͔̤͓͎̦͍̺͖̜̥̳̥͔̩͎̩͕̼̖͚͙̭̻̩̹̻͕̮̥̫̪̭͚̩̥͖̣̮̗̱̪̖͉̻̤͎̲̬̪̳̟̖̳͍̜͖̖̙͕̣̲͇̦͓͉̪͓͍̺͙̹̰̗̗͕̻̼̲̙̗̤̜̤̰̦̘̌̄̅̃̐̐̋̍̄̋͗̑͆̓̏͌̈̏̏̉̀̆̄͐̈̔̎͑̆̽̂̃̃̈́̈́̂̌̆̊̈́̈́̅̌̀̔͂̒̽̇̒͐́͛̿̈́̏̊̍͊͆̒̃̓́̿͗͋̓̐͂̑̔̌̅̓͋̈́͊͊̇̉͂͒̐͗͗̓̓́̒́͒̇̾̂̂̔́̑̈́̇̃̔͋̓̉̌͌́̄̑̀̊̋̇̓͑̀͒̈́͒͂̓̓̒̅͂͐̔̇̉̓̆͋̓͆̔͑̑͒̆̂͘̚̕̚̚̚̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͠͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̴̧̢̨̨̡̨̢̧̧̢̨̡̨̢̛̠̰̝̳͕͇̻̙̩̯͓̠̳͓͚͕̩̖̪̬̝̮̞̱̟̲̲̻̦͈͔̲̘͔̗̩̹̻͖̲̜̮̞̳͔̞͖̭͈͕̦̱̭̖̙̖͓͎͙͇̖̰͓̩͔̼͎͔̞̣̗͍͓̤̜͕̰͇͖̞̳̫̮̭̘͙̲͙͇̰̟̖̻̞̥͕̙̤̰͚̤̻̹͚̬̘̟̞̪͈̱͕̪̗̤̭̮̝̪̻̪͖͔͚͓̱͔̳́̓̉͒͑̓̑͑͐̓͛́̇͛̾̿͌͒̐̏̉͌̊͛͛̆̿̽͂͌̈́̇̇̈̋́̀̄̍̌̋̋̇͋̎͗̇̎̓̏̅̈̈́̀̐͒̇́̆̇͒̓̉̈̉͂̀́̔͛̅̀͑̆̌͐̔́̓̄̋̾̽̎̋̈́͛́̏̄̏̇͋͑̄́̌́̋́͐̋̓͂̑͛͑̑͒̿͒̋͗̎̌͊̐̎͋̔͌̈́̽̽͑̀͛̽̑̅̀̅͋̈́̀͂̿͌̑̄͒͐̎͆̓͑̋̓͑̒̒̽̑͐͂͊͐̋̑̕̕͘͘̕͘̚͜͜͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͝ͅA̶̡̡̨̡̧̧̨̡̧̧̮̱̠̹͎̹̺̱̼̭̣͖͎̖͙̙͎͔̯̗̞̱̪̙̣̗̭͙̯̬̩̙̗̟̤͓͚̹̗̳̤̖̹̥͙̺̖͖̫͕̙̮̘̱̞̭̮̥̞̝͖͙̟̺̝̭̭͓̲͚̠͎̙̥͈͈̣̫̹̹̮̫̣͕͉͉̮̝͇̝͖̠̘̻̫̲̺̭͚̝̲͔̬͈̳̳̩͉̞̩̣͙̱̮̩̤̺̲̜͈̥̯͉͕̭̫̪̹̯͍̜͔̪̭̻̝̞̤̳̜͈͇͇͚͇̣̟̘̝͇̜͙͎̤͔͓͑̉̀͆̇̽̐͐͗͋̈́́͆̉̑͐̚̕͜͜͜͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̵̨̧̢̨̨̧̧̢̢̨̧̨̢̡̢̨̢̢̛̛̛͇̼̦͉͕͇̪̻̪̯͚̣͎̖̠̫̯͎͕̼͔̰̬̦̥̝͙̩̠̜̭̣̬͇̭͔̠͙̭̤͎̹̫̫̬̗̣͈̫̖̳͚̭̺͕̜̘̦̬͚͉̖͈̥͙͉͍͚͈̝̤̪̱̤̪͔̪̖͈̹̣̱̫̹̩͙̪̻̹̩̞̼̖̩̹͎͉̻̗̭̤̳͔̖̠͖̫̳̙̖̳͙̦͙͇̫͉̗̝͉͙͖̞̥̮̹͕̞̟̳̻̦̻̲͎̣͓̦͎̯͕͙̮͔̮̹͎̖̙͍̦͍͎̖̪̻̬̠̟̪̺̮͎͉̖͇͉̭̥̳̞̩̲̫̯̻̅̾̔̎͛̀̇̊̿̉̈́̾͑̑̈́̔͆͛̎̏̿̂̀́͛̈̿̏͊͑̅̓̐̍̀̈́̌͗̃͒̑̆͊̀̈͋̓̅͛̏͐͆̿̇̏̓̐́͗̈͑̎̔͌͛̉͛̓͋͑͌̌̓̒͋̌̀͛̍̂̆͗͒͆̀̔͊͒̈́̎̈́̉̒̓̾̌͆̉̇̊̀͆̈́̈́́̽͗͒̓͂̾͂̌̇̈́̓̄̎͌̒̐̄̽̍͂̎̆̆́̍̉͐͊̓̂̎̄͂́̊̅͛̚̕͘̕̕̚̚̚̕̚͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅÄ̸̧̧̢̡̡̧̧̨̧̧̻̯̞̙̠̗̦̲̠͓͉̞̦̯̫̩̺̥̘̜̩̹͇̝͈̬̭͎̞̺͈̜̜͉̟̣͎͕̹̲̺̪̱̙̮̹̣̲͍̯̰͈̟̰̖̝̰̹̮̳̺͙̝̖͉̭̀̐̀̂̎͛̆̋́̀̚͘̚ͅͅͅÄ̸̢̨̧̢̨̡̢̧̧̨̧̢̧̡̢̢̢̡̨̡̢̧̛̛̛̛͖͚͍̗̖̖̼̺̟̰̘̥͎̫͈͇̙̜̰̻̱͚̟͇̠̪̺̹̣̣̪̼͓̙͉̦̗͙̫͚͓̯̻̘̻̘͚̟̦̗̬͖͚̗̪̘̗͚͕͈͔̱̠̘͈̘͉͉̮͇̰͚͎͖̲͖͍͉̮̟͙̤̹̫̼̝̣͖̣̙̤̮̥̖̤̭̰̪͖̘̟̳̙̪̟̲̬͖̙̗̺̰̥̗̜̲̖̥͚̠̥̠̻̞̲̝̮̤̲̪̰͎̟̻̦̞̱̤͇̹̳̻̫̻̘́̏̍͊̋̀͑͐̿̋͆́͒̂̌̈́͆͗̉̀͌̔̂̃́̊̆̓̍͗̐͑̔̋̅̌̾̃́̎̏̾̍̑͑͋̊̑̒͒͆̈̎́̑̒͗͆̓͂̅͑͂͋͛̽͛̓̅̎̔̀̂̓̈́͛̍́̀̂̌̇̄̋̾̃͑̄̈́̿͂̅̐͗̋̂̍̋͂͆̃̿̎͛̆͐̔͗͒̂̿̋̆̿̊̀̃̾̃̈͊̌͒̋̈́̆͂̅́̿̅͑̇̓̓̀̔́́͐̌̊͋̏̉̀̅̕̚̚̚̚̚̚̚͘͘͘̕͘͜͜͜͝͠͝͠͝͠͝͝͠͠͝ͅͅͅẦ̴̧̢̡̧̧̡̢̛̛̛̺͇̭͕̯̟͖̠̫̤͓͚̞̰̘̠̮̪̲̱̠̟̟̰̻̯̬̲̳̜̰͍̰̻̺̜̺̺̺̮̘̞̣͕̲̙̭̻̠͔̹͍̗̍̐̀͌̿͛̎̅̍̎̈́̇̅̐́̀̆̓́̌̽̊̽͑̅̃́̔͆͆̇̊͆̆͛̋͗͐́̎̐͐͋̓̓̀͊̈́̈͌̔͑͆̉̋̎͌̓̆̾̇̐̋̽̅͒̒̾̀͗͆̒̊̊̒̽͐͛̐̆̒̑̃̌̅̔̌̔͂̊̓̆̑̈́̔͗̈̉̍̈͐̀̽͛͛̄̃̃̃̓̔͌́̽̇́͗̔̌́͊̓̏̾̍͛̔̊̃͌̎̆͂̂̌̀̍̓̂́̀̎̈́̄͊̓̾̀́͑͊͗͆̒̀̊̈́̍̈̋̍̍͊͒͒͌̇̓̑͌̀͒͆̒̐̀̆̐̈́̿̎̽̾̾̿̉͊̃̽̃̅̏̈͂͛͒̀̓̔̍̎̐̇̀̈̋̓̄͛̎̒̈̕̕͘̕̚̚̕͘̕̕͜͝͝͝͠͝͠͠͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͝ͅͅͅA̵̡̨̨̢̢̧̢̡̡̢̧̡̡̡̢̢̨̧̧̡̢̧̛̛̛̛̹͈̹̠̪͎̥̤͎̭̺̯̣̻̬̗̪̫̟̙͍͕̘͇͍̞̠͓̠̠̬̙̲̙̼̞͇̪͓͙͚͓͇̻̘̳̟͇̝̘̖̳̼̘̲̤̙̹̺̜̖͓̞͚̙̣̖̻̼̪͉͇̥͍̗͔̻̜͖͇̯̱̦̰̟̜͇̣̬̜̰͉̝̬̺̜̻̩̱͍̠̲̦̘̞̥̲̤̟͎̻̹̮̳̣͎̺̝̥͚͈̜̥̤͙̜̲̙̞̩̝̯̥̠̘͉̥̙̗̦͖̠̼̬͔̯͍̯͓̠̯͇̖̙̗̖͇̖̩͑̆̾̾̌́͋͂̐̓̈̌̇̅̄͌́̈́̅̉̑̎̔́̂̇̓͋͌͊̀̒̄̏̽̿̓̆̓͆͋̐̒̉̐̅̇̅̏̿̊̃͛̋̇̆̎͒̒͌̈́̌̿̉̐̂̓̈́̅͗͒̄̎̈͒̄͌̇̎̄̌͋̈́̀̿̇͂͆͋̀͑̈́̐͆͌̈͂̊̎̂͗̿̃͋͛́̽̄̐́́͛̎͗̀͒͑̾̐̔̏͘͘̚͘̚͘̕̕̚͜͜͜͠͝͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̴̡̨̨̧̨̢̧̧̡̨̡̨̛̛̛̛̗̱̹͕̫̻̖̜̤̜̤̻͈̦̻̙̦̗̻̖͚͈̦̤̖͉̣͎͉̰̮̙̜͙͉͍̺̹͎̺̤̤͇̺̩̹̝͚̳̰̞̹̥͎̫͕̥̘̞̥̹̩̯͇̳̳̻͔͓̩̗͇͕́̾̈́̂̍͋͗͑̍͆͐͂̾̇̉̽̋̔́̓̐̾̎́̈́͒̌̀́̐̃̀͋͂̄̃̈̆͒̋̀́̆̽̆͐́̍̓͐͆͆͊̾̿͐̄̀̈́͒͋̈͂͂͒́͒͌͂̏̈́̍͐̆̓̄̽̿̀̆̏̊̔́̋̏̇̓̀͆͒̊͆͒̃̾̈́̏̆̒̀̐̀̀̊́̃͐̈́̄̐͑͌͑̆̌͆̈̓̿́́̂̓̾̃̊͊̋́̀̒̂̇̾͐̀͑́̆͊͆͂́͛̊̂̑͆̂̓̒̚͘̕͘͘̕̕̚͘̕͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͠͝ͅͅͅͅȦ̸̡̢̧̨̨̧̡̢̧̧̨̢̢̧̡̢̨̧̧̨̡̧̛̛̛̛̮̙̳̻̼͕͕̖͍̪̖̗̱͎͔̘̙̳͇͚̺̤̣̘̥̫͎͉̻̗̼͍̠͔̲̰̻͚̬̻̭͚̹̠̰̬͙̗͎̞̤̱̝̦̭͙̳̠̘͓̘̥̦͇̘̞̘͎̲̻͕̦̬̥̫̤͖̹͉̮̱͕̘̻͈̤̹̺͔̻͉̙̦̤̻͈̱͙̭͙̪̭̦̞̭̥̼̬̪̦̞̝̬̦̞̯̠̩̰̦̭̹͖̺̥͖̙̗̠̖̮̝̙̩̜̦͕̤͈̩̤̰̭̣̼̪̝̖̭̤̙̖͚̦̜̟̝͖͚̙̠͉̣̤̥̫̟̺͎̥̯͔͇̹̺̻̝̳̺̻̼͉̞͍͍͎̺͙̭̲̣̟͉͍͈͍̭͍̖̝̗̝̳̹̘͓̳̤̞̥̪͕̰̬͍͎͙͈̜͍̭̞͖̙̲̗̩̩̙͔̲̙͙̺͙̖̱̠͎͇͈̤͉̱͍͇̗̟͓̫̺̦̭̗̤̙̻̥̲̜̉̋̄̄̒̅̈́̀̏̅̅̈̓̈̀̈̾̆͑̆̅͋̐̎͋̈́̃̍̾͌̆̂͌̽̓̒̏͋̃̂̀̊̏͊̔̑͛̔̊̐̍̈̔̈́́̏̊͛͗̽̅̇̆̃́̓̈́̊̆̽͂͐͌̑̐̈́͐̈̑̈́̎̆͊̏̎́̉͒̊̍̀͑̈́͌̓̈̆̏̔̐́̾͌̏̏͒̃̅̈́̓̂͊̽͆̅͌͂̄͛͗̆̈́̌̒̾̋̈͒̌̍́͆̏͒͋̃̈́͒͌́̈̎̀͑̓̾̐͌̆̏̓̿͆͆͂͐͗̆̄̿́͌̒̃̓̂͗̈́̀̇̂̈̍̆̈̔̍̀͆͂͒̍͐̐͂̂̓̆̅̎̾̑͗̾͆̊̓̾̌̋͋͛̇͂̒̂̋̈́̌̐͒̔͂̐̄̀̈́̈́̀͑̎̒͆͑̔̿͂̀͛͊͆͌̓͒̅̒̐͛̀̾̎̎̇̋̒͛͑͆̿͛̎͆̒́͛̀̊͂͘̚͘̕͘͘̕̚̕̕̕̕͘̚̕͘͜͜͜͜͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͝͠͠͠͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅA̸̧̨̨̢̧̧̡̧̨̢̡̡̨̡̛̛̛̠̥̣̪̪̝͈̙͚̹̹̱͓̙̬̱̩̣̭̩͚̪͇͎̣̝̜̤̰̦̝̹͙̙͕̤̮̺̯̳̘̣͓̤͔̜͎̩͚͍̤͖̭͍̬̬͕̣͕̫̘̦̦̝̖͓͓̣̠̟̗͇̺̗̖̼̩͓̰̙͚̱͇̯͈̹͇̻͚͇̟͕̼̗͖̖̗̱̞̗̝̟͓̪̖̞̞̰͔̭̘̮̪̩̼͎͎̳͈̟̰̟̥̪͚̻͕͉͙͈̹̫͉̙̣͇̜̜͕̖͚̖͙̬̘̰̿́̍̍̅͆́̈́̑̀̈̋̒͊͊̅͋̔̑̽̆̎͛̉͊̇̀̄̿̓͐̓͆̾̈́̉͗̒̄̋̊̆̿̆̍͋̿̉͌̆̊̈́͗̾͛͛̈́́̇̽̂̉̅̈̔̏̈́͆̍̐̆͊͐̾̏̐̓̽̀̉̄̊̿̋̽̌̊͊̄̈́̈́̿͑̾̊́̇͑̓̑́̐̀̃̄͂̌̃̍̄̏̎̓͆̄̅̂̾́̀̑͗̋̓̈́̒̍͌͗̔̓̉̉͑͑̍̂̏̂̽̈́͐̎̈͋̒̀̐̏̑́̐̿͌̍͘̚̚̕̚͘͘̚̕͘͘̕͘̕͘̕͜͜͜͜͝͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅA̸̢̧̢̧̨̢̡̡̡̡̨̢̨̡̢̨̨̡̢̧̨̡̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̳̹͉̲͙̹͙̝̺̦͚̱͇̼̮̰̱̻̼͙̠̩̬̫͎̘͎̣͕͎͕̘͙͉͓̺̣̯̩̹̯͍̮̦̻̦̝̩̦̬̼̟̘̤̖͖̺̩̟̝̦̙̬̯̱̬̦̯̮̣̝̟̞̟̝̭͕̹̜̘̹̝̯̭̖̠͔͙͚̠̙̟̲̰͈̟̻͔̼̫̪̣̦̰͓͇̟̝̰̣͚̞̮̙̣̣͓̤̯̯͔̼̗̯̘̠͔̬̣̦͙̖̺͎̮̖̼͖̟̗̭̰̘̦̩̤̮̦̭̹̪̤͚̘̹̮̻͓̝̣̪̫̬͉͇̩̙̹͕͚̟̥̣̤͖̥̞̩̤͉͖̹̘͖̝͖̲̭͕̩̩͈̹̼̮̩̬͙̱̪̥̹͇͚̜̥̰̟̱̜̬̝͒͑̓̽͒̒̀̆̂̍̀̓͒̀̀̉̔̍͒̈́̅́͆̽͋̌̓̋͆̏̓̅͋̅̌̈́̒̌̍̑͑̀̋͒̔́͂́̈́̿͋͂̌̔̂͑̉̐̅͛̈́̀͂̍̿̀̅̉́̀̃̉͌̋́̽͗̄͑͋̈́̑̾̑̄̾̈́̎̂́̈́͑͒̿̀̍̇̿͂͂̇̉͒̀̀̐́̎̆͆̏̈́̓̀͋̈́̔̀͒͊͑̊͒͋̉̓̐͌̊̀̉̂̓̃́̀͒̀̔̊͗̐̾̇͊̍̈́̏̀͐͆̓́̊̍̇͛̒̀͐̀̑̿̄̄͛̌͊̇͋͒̽̉̒̋͋͊̄̆̾̐̈́̐̇̍̏̅̀͊́͑͗̓͊̀̀̀̒̍̒̈̄̉̓̓̋̒̈́̀͗̓́̾̎͋͒̕̚͘͘̚̚̚͘̕͘̚̚̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅA̵̢̨̧̡̡̡̧̨̨̧̛̛̛̠͔͖̘̼̬̪͕̻̱͕̱̖͈̗͓̠̘̯̺̗͍̫̱̹͔̺̞̙̠̫̜̹͇̜̳̺͎̘̜̼̭̲̥͔̜͍̺͎͚͉͎͍͙̩͎̺̳̝̲̼̼͖̯͔̫̺̙̘͚̼̥̩͔̖̤͖̬͉̖̥̖̺̩͇͈̖̻̼̮̙̯͈̠͙̯̫̥̬̼̩͎̪̘̞͇̥͈͍̜̥̮̲͔̠̙̘̳̜̜͈̫̥̘͈͕̼̝͈̰̣̱͎̥̠̖̳̖̻͎͉̥̭͚̙͂̔̀͛͛͌̐͆̈́̉͗̏̏̓̑̏̅̆̌̅́̊́͊̅̍͑̅̎̆̌͆͂̃̋͗̓͆̽̌͌̏͒̂̓͐̐͊̍͋̀̆̈́́͛̿̓͊͂̃̽̅̈́̈́̔͒́̂̑̄̉̐̇͒̑͆͐̔̏̅͌͒̈́̓̈́̄͆́̀̾͘͘̚̕̚͘̕̕̕̕̚͜͜͝͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅŖ̵̢̧̧̨̧̢̢̧̢̧̢̧̢̡̱͇͈͍̹̙̱̺̣͙̝͎̝͉̙̯͕͉͓͍̟̫̥͉͎͚̤̣͉̹̹̗͓͓͖̮̜̩̞̝͎̠̫̯̦̲͍̭͉͖̝͔̪̼̻͎͓̫̪͔̣̥̫̖͖̼̠̙̟̗͇͎̤̮̰̺̻̘̲̝̫̝͍͈̯͉̖̗̖̠̳̮͙̣͙̯͕͖̜͚̩͓͉̪̯͚̳̣̝̺̠̰̖͉̟̖̹̬̹̦̺̗̟̻͖͔͎͎̗̹̙̯̺͉̭͔͕͖̟̮̤̳̻̠̹̼̝͚̩̥͎̼͉̭͙͉͖̲̲̦̪̮͈͖̟͍͓͍̫̯͕̣͇̝̫̘̲̻͖͇͍͔̪̟̜̟̖̮̬͓͖́̍͗͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝ͅͅͅR̸̢̡̨̨̧̧̡̧̢̡̧̢̨̢̡̨̢̡̨̧̛̛͎̹̲̣̩̣͔͚̘̖͇̩̩̜̱̭̳͎̤̹̣̱̮͚̼̦̠̩̝̯͚̠̜̭̗̣̹̬͈̩͖͚̲̮͎̠̹̹̠̠̤̤͎̲͓͍͓̩̪̻̤̫̭̳͓̫͎̳͔̞̣͔̯̥͉̹̪̙̭̹͈͍̳̬̰̰̭̬̮̟̞̯̟̱̠͕̹̻̙͔̩̠̟̙̳͕͖͚̯̩̙̬͕̯͉͚͕͍̣͇̖̙͓̖͕̥̳̺͙̼̳̖͎̭̘͇̦͎̜̟͖̈́͌̂͂̔̒̊̐́̿̈́͑̌̒̐̈́̓̀̈̍̿̊̀̐̇̋̊͑̀́͛̌̑͒̓̄̀̆͌́̿͆̒͂̈̒̿́̀͂͆̾̐̄̍͊́͋͒̏̊̿́̊̆̈́̈͐͒̽̐́̅͆̈́̂̎̋̐̔͌͂̔̾̎̋̄͌̅́̐́͑̄̒́͑̈̑̿̀̈́́̿̾̏̐̉͛̀̽̀͊̍͊̈́͆̒̿̀̾̚̚͘̚̚̚̕̚͘̚͜͜͠͝͠͠͠͠͝͝͠͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅR̶̢̨̡̨̨̢̢̧̢̢̡̡̡̡̢̢̧̨̧̢̡̨̨̧̧̢̧̧̢̡̧̨̢̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̺͎͖̟̤̙̪̝̲̫̮͈͔̺͈͙̭͖͙͎͔̫̮̼͙̱͍̥̱̞̹̱̘̦̮̝͇̥̖̯̪͓̩̬̘̫̯͓̱͈̙̩̫͔̖̲̗̗̘̤̖͓̖̥̰̱̝̪͙̭̳͕̺͕̪̭͎͎̳̥͍̩̮͍̟͉̫͓̺̮̬̠͖͖͖͕̯̥̦̞̭̘̟͎̜͔͈̲̼̞͉͍̟̝͖͔̣̦̩̙͈͚͚͔̗̞͖̘͍̗̮͓̯̫̦̯̪̰̹̠̖̠̮̪̟̟͎͕̙̳̪̗̞͖̺̖̻͓̼͕̻̜̞͇̺͍̯̖̬͇̥̘̼̟̜̭͈͈̟̮̜̪͍̝̱̰̭̩̱̯̮͉̞̠̤̣͉̫̦̗͓͔͖͚̻͎̗̩̩̯͍͎͉̟̹͚͖̻̳̫͈̪͎̪͉̜͕̥̥̼͉̞̤͔̗͍̹̯̒́̈́͆̿͆̃̍͒̅̋̈́̈́͌͐͌͗͗̋̎́̑̏̑̀̈͐͆̇̐̀̋̓̒̄̄̋̋̿̆̔̑́̇͊̀́̑̆͐͆̊̔̆̆̌̓̇͗́̔̍́̿͆̆̋̅͋̏̎̓͒͌̎͛̐͐̎̋͌̒͛͐̑͆͑͑͒̆̆̄̋̋̂̀̋̎̓́͑̓̓̿̾̍͛̉͒͑̑͗́̉͑͑̓͛̌̓̎̔̅̏͂̽̏́͑͋̈́͛͊̂̒̀̓͌̆̓͑̅̈́́̌͂̏͌̔̇̑̌̎́̑́̽̏̽̋͋̏̈́͌̊́̌̈́̇̆͋͆͗͋̌̇̎͐̋͋̍̊́̃̒̉͛̽̆̓͋̓̍̌͑͐͗̑̏̍̌̓̾̊̓͋͛͒̾̾͛̎̆͋͂̍̋͋̄̾̾̓͑͑͗̕̚̕̚͘̚̚̕͘̕̕͘̚͘͘̚̚͘̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅŖ̸̡̨̨̧̢̧̛̰̰͓̝͔̪̳̘̻̩̩͉̗͔̠̙͍͍̹̖̳̩͕̱̺̣͎̗̯̟͓̠͍̩͈̜̹̣͇̝̺̦͉͓͖̬̞̠͕͍̥̤̯͓̞̅̀̋͌͆͒̏̌͑́̏́́͆̀͑̉̍́̾͗́̅͌͐̆̿̈́̉͌͌̃̀͌͆̏̍̏̎͒̂͐̀̓̿̈́̈́͒̈͂͂̔͆̃̚̚̕͜͜͜͝͝͝͠͝ͅͅṚ̸̢̢̧̧̢̨̨̢̢̨̧̨̧̧̛̛̗̖͓̫̻̥̼̺̼̪̖̘̭̯͚̼̞̼͕̪̣̜̮̪͕͉̠͚̜̪̘̲̮͈͕͎̟͉̰̠͖̜̝̣̯͍̟̦̪̙̲̫̤͙̰̹̠̩͓͔̖̙͕̼͍͈̱̯̣̲͍̖͚͍̠̙̜̜̦̤̻̤͉̫͇̘͈̼̝̺͖͉͍̝̹̪̥̣͎̰̟̳̺̥̥͖̳̲̱̱͚̼̖̼͎̮̲̩̝̪̹̖̤̼̫̼̭̣̜̞̥̘̤̫͚̥͎͙͖͍͉̣͙̭̫̮͖̰̤̝͔̟̤̭̘͓̰̙͙̜̭͙̃͌̍͌͑̊̏̋͂͑̇͗̽͂͒̂̒̌̂͌̀̏̐͋͒̔̓̽̑̀́́̔̿̓́̾̿̒̈́͒͗̈̅͋̂͋̋͒̑̀̽̉̓̑̈́̋͂̏͐̒̿̑̈́̏̄͊̔̍̓͑͊̽̑̀̉͋̋̊̈̈́̾̒̽̔̆̍̿͋̆͛́͐̔̍̿͗́̾̏̌̈́͋̍́̄̎͊̊̒̓̂͛͘͘̕̕͘͘̕͘̚̕̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͝͠͠͝͠͝͠͠͝͝͠ͅͅͅṚ̶̡̨̡̨̨̨̧̢̧̧̢̧̢̨̢̡̧̢̨̢̧̢̡̨̡̡̧̢̨̛̛̛̰͕̦͕̬̱͈̫̞͇͙̪͍̩̺̩̪̜̫̰̗̺͎̯̮̝͉̠̺̳͇̭̩̲̯̝͕͉̠̱͇̮̹͍̳̝͚̖̺̻͕̣͚̥̭̮̦̥͙͙̭̙̹̹̟̣̤̯̱̩̯̭̼̙̠̬̮̰̫̖̩͈̤͖͎̫̹͍̖͍̯̯̠̞̜̙̜̹̱̲̫̭̗͍̙͉̘̙̼̥͖̟͖̭̝̻̪͓̫̪̯̝̰̟͈̩̘̦̦͎̳̖̙̱̱̳͎͖̱̬͚̮̗̦̳̮͈̟̲̙̩͈̥̪͎̗͔̠̳̼̣͕̦̮̮͚̰̲̩̬̠̼̹̳͈̖̲̩͔͎͎̩̣͙̼̼͙̥͙̮͎̫͔̦̠̥̭̯̮̟̣͍̞̖̜̜̞͚̝̟̤̟͙̥̻̱̜͍̰̮̪͓͙͖͕̘̜͍̰͎̖̭͕͍̼͉͙̗̗͕̮̰̭̌̀̈́̽̅̉͂̾̈́̓͑̒̒̽́̃́̍̂̈́̊̌̓̈́̇̓͒̑̇̂͒̔̾̇̿̉̑̂͋̋̒̋̆̇͋̐̌̐́̑̍͒͛̈́͊̎̏̓̀͒̓̋̾̾̇̆͌̾̈́̅̊͆͋̊̈́͗͌͆͊̔̋͐͑͛́́̆͐̅͗͋̊͒̿̑͛͛͊͒͆̃͆͑͆̾̏̈́̀̓̎̀̏̽̆͗̽̍͌̏͂̐̂̑̓̔͛͒̒̃́͆͆̀̂̇͑̓̏̀̈́̓͂̈͛̈̀́̌͑̌̎́̈̋̃̋̈́̅̌̄̒̋̈́̉̀͛̍̇̅͆͗̇́̀̽̓̊̈́͂̿̈̌̒̐̉̉́̍̓̈́͋̽͛̀̉̊̅͒̿̔͑͆̒́͐̂͑̓̀̅͛́̓̿̐͑̾̏̍͌̏̎̚̚̕̕̚͘̕͘̕̚͘̕͘̚͘͘̚̚̚̚͘̚̕͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅR̵̡̢̧̢̡̡̢̧̛̛̛̛̮̱̘̟̠̫͚̤̭̥͓͈̲̟̺̳̤̜͇̼͉͕̫͓̺̺̟̼̺̫͎̲̦͍̳̙̞̯̫̹̝̠͓̺̻̦̝̭͓̱̝̘̮̞͕͔͔͇̟̰̳̭̭̥̥̼͖̺͎̰̙͚̳̙̖̳͙̗̥̤͍̮̣̯͍̗͚͍̪̯̟̹͍̥͇̬̬̮̦̼̣̣͚̫̻͉̮̟̻̖̤̬͇̞̻̜̗͍͖͉͎̥͔͖͉͚͎̹̰̟̠̞̹̰͋̎̎̐̈̽̈́̀̀̓͆̂̾̽̀̈́̔̒͊̂͌̋́͐̓͒̇͋̓̿̈́͌́̾̅̊̂̾̈́́̒̽̃͗̐̀͆̑̑͆͑̃͐̀̈̀͂́̀̐̇̔̿̋͌̋͛͋̄̌͊͑̌̽̽̎̈́̎͐͌̈́̀́̄̂̾͒̀̽̅̓̃̂̓͑́́͊̓̏̿͑̀́͛̇͛͛̆̌̈́̃̾̇͑̌̾͐͑̽̀̂̍͛̆̂̔́͆̒̓͂̒̂̽̽̒̓̑͌͌̈́͒͂͒̿̆̋̂̈́͗̉̇͂͋̇͐̓̃̓̓̿̎̌͋̍̒͒̀̿͐̅̒̒̈́̀͛̀̍̓̃͆̏̓̽̈̑̀̍̉̓̂̍̄̄̀̀̒̾̄̽̿̊͌̽̀̍̂̌̂̀̇̇͛̔͒̋̀̈́̍́̔̍̾̒͂̋͌̇̈́̔̂̌̽̏̈́̉̿̐͒̏͂̚̚̕̚͘͘̚̚͘̕̚̚͘̚͜͜͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅR̴̡̡̧̧̡̢̧̢̢̢̡̧̨̢̨̨̨̡̧̢̡̧̧̛̛̛̛͈̪̜̟͎̟̠̫̪̥̯̹͖͉͇͔̤͎̰̩͚͈̟̘̱̞͇̥̠̞̠̥̦͉͉͚̠͍̠͖̲̜̙͕͈͎͇̲̼̺̱̟͓͕̬͔̟͓̰̱̹̪̻̳̰̗̤͍̦͕̙͇̜͙̜͖̺͉͖͓̹̝̟̱͍̞̝̼̼̲̼̞͚̯̯̘̺̭̤͙̲͔̜̗͉̲̣͚̳̲̞͈̲̭̭̯̞̩͓̞͍̦̜̝͍̭̩̳̬͎̗̮̟̤̖̯̤̭̹̗̩̤͈̭̱̝̭͇͔̹͍̭̞̣̝͈͕͔̮̠̻̪̰̦͙̫̹̗̲̠͍̻̫̫̲̼̯̬̝̳̳̭̬̺͉̻̥͎͍̲̪͇̙̮͖̺͓͇̼̻̗͚̻̝͔̹̞͍͙͎̖̙̬͖̼̻̱̣͕͔̫̘̹̦̱̪͇̗̮̣͎̯̖̳͔̰͔̬͓͈̺̬̹̺͖̪͔̠̼͇̬͈̞̦͓̍̐͒́͗͆̀͌̏̃̈͗͛̃͒̒̉̓̈́̒̿̈̈́̓́̃̾̐̋͑̈̍̓̑͐̈͆̍͛̋̓̀̊̓͂̐́̈́̅́̓͒͒̈́̓̈́̀͋̂̑͋́͂̊͊̊̌̈͑͒͛̑͒̋̍͋͗͒̅̏̃̐̓͌̏̊͐̂̓̇͌͋̇̏̒̆̆̈́͛͗͛͊̈́̿̄͒̽͊̉͆̋̅̄̅̅̑̔͗͒̐̒̒̎͒̇̓͂̿͑̈̔͊͌͛͋͒̎̌̉͘͘̚͘͘̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͝͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅK̷̛̛̫̱͕̻̭͍̼̥̭̀̈́́͒̉̊͒̎̿͊̓̆͗͂̃̿͌̎̒̍̓̀͋̉͊̌̈́͗́͊̎̉̋͂̉̏͒͊͂̈͑̈̉͒͂͂͆͗̐̃͒̐̄̑̀́̇̄̄̄́͋̄̑̈́̑̔͐͊̽̀͒̃̐̀̃̓̍͊̆̌̅͑̆̑͋̋̐̉̃̏̈́̓̓̔̇̍̎͊̏̉͒͌̃̀́̀͑͋͑͊̑͘̚͘͘̚̕̚̚̕̚̕͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͠͝ͅK̷̡̧̧̢̧̡̧̧̧̨̢̡̧̡̨̡̢̡̡̨̢̧̨̛̛̛̰̰̖͕̳̮͚͔̣̮̰͇̜̗̫̣͎͕͉͉̻̫̹̩̠͇̯͈̖̩͔̜͚̦̤̦͖͎̦̤̫͇͕̻̻̮̯͍͉̤͔̲̖̬̼̗̻͍̫͔̤̝̬͚̲̥̫̮̻̳̝̞̻̘̻̞͇̝̮͉͇̤̼͎̗͉̮̪͈͎̖̥̞̙͍̟̥͚̝̖̺͕̳͕͍͈̫̰̭͉͎̝̯̻̼̞̘̹̱̭͓̱̹̥̟̭̟̳͎̞̬̭͉͚̰̮̣̺̘̥͉͚̤̪͚̼͖̻͔̳̠̝̪͓͓̺͓̟͖̟̜̜̘̦̯̲͉̬͈̗͓̻͈͎̯̠̝̦̩̜̖͙̲̙͖͈̳͚͖͔̻̖͉̦͇̺̜͓̪͔̫͙̻͈͇̳̝͔̪̜̙̪̱̤̹̩̥̪̦͙͍͎̱̮͖͉̹͕̜̟̬͈͓̹̠͓͈̜̣̯̜̠͙̪͖͖͔̪̮̖̰͓͕̬̥̮̠̳͕̟͉̪̐̀̏͋̈́̍́̂̄́͂͒̅̍̈̄̈́̀̓̉̈̿͗̑̊̌̌͑͊̍́̽̾̎̒̿̅͌̒͛͑̀̃͗͋͛͊̈̉̇̇̈́̊̏̈̈̀̌̌̄̆́̈́̅̒̎̓̂̀̃̃̎̐̿̒̀͌̊͐̓̓̑̓̈͆̾͑̒̿͑̃͐͌̽̏́̋̈́̔̀̂͆̽̐̃͒̋̐́̄̋̈́̿͋̈̃̈́̈́̌̿̄̇̈́͐̈́̏͆̃͐͒̀̇̄̊̀̋͐̀̓̊͛́͂̑͋̓̽̈́͊̆́̆̃̔̈́̃̑̂̊̏͗̃́̿͂̒̑̍͑̍̈́͋̇̀͂̎̋̅̎̌̄͛̑̉̈̆͐͋͑̍̇̄̽̂͛̏̎͌̋͌̑̌͐̀̉́͑̆̊̿̏͐͊͗̓͋͑͒̎̍͌̎̓̈́͌̐̀͋̕̕̕̚̚͘̚̕̚̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅA̸̧̨̢̡̢̨̧̢̧̡̨̧̧̡̢̧̡̧̧̡͕͖͉̗̝̜͈̰̩̳͚̫͖̲͈̟̥̼̱̹͔̺͈̯͖̥̬̳͔͎̙͎̲̲̯̻̹̱̖̹̺̦̝̝͙͈̺͉̻̠̰̖̮̻͈̙̘̞͔͍͎̖͖̲͖̠̝̮̯̝͔͙̟̻̗̬͓͓͎͚͓͙͓̖͕̪̝̬̫͉͍̬͍̘̠̱̤̪̞͈͔͕̜̫̤̩̙̳̪̝͓̺̞̯̣̻͈̤̮͙͓͙͎̱̗̬͇̲̼̭͔̤̳̭̫̪̫̫̪̹̥̼͖̞͙̰͎̼͕̞̝͍͚̰̩̳̮̯̮̝̮̥̻̭̜̤̫̼̲̘̭̻͎̭̠͚̻̻̱͙͎̠̜̘̘̘̰͕̘̭͙̗̬̲̺͉̪̳͙̰̻͚̼̟͍̭͔̠̺͎͉̟̜̺̬̹͙̦͍̪̥̫̱͔̖̭̗̦̱͔͇͙̪͚̭̮̳͕͙͈̣̻̱̱͚̼̘͔̹̝͕̞͚̻̪͎͔̠̪͔̜̳̞̎̌̈́̄͊̃̍̈́̀͗͋̾̇͒͗̉͒͌̿̈͑͗̋͑̒̏͆͌̚̚̕̕̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̶̢̨̧̢̧̢̧̢̨̨̡̧̡̡̨̡̛̛̰̹̳̫̙͙͎̦̥̮̹͕̩̬̪͖̲̼̰̻͇̪͍̖̙̦̗͕͇̱͙̰̯̩̖͓̯̳̹̘͔͓̦͍̦̦̘͇̙̖̫͈̱̦̫͍͕̹͔̩̮̥̼̟̜͓̭͙̹͉͉̫̖̹̱̖͓͙̫͉̙͇̗͈̣͍̩̹͖̭̦̩̹̪̟̪̝̹̦͖̻̬̩̞̻͇̮͓̪͕̭̳̯͇̻̗̠̖̮̮͙̳͔̯͙͚͖̞̝̩͇̱̩͙̳͍̺̙̗͓̼̮͎̳̮͍̤̮̩̘̣̰͈̱̞̫̖̣̻̼͕̥͍͚͚̹̯̗̙̹̖̗̼̱̳̥͕̝̜̳̜̻͚̺̱̲̖̦̝͚̤̗͍̣̫̭̦̟̝̱̦͔̠̥̲͔̟̥̤̫̻̰͍̭͉͙͚͓͍̳͖̻͔̼̩͓͉̰͉̹͇͗̂̃̍́͂̀̽̏̊̇̑̉̐̒̀̊͊̾̿̓͂̐́̀̽̉͆̉̋͛̓̍̆͒̈́̾͐̂̂͒̆͛̈̍͂̀͐̂͋̾̊̾̾̌̈́͐̈̈̌̅̉̽͋͑͛̆̒̈́̈́̆̈́͒̽̿̆̄́̃͌̉̇͒͂͗͆́̓͆̊̂̀̎͋͆͊́͑̈͊̒̑̉̈̃̍̀̅͑́̂́̄̈͌̓̀̓̂̀̓́̉͗̃̒̓͛͒͒͆̓̈́͑̄̾̆̇͛̉́̉̄̑͐̀̐͊̿̇̂̑̄̓̇͋͑͋́̎̄̉̃̆͐̒͒́̅͐͐̌̾́̃̍́̉̓̎̿̓͒̋̀̿̄̓̚̚̕̚͘̕͘̕̚͘̕̚̚̚̚̕͘͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̷̡̢̡̢̨̢̡̨̨̧̨̛̛̛̛̛̛̦͕̻̫̞̦̰͇̰̦̖̲̯̻̭͍̟̹̭̦͉̬̯͇̰̱̦̯̺͇̮͙͚͖̼̞̮̣͚̪̱͍̜̜͕͉̻̺̲̫̙̮̫̣̻͙̩̲̗̩͈̲͙̙͖̟̻͇̫̱̦̻̤̺̗̪̳̖̹̻̘̠̲̤̟̫̼͖̞̳̜̣̩̣̬̦̜͙̭̣̘̝͇͔͉̰̭͇̱̰͚̣̝͙̘͙̳͌͐͋̈́̈́͂̀̈́̋̒͆̒̿̾͗̂͋̽͒͛͛̏̓̐̍̐̓͌̏̐̅̈͒͑̽̀͒̒͌̆̂̍́̉͊͂̅́͑͂́͑͐̓̀̀̌̈́̔̋́̆̋̐̌̅́̏̒̇͑̈́͌̈́͊̎͑͐̐̒́̄͂͆͆͊͋́̄̋͆̓̅̂̇̂̓́͐̀̉̀̆̀̑̿͋̉̽̈́͊̾̈́̀̊̽̊͗̈́̆̌̌̆̋̽̒̍̽̉͊̈́͗̇̌̂̉̈́̍̓̈̄̌͛̎͑̈́̋̎̃̽̏͂̑́͑͑̒͋́̒͋̈́̍̅͊̾͒̄̔̉̈́́̅͌̀͊̒͒̌͋̈̄͒͌̏̄́͂̀̀̓́̒͗̈́̍̈̍͒̋̃͊̌͋͛̎̾̌̀̚̚̕̕̚̕̚̕̕̚̚͘̕̚͘͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅA̴̡̡̨̨̢̡̡̛̛̛̛̛̠̱̲̗͖͚̪̭̻͇̳͈̹͚̘̩̙̗̻̳̼̩̦̟̱̝̝͕̪̖̣͍̻͕̝̬̟̗͕͍͕̩̞͉̣͎̟̙̱̳͓̖̺͎̱̳̤̘̝̼̦̮͓͈̲̺̰̟̞̟̙̰̣͙̣̼̫͎̲̼̞̞̓̏̏̎̽̇̈́̇̐̏̓̏̎́̊̀͋̌̓͐͋͂̄̈́͋̇̈́̊̇̒̓̈́̓̌̀̆͛́̏́͑̿̄̽͑̅̿̌́͊͗͛͋̀̽̄̓͋͆̉̌̂̀͂͊̆́̒̽̍̽͆͋̎̒̂̇̋̎̍̊͐̋̿̑͐͒͗͐̀̈̿͊̒́̓̏͒̈́͑̔̆̓̾̌̊̅̓̾̌̔͗͆́̂̎͂̊͊͆̓͒͆̊̇͑͗͒͋̎͊͛̉̌̇̏̑̾̎̎̍͂͑͒̄͑̐̀̄̆͐̄͂́͋͒͗̐̓̈́̀̎̌̏̑̓͋̾͂̎͂̿̍̊̇̽͆̃͒̐͐̑͂́͆̔̑̾̂͗̽̽͛̿́́̈̌̓͂̀̎̽̓̒́́̄̌̌̚͘̚͘̕̚͘̚̚̕̚̚̕̕̕̕̚͘̕͘͘͘̕͜͜͠͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͠͠͝͝͠͠͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅÁ̸̢̢̡̛̠̟̝͇̳̻̝̞̰͎͓̤̪̲̰͖̱͖̯̩̜͕̮͚̬̻̜͕͈̫̙̒̒́͑̑̌̓͊͂͊͋́̊̀̋̔̾̏̒̀̂̎̂͊̽͒̔̾̿̾͆͂͑̇̈́̏̇̐̈́̂͐̾̔͗̓̿͒̌̾̾͗́̚̕̕͜͝͠͝ͅÃ̸̢̨̧̢̢̧̢̨̡̢̡̧̨̨̢̛̛̛̛͕̥̘͍̫͇̟͔͚̟̣̝͉̬̰͚͎̠̯̥̰͍̟̗̝̙̤͕͈̪̼̟͙̫̤̳͉͓̫̥̱̼̭͎̩͖̞̳͙̞̬̞͓͚͙̟͓̬̰̱͖̣̦̙͓̮̗͎̘͚̻̺͇̲̻̮̖̲̣̖̟̣̣̹̤͙͙̰̱̜̖̳̗͉̹̰̣̺̥̞̱̼͎̭̩̣̣̬͔̫̰͓̹̞͍̼̗̭̥̘̥̹͕̝̠̻̜̀̂͊̈́̓̄̉̆̔̀̌̈́̋̈̓̀̾͗͂̉͊̃̈́̑͑͌̃͊̉̑́͂̆̈́̍̽͊́͛̃̽͌͛̒͊̓͛͂̓̀̂͐̊̇̇̇͊̐͋̄̀̅͆͊̌́͒͗͒̄̈́͋͐̀͐͊͗̄͌̀͛̽̽̈̓̓̿̓̈́̍͒̃̌̾̑̌̃̑͒̉̒̇̆̑̾̏̀̔͌̈́̋̊͂̇̉̽̐͛̾͛̄̀̃̏̆̃̃̈́͂̌̾̆̂͒̾͋̇̌͐̎͗͐͑͗͒͆̾͑̐̎́͊̍̈́̽̇̀͂̇͋̆̾̄́̐̋͗̏̎̀͆̄̉͑̓͋̈́̌́̕̚̚̚̚̕̚̚̚̚̚͘͘̕͘͘͜͜͜͜͠͠͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͝ͅͅĄ̵̡̧̨̧̨̢̨̢̡̡̢̧̢̨̧̧̡̢̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̝͉̻͔̖̺̮̱͔̳̖̳͕̬͇͖͕̫͓̰͕̜̤̹͉̺̳͈̺͖̰̰̱͕͈̠̬̲̭͇̣̖̖͍̦̲̫͖͎̯̹͇͈̮̳͙̫̖͙͇͎̼͚̱̪̥̭͔̙̰͈̪̩̗̥̩̰̜̙̦͕̹̰̣̤͓̱̥̹̫̗̳̱̜̦̯͇͓̝͎̱͎̦̟̝͚̺̬͖͉̹͓̤͇̲̫̼͍̖͔̺̭͓̻̳͔̺̭̤̪̻̱̪̱̼͖̘̭͖͓͕̼̣̲̹̥̺̣͍͈͉̖͕̖̹̯̻̗̱̘͎̖͕̞̜͓̹͎̞̝͔̜̖͙͍̫͔̮̟̰̺̮͚̭̫̼̙͙͇̳̱̺̱̰̣̤͎̲̮̬̺̥̳̮̦͎͚̗͓̘̺̳͙̤̙̣͓̭͚͇͎͍̼͖̜͙̥̮̺̙̰̩̜̞͕͚̔̽̒͑̿̓͛̈́̉̇̂͊̓̎̓̐̀͑̃͆́͐̈́͛̀̒͐͋̇̔̀͑͑̂̾͋̎̉̅̋̔͊̓̈́́͂̑̒̈́̓̀̄̋́̆̎͌͊͑̐͐͗͛̍̓̓͗̈̎̀̋͊̾̀́͊͌̐͑͐̌͒̀͑̏̐̒̓̓͛͗͌͂̀̋̽̉͆̏͌͂̍̎́̈̉̾͆̀̏̄̌̎̎͑̊͂̒́̃̾̓̍̉̾̆͆̈́͐̿̃̊̍̄̈́͛̽͐͑̋̌̀̇͗̈́̾̓̉̔̈́̆̾͆̒̋̿̇̾̃͐͊̔̈́́̄̇́̾̈̆͗̅͐͑̍͂̋͂͗͌̊̈̈́̈́̾͛̄̀͛̃͑̆̎͌͆̓͗̉͑̃̾͆̓̿̐͆̅̀̆͑̃̂̀̈́̑̉̀͋̑̿̒̈͆̽͋̐̉͒̀̀̆͗̎̈̈́͊̽͗́͊̎̎̽̎͂́͋̚͘͘͘̕͘͘͘̚̚͘͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͠͠͝͠͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅẢ̵̧̢̨̧̨̢̡̧̢̡̨̨̨̢̢̢̧̡̢̨̨̡̛̛̛̱̘͓̟̦̞̲͚͙̬͎͈͍̥̜͇̼̟̲̮̣̺̠͙̩̣̞͙̬̙̝̫͙͕͎̯̟͖͉̙̩̦̘̖̪͇̤͚͚̩̟̣̟̰̭̝̙͉͈͉̲̤̻̮̘̠̲͚̭̞̙̠͕͇̗̦̥̯̠̖̗͈͙̱̪̝̭̰̲̻̙̳̻̯̦͓͖̞̭͉͇͉̹̘͚̪̦͚̻̜͚̦͚̗̣͔͔̗͔͖̯͎͎͍̤̰̪̻̝̳̳̥̭͉̱̞͙̤͎̦̖̟͖͔̖̬̦̩̤͚̣̪̹̰̹͍̹̖̜̝̦̰͎͓̥͍͍̩̰̼͈͈̟̖̰̝͇̈̊̌͑̎͂̎̄̈͊̓̎̐̿̇̓̐̀̓̒̾̓̍̊͗̃̋̽͂̀͛͗̌̐̈́͑́̐̀́͐͌̒̏͆̏͒̅̾̑̓͐͌̊́̌́̈́̈̃͆̊̓̑̉̿̌̐͐͒̔̍̆͋͛̋̇̓̊̏̎̉́͐̀̊̒͊̂̄̌̔̌̂̄̂́̃́͑̊̅́͒͗̅͑͑̓̅͑̃̉̇̐̇́͆͌̀̒͊̌̔̏͋̓͛̆̉̄̽̀͒̒̉̌̀͐͛̊̂̓͂̋͑̈́̔̄̊̇̈̎͆̿̐̄̍͊́̂̀̑͌̂́̈́̑̀̾̐̆̍͆̏̇̊̎̋̑͊̔̂̏̿̿̃̽̈́̆̀͊̈́̍̊́̋̊̓̐̈́͆́̔̇̍̈́̽͛̔̿͂̅̈̏͐̒͗̈̐̽̓̈́́͋̓͒́̈́̇̓̾͒͒̔̍̆̑̕̕̕̕͘̕͘̚͘̚̚͘͘͘̚̚̚͘̚̚̕͘̚͜͜͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͠͝͠ͅͅA̸̡̡̧̧̢̧̨̧̨̟͔̝͎͇̩̖̪̰̣̞̲̠̯͉̮̘͖͉̖̺̥̺̥̮̪̟͚͚̭͓͚̜̝̣͎̲͙̳͙̹̰̭̗̹͍̟͍͓̪̯̰̺̺̪̖͖͕̰̻̫͙̣̻̜͊̓́͛̊̽͑̀̀͑̄͐͂̃͒̇̉̓̓̂͋̋̍̏̌̂̇̀͂̐́̉̈́͒̈͆͛̄̿̐͋̈́̄͒̿͌̔͂̏͐͆̏͋̏͂̈́̿̔͛̇͑̎̂̆̾̀͆̈́̀̓̽̎̃͂͌̑́́̅̃̓̇͒̒̆͑͊͌̓̏͑͑̽͊̾͐̐̐̎̉́́̍̓̽͒̃̓̍̌̓̒͘̕̚̚͜͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͠ͅĄ̶̧̧̡̡̨̧̨̡̧̡̧̢̛̛̛̛̱͓͉̪̗͚̳̤̫̖̫̱̭͍̬͕̼̦̜̮̯̞͙̦̰̭̲̲̘͔̘̖̪̠̬̬͍͙̫͕̭͙̬͍̱͍͙̭̥̼̦̠̞͇̘̦̲̮̜̞̠͓̩̥̩̥̞̹͎̺͖̬̜̹̯̞͚̺̞̞̻̳͍̲̖̥͈̙͈͓̠̫̳̜̖̰̯̱͕̯̪͎̠̹̗̣͇̼̳̙̫͉̦̱̺̬̖͍̭̻̜͖̘̦̝̮̪̱͖̠͙̮͕̪̬͉͎̙͓̠͍̹̞̗̟͍̝̝̝͖̫͙̲͕̳̪̬̠͈̞̳̖̹͕͓̻̰͉͕͇̪̰̮̯̺̻̫̗̩̘̟̭̞̣̱͍̹̩̬̣͉͒̃̈́͗̂́̎̑̃͌͋͌͊̀̉̄̊́́̍̿͑̾͐̃͆̑͊̓̍̍̊̓̇̌̈́̋̇̊̾̌̔̓̇̔̃̃͐̐͗͆̐̅͆́̐̇͑͗͗̆̓̅͋͌͐͒̏̆̓̆͆̋́̿̅̿͌́̏͊̐͒̔͌͐͗̏͋͋̉̍̿̅̔͆̄̊̌̓̿̑͐͑̅̌̒̔̐̓̎́̔͋̓̋̈̔́͗̂͆̽̔̏̈́̍̒͌͛̑̔͌̈́̉̀̊̉̂̿̊̒͛̔̔̏̈́̉̔͑́́̏̐̚̚͘͘̕̚͘͘̕̕̚͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͠͠͠͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̴̧̡̨̡̡̧̧̡̡̡̡̨̛̛̛̛̺͍͖̻̮͍̞̬̘͚̖̩̤̩̖̬͍̳̼͎̝̖̥̪̣̣̳̦̫̞̭̦̘̝̦̘̜͙̲̙̼͔̣͍̼͍̜̼̘͈̯͓͉̰̞̻͖̙͚͉̬̦̙̭͕̲͙̦̟̖̙͔͓͕̜̥̙͕͍̬͈̩͕͍͉̜̳̼̤͚̬͔̳͖̺̩͉̖̳̝̮͉͎̱͉̝͎̠̭̗̼̫̝̰͓̦̜̦̬̟͈̪̘̖̳̭̤̼̣̻̠̥̺͖̺̲̘̹̺̱̫̣̱̰̜̙̳̯̺͉̬̝̠̅̊̿̈̑͑̈́͌̓̽̿̈̄̆̾͛̽̐̊̎̂͛̒̓͋̽̈́̄̃̒̓̅̍͆̄̈́̈̎͐͌́̅̊̾̍̾̈́͋̇̈́́͛͋̑͑͊̈́̔̔͂̑̏͗̈̀̐͛̂͛͐̆̉͊̾̌̌̉́̂͛̀͒̒̓̆̾̏́̑̀͆̽͆́̽͛̌͂͊̂̋̅̀̎̈́̔͋̈́͐͂̇̌́̋̾̐̾̋̋́̓̅̈̈́͆͌̈́̇͑̈̏͒͐́̑̄̊̐̈́̈̐̄̇͋̌͆̌̿̏͒͗͂̿͐̈́̍̐̇̍͑͂͛̉̌̐̅̓̆̌̆̈́̉͛̍̂̊̅̐̈̈́̊̆̾̈́̈́̅̉́̎͐̒̓́͊̌̂̎̚̚̕̕̚̕̚̕̕̚̕̚̕̕̕̕̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͝͠͠͠͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͠͠͝͝͠͠͝͠͠ͅͅÀ̴̧̡̢̡̨̢̨̨̨̧̢̡̡̨̨̨̡̧̢̧̧̡̨̨̨̡̧̛̛̛̛̛͚͕͈̺͖̯̥̘̻͙͖̹͉͓͉̺̩̻̲̤̹͍̞̗̬͉̫̟̯̯̻͎̱̪̳̗͙̥͖̟̝̥̹̞̰͍͍͉̟̙̗̦̣͎̭͔̖̺̦̫͈͉̙̝̫̻̬̠̙̲̺͖͚̙̗̖̤̺͈̗͙̮̞̘͍͔͖̦̯̟͔̺͍̳̳̳̪͙̣͓̹̤̣̜̞̤̬̙̟̞͈͕̳̹̫͓̟̜̘͔̖̞̪̮̣̰͓̰̗̙̗̗̩̪͙̠̟̜̙̞͎̪͓͓̘͚̰͔͓̳͇̼̞̹̪̦̠͎̹͍͙̟͈͍͚̦͓͎͕͎̙̮̻̲̦̰̲͓̫̣̤͇̲̺̙͇̗̳͓͎̪̺͕̖̙̙̲̜͖̯̮̞̱͈̤̩̤̱̠̳̜̙̠̥̩͉̙͉̩̰͖͙͙̰̞͇͕̮̞̩͙̺̰̲̟͇͎͓͉̩͖̲̖͓̩͉̞̝̫̼̫͓̩͚̙̳̬͙̝͓̲̀͐́̽͑͒̍̆͐̍̉̋̋̑͆̋̅̓̆̉̍̓͗́͌̄̃͑̈́͊̍̂̅̊̐͂͛́̎̅̅͑̑̊̏̀̔̀͊̽̎̌͂̓̈̉̊̏̎̾̑́̔̀̉̇̓̎̑̈̈́̀̈̔͊̂̐͊̓̒̈́̋͊̇̑͗́̈́̏͊̋͌̇̀̔͑̌̒̌̇̍͗̊͂̔͐͂͒͐̈́̒͊͌̓̅͌̆̏͌̒͑̽̋̓́̈̔͂̔̾͐͛̆̒̇̓̈̈́̎̏̆̿̓̏̀̐̈́̎͗̀͋̀̽̉̀̾̐̏̆̋̋̈́͂̒͋̽͐̆́̊̉̍̓̇̚̚͘̕͘̕͘͘͘̚̚̚͘̕̕̕̚͘͘̕͘͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅA̸̡̢̧̨̢̡̡̢̢̧̨̡̢̢̨̢̨̛̛̛̛̛̛͎̲̪̞͇̹̻̱͙̮̳̟̹̺̜̥̖̤̼̝̦͓̭͕͇̯̼̮̣͚͕̜̝̜͍̯̣̬̟̰̼̭̞̪̗͉͕̞̣̬̲̹̪̯̹̦̟͉̩̝̖͓̮̠͖͎̥̗͈͔̼̝̠̲͈̭̬̜̩̠̯̥͓̘͙͙̞̻̠̪̰̫͕̜̼͕̱̹͙̙̜̰̗̗̬̣̼͖̳̩̟̜̟̹̻̙̺͙̟̰͔̫̯̩̩͇͙͙̺͚͖̥̝̗̣̩͉̤̺͎̺͎̯̪͕͓̫̫̼͇͖̩̖̦͍̻̞̣̜̮̥̖̥͖̻̤̞̹̬̜̰̘̻̞̼̗͚̥̰̣̗͎̹̦̠͍̯͈̩̮̬̯̳͖̭̞̗͔̜̻̩̦̲̹͍͖̫̙̰̱͔̪̞̰̻̟̬̱̹͔͇̮̲̫̤͎̭̝̪̲̺̯̞̦̗͉͕͇͔̭͍̞̬̗͔̟͖̝̳̟̙͈͛̓̔͂̿̊̂̓̈́̈̆̓̇̈́̉̎́̓̅́̓͌͊̃̔͗̐͒̎̈͆̋͑̂͋̀̏̆͊͛̓̽̌͂͑̓̎̐́̑̏̄̌̍̈̈̇̌̊͊͒̆̄̇̎̀͂̄͒͆̓̎̊̌͂̀͆́͋̋̀̉̒̏̓̂͗̇̀͋̈̀̅͛́̌͑͛͋̌̇͐̌̅̋̍̋̆͑̋͛̀̋͛͋͌̿͛̓͆̌̍̀̇͊̄͋̎̋̃̐̽̎̃͒̿̅͆̽̇̊͑̀͋̃͂̽̀̄̋̌̃̀͋̄͑̋̀͌̑̈́͌̔̀͐̉͑̀̈̓̈̎̍̽̂̒͒̄̄̓̀̂̌͆̈̉̔́̐̿̅͌̒̉̔̽̚̕͘̚̚̚̚̕̕̚̕̚̕͘͘̕͘͘̚̚̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅA̸̢̡̨̢̧̨̢̢̧̛̛̛̝͔͇̳̩͔͈̣̻͇̞̟̫̳͔͔̞̗͍̯͈͖͇̪̩̝̙̖̙̦̥̪̣̬͖̞͚͚͍̬̠̗͚͈̗͖̙͓̣͔͚͕̝̠̝͓̯̤̘̮̟̹̳͉͓͚̗̳̞͍͔͎̺̱͕̹̲͎̣̰̹̬͑͑̏͂̊͐̒̿͐̅̍̒͛̇̽̓̂͂͒̃̐̍̒̅̉̃̓͊̆̌͛͐͌̒̿̈́̊͗̈́͐̒́̾͐̿͌̾͋̊͆̉́̋̉̆̊͆̐̿̋͒̊̒̀̀́́̍̎̇́̿̔͒̂̅̍͐̎̅̓̓̋̿͛͐̿͊̀͋̀̑̽̓͆̇̒͑͂͛̇́̒͗͌̂̃̃̏͑̌͐̌̎̇͌̿̀̆̋͑̾͑̑̊̆̇̍̐͗̅̈́̊͊̇͋̐̀̈́̂́͂͆̈́̔́̎̉̓̃̒́͊̾͗́̌̐́́̓̌́͑̒͑̋͊͒̈́̊̍͌̂̈́̓̉̅̓͗̉͑̒̈̉̽͗̎̓̈́̇̎̓̐̅̀͊͗̌̈́͒̓͒̌̀̊̈́̾̅́̾̌̓̈́̉͑̑̆̄́̈́̈́́̏̉̓̂̍͑͒͊̋̽͐̂̾͑̋̈͐͋͗͋̐̽͂̂͌̏͗͌̈́͗̉͂́̃̾̋͛̽̚̕̚̕͘̕͘̚̕̚͘̚͘̚̚͘͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅÁ̶̢̧̡̧̡̨̧̧̨̨̡̨̧̡̨̧̨̨̢̡̢̱̬̠͎̮̤͕͈͈̝̰̱̘̬̟̱̬̤̥͕̥͓̱̩̝͓̙̦̻̤̼̤̱͇͍̰̙̣̻̝̞̻̥̗̤̥̞̟̩͔̫̞̗̬̼̙̥̙̣̯̺̟̤̖̹͕͕͓͉͔̜̮̱̮̞̼̝̼̳̞̠͉̙̝͍̻̰̻̦̖̺͇̳͇̺̪͖̪̱̝̥̫̙̹̬̘͙̰͓͎̗͇͙̠͚̳̦̭̼̜̖̗̞̺̰͔̙̱̭̪͇̺̙̞̗͎̠̯̠̲͎̩̟͙͇̩̝̲͈̟̺̲͇̺͓̦̥̤̤̟̠̙͉̙̝̳̟̯̲̪͚͖̦̞̹͍̟̰͖̥̝͚̭̙̬̖̻̺͉̗̣̬̻̙̝͎̣̻͔̖̥̖͕͙͍͓̪͙͓̩̳̟̻̰͕̞̺͈̲̭͎͖͈̟͓̭̹͖͇̱̼͎͇͍̲̬̩̗̯̹̞͓͚̬͓̫̼̠̘̭̳̜͖̙̖̭͐̎̂̈͗̄̾̓̏͗̉̏̅̈́̅́̿͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͠͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅA̷̢̧̧̨̡̧̧̨̡̢̨̢̛̛̛͎̜̪̜͚͔͉͔͇̥̦͍̺̯̱̗̝͍̞͙̗͔̺̩͍̭̻̜̜̱̗̫̙̣̝̳̯͍̙̥̺̞͖͚̘͙͉̟̬͔̜̦̟̗̱͉̼͍͍̳̬̬͍͓͉̭͈̲͔̫̺̻̟̳͎͍̗͍̘̼̯̥͙̭͕̰͈͎̺̱̞̥͍͓̹̟͚̫̩͓͈̲̟͎̹̠̮͚̙̯̜̯̥͙͉̯̤͓͓̿̄̂̑͑́̑̆̍̿͆̾͒̆̂̐̓̍̓̋̓́̽̈́̔́̿̀̚͜͜͜͜͜͝ͅÁ̵̧̢̢̢̧̧̢̧̢̢̨̢̡̢̧̡̨̢̨̧̗͚̯̙̹̫̼͚̮͙̮̼̯̱̤͚̠̞̬͚͇̫̬̰̭̭̬̞̺͇͍̣͇̖̯͙̝̱͙̘̳͎̤̻͚̩͈̪̯̼̱̯̰̮͕̝̲͓͉̼͈̣̫̥̤̻̩̖̰͙̳͚̺̙̩̠̹̯͉̭̪͇̰̦̤̱̗͕͍̜̪̜͓͎̩̰̣̺̺̻̝̱͇͍͈͈̙͚̱̯̼͙̞̻̦̺̟̥̟̖̝͙̞͍͎͉̜̙̘̳̹̗̘̙̟̤̰̯̜̣̮͓̩̻͙͓̠̞̠͍̙̺̣̝͙̲͎̺̼͓̖͚̟̝̲̖͉͔͎̝̜̻̩̳̙͔̠͇̰͉̮̺͇̥͓̭̰̟̥̞̭̮͓̝̥̫̰̥͕̰̤̻̔͛̐̓̋̐̐͐͛̏̈́͐̄̅̈͊́̈́̈́̆̀͆̀̏̒͘͘͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝ͅͅͅͅͅĄ̵̡̡̡̨̢̨̡̧̨̨̨̧̨̧̨̡̧̢̢̧̨̢̢̢̡̢̢̨̢̢̛̛̛̛̛̛͕̞͔̤̭̜̝͉͚̗̘̠̺̰̘̝̤̺͇̭̝̗̤̤̹̭͔̘͉̬̥̺͖͔͕̻̗̜̥̙͇̻̩͙̪͇̩̠͉̗̝͔̯͍͕͕̗̟͖̞̻͈̙͕̤̞̭͈̮͉̻͉̩̖͚̭̠͔͚̰̘͍̞̥̭̰̖̞̝͉̦̰̹̣̳̰̦̠͖̖̫̱̘̖͔͍͚̱͚̗̠̳̖̻̬͙̟͍͙͈͇̪̩̻͕̱̹̹̮̗͈̬͈̫͔͓̠̤̪͓̩̠̯̭̟͕̣̦̗̺͙̰̲͍͔͚͓̺̮̤̻̰̭̙̻̫̰̫̝̣̳̙͚̗͙͉͍͖̪̯͈̬͍̝̥̠̜̺͕̥͉͚̲̖̳̮͓͙̼̝̠̥̝̟͎͕͍͈͙̤̩̦͕͖̪͍̹̳͈̣̰̲͚͕͔̫̙̯̗͇̘̪̲̣͈̼̯͉̪͈̘̊̃͊̿͗̑̍̇͆́͆̀͗̈́̏͐̇̅͐̅̑̂͌͋̐̾͐̊̏̇̌̅͌̓̆̆̽͌͊̄̈̋̉̍̿̒̒͐̿̉̒̓̌̍́́͊̋̈́̊̈́̍̓͑̿͑͗̂̈̿̓͐̎͆̑̓̔̄͛̒̄̾̐̊̏̍͂͋̓̐͂̄̄̅́̔̈̔̈́̄́̑̌͒̅̀̏̈̑̊̉̓̃̒̇̓͒̎͌͂̐̃̋̒͛͆̈́͗͆̀͑̋͂̉͊͒̎̈́͐̈́̓͂͋̐͛̉̊͂̇̽͑̌͆̏̓̓̄̂͐̏̒͛́̍̍͌̍̾̽̀͒̐̉̀̔̓͊̋̎̉̉́̈́̿̉͐̃̇̈̈́̈̆̀̄́̉̌͊̈́̂̌̓̈͂͛̀̓̀̓̔̏̈͗́̉͗̓̏͌̑̃̑͗̅̈̌̅̄̈̋̀̋̈́͐͒͐̑̓̆̌̐͗̈́̿͋̿̾͑̅̒̾̍̋͆͛͘̚̕̚͘̚̚̕̚̚̚̚̕̚͘͘̕̚̚͘̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͜͠͝͠͝͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͠͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̷̧̡̨̢̢̨̢̛̛̛̛̛̛͖̘̮̭͍̘͕̬̖̲̖̳̬͎͚̰͉̫͎̤̰̪̭͖̼̦͔̯̘̦̦̻̣̦̫̣̻͍̺̦̻̺̙̤͎̣̠̭͎̫͚̘̖̻̠̩̻̘͖̤̞͇̠̮̤̗̭̤̩̈́̓̏͌́̏́̀͗͛̋̀͂̐͐̋̅̓͑͆̓̾̾͋̔̎̆͆̀͂́̇̈͑͐̆͒̎̏͋̈̉́̂̏̿̍̈́͑̿̉͋͋̎͗̌́̈̐̀̈̂͗́̌̿̿̆͗̊̽͊̄͛̆̀̊̑͊̓͗͗͆̓̍̐̂̔̈́̋̽͌͊̓̏̎̅̑̀̅̽͗̍̆̈̅͐̀̊̂́͐̀̉̓́̆̔̈́̎̈̐̎̈̈́̾͛͋̽̎̾̍́̔͗̃̍͋͐͑̎̂̆͊̐͂̚̕̚͘̚̕̚̚̕̚͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͠ͅA̶̡̨̨̨̡̡̨̨̢̛̞̲̜̮̠͉̲̮̝̥̤̹͖̣̗̣̯̹̹͈͉̮͙̺̤̹͙̖̺͕̱̘̞̙͙͍͍̰̳̣̱̮̘̘̰̗̭̣̘̜̰̫̟̳̘̦̣̤̯͎̫̣͔̭̥͓̩̰̞̼̠̘̪͓͚̮͉̬̪͎̝̗̟̪̭̘͖̗̝̫̰͍̱̳̫͖͍̫̹̭̥̮̤̟̟͇͎̗̟͖̘̮̼̩̪̗͔̪̲̯̜̰͙̻͚͚͓̺͙̦͈͙̪̬͇̥̝͙̘͈͔̗͈͎̦̫̖͈̯͖̻̗̦̠̞̰̻̱͖̪̞̺͔̠̰͙̗͍͔̬̟͔̦̹̗̿̏̂̓̇̀́̈̌͒̂̏͛̉̎͂̏̂͆̀̇̒̉̿͂̍̑͊̎̍̓͂͗̔̈́̉́̈̏̋́̏̽͑͛̓͑̓̓͛̈́͒̓̈́̇̑̀̍͗̂͛̾͐̓͒̎͋̐̊̓̒̆͐̈́̈̄͐̑̓̋̈́̈͂̃̐͒̓͐̑̌̌̑̄̌̈́͊̽͂̽͂̀́̈́̈̈́̊̅͗̅̀̈́̅͆̀͗̂̑̑̾̒̈̈́̃̏͑́̒͂̑͌͋́͊͐̄̐̃̏̉̉͛̌̀̔͋̈́̐̀̔̓̐̊̌́͋̆͌̃̑͋́͆̉̿͑̑̉̀̿̀͂̅̀͑̀͂̓͗̌̈́̈̈̈́̃́̾̏̑͗̄̈́͋̊̐̉̒͂̕̕͘͘͘̚̕͘͘̚̕͘̕̕̕̕͜͜͝͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͠͝͠͠ͅͅͅͅͅA̷̧̧̨̢̡̡̡̧̨̡̛̛̛̛̛̹̳͔̬̳̰̬̤̼̥̥̞̦̲̺͕̺̼̠̹̜͚͙̥̹̯̙̭̟͇̩̬̩̰̤̳̗̝̜̙̱̲̘̙̠͇̖̟͙̯̹̹̦͙̳̦̱̼̠̼̞͉͖͖̜̖̼̣̗̲̤̙̼͎̬̪̠͖̗͖̜͇̯͚̬̬͈̯̜͎̫̥̺͔̣̗̪̰͖̩̪͓͚͎͚̦͍͕͍͕̣̜̹̹̫̹̱̹͔̞̥͇͇̞͔̘̥̺̲̳̟̼͖̥͉͙̘̤̝̓̅͋̉̿͆͆͆̇̓̐̀͗̓͗͌̀̓̓̒̾́̆̌̐͐͊͆̓̈̂̀̽̐̽̃̈́̋͗̋̈̓̌̓̏̈́̈̇̑̍̃̈́͗́͆̀͊̇̉̏̈́͛̓̌̏̈́̉̈́͌̀̋͋̄̈́̒̈́̌̃̈́̌̈̐̊̂̍̓́̈̔̔͂̀̀̈̈́̍̄͛͆͌̎̉͋̐̏̔͆̀̀̒͒̏̇̐͗͗͐̀͐̔̀́͗͐͊̇̽̒̑͛̿͒̐̾̈̒̍͆̐̌̋̆̇̅̇̓̌̉̿̈́̽͂͂́͋͊̐̋̀͒̉̃́̀̒̇͑́̈́̋͆̓̈́̒̇̔͂̋͛̄́͋͑̿͛̽̂̋̌͋̋̆͋̓͒̀̐́͊̈̾͂̿̈́̏͂̏̽͊̈́̽̅́̑̈͊̔̀͂̄͊͊͒͂͂̒̎̊̂̑̇̊͗̌̉͒̂̏̕̕̚̚̚̕̕͘͘̚̕̚̚͜͜͜͝͠͝͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͠͠͝͝͠͝͠ͅͅͅȂ̴̢̧̡̡̢̡̢̡̡̡̨̨̧̢̢̧̡̡̢̧̧̢̨̢̢̨̛͚̮͙̺̺͚͙̯̮̞̖̹͔͓͙̥͍͕͈̗̥͚̻̞̱͓͕͎̬̲̠̥̦̩͉̥̳̭̯͍̜͉̭̱̙͈̘̖̗͇̞͚̣̠̣̬̱̜̣͉̝̟͕̭̗͕͈̜͖͓̲̜͍̳͇̱̠̣̱̠͈͕̙̝̭̱͖̠̥͙̱̤͖̙̣̼̮͓͙͔͚̮̞̝͕̬̙͚̝͈̯̫͕̟͈̳̼͖̲̫̤̲̗̣̼͙̜͖̖̦͍̭̺̥͈̝͈̲̲̼̼̠͍̭͉͍̖̱̘̜̳̜̩̫̗̮̯̼̟͕͖̮̬̥̺̹͎̹̰̝̝͎̭͔̗̺̞̼͈͖͚͍͇̟̟̯̫̙̤̯͙̮͓͔̼̠̳͔͚͔̹͈̒̀͋̾̂͌͌̍̃͗̑̑͌̽̿̓̇̆̽͗̎̆̀̓̅̽̒̽͂̎̏͐̿̀͋̀̈́̅̓̽̏̆͒̔̅̂̓̊͗̓̆̾̋̎̎̀̔̀̈́̓̈́̈́̄̇̊̐͌̋̇̉͗̑͗̓͒͌͊͛̄̄̇͋͆͐̐̂͒̿̔̃̈́̏̇̄̊̈́̎̉̊͆̈́̔̈́̿̾̀̆͛̍͌̄̀̿̈́͗̓͒̅̋͗́̂̅̂́͒̈́̈́͊̂̿̀́̈́̌̈͋́̽̈́͗̑͑̇͗̈́̆̇̈́̐̄̒̾̓́͂͊͑͌͆̈́͐͂͛͘̕͘̕͘͘͘̕̚͘͘̕̕͜͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͠͠͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅͅĄ̵̧̡̛̛̛̛̛̤͉̥̺̟̤̠̲̫̲͈̖̬̮͓̜̟͍͈̫̻̲̘̘̝̙͈̗̠̝̪̼͌͋̇͊͑̓͐͋́̉̓̎̔̈́̈́̌̂̔̆̄͐̽̌̅̂̔̒̔̄͋̊̄̔̍͛͒́͛̊̅̀͂̓͌͂̿̄̇͑̃̎̀̾̋̊͂͊͗̌̈͌͋̎͌̅̿̊͂̓̂̊̍̎̊̈́̅̅̃̓̔̋̿͑̎̀̈́̄͛͂͒̓̓̄͐͋̓̃̑́͌̅̆̅̃̂̈̎̇͊̑̊̋̈́́̈́͌́̍́̏̈́̄͌̓̔̂̔̽͑̋̒͂̌͐̀̿̅̽̊̅̌̉̀̐̈́̓̄̈́͌̂͛͌͊̈́́̕̚̕͘̕̕͘̚̚̚͘͠͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͠͝Ŗ̶̡̧̧̧̢̨̛̛̛̛͈̲͔̻̼̳̺͚͈̭̬̫̜̠͚̟͔̟̣̫̻̼͍̝̫͓̥̘̼̝̺̲͖͔̯̠̟̦̗̠͕̯̮̦̬̫͎̩̫̠̳͔̜̠̩̖̳̳̠͇̻͔̗̝̘̗̦͇͍̣̞̮̱̰͕̻̻̤͇̮̹͙͔̝̖̭̩̪̪̫̜͚͔̰̝̼̗͈͍͕̬͗͒̑̎͊̉͒͗̈́̽̈̌̽͗͋͗̓̑͆́͋̀̓̐̈́̉̀͋͌̾̏͐̀͑̓͗͘͜͜͝͝͠͠ͅͅͅR̶̨̛̛̛̛̙̪̲̥͙̘̱͇̜̻̟͉̖͙̱̬͍͙̖̤̞̻͇̬̘͉͋͑͑̀̿̋͛̉͂͛̿̾́͛̽̄͂͋́̌̿̍͗͊̄͐̈́̐͛̀͆̆̄͐͒̀͆͒͑͛͂͛̓͋̔͂̑̇͋͒̍̓̏̈́̔̅̀̾̑͆̀̏̇̉̔̍͒̆̎̎̑̽͌͑̓͊͆̓̄̎̊̊̄̈̑̾̽̽̃͐̈́̈́̂̌̃̀̈́̊́́̿̊̓̍͋̿̀̄͗̌͛̉̓͗͋̊̋̇̄̔̏̀͊̎̃̾̌̑͗̅̃̽̀̀̔͗̽͆̂̉̈́̐̀̈̅̑̈̽̍͆̊̾͆̆̂͗͐̋̍̈̄̽͛̽̒̌͆́̒̓͗̆̓͂̊̈́̍͊̾͌̏͒̽̒̓̒̓̇̔͛̋́͒͗̇̆́̈́̄̓̊̂̐̍̀͑̾͒̑͑̏̿̔̾̒̾̆͒́̏̒̚̕̚͘̕̕̕̚͘̚͘̕̚͘̚͘͘̚͘͘̚͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͠͝͝ͅR̸̡̡̧̛̞̩͓̞̦͖̘̳͚̱̳̤̙̞̭̱̹̝͉̪̰͉̪̦͉̫̀̍̂̉͋͂̂̓̅̑̉͐̄̐̀̈́̎̽̽̋̈́̌́́̄̈́̈́̉̇̔̾̆͒͗̈́̀̑̄̍̈́́̿̅̌́͗̑̋̄̋͒͗͒̽̊̅̀̎̃̅͂̉̔͒̒̍͊̊̒͗̐̌͌̔̈͑͌́͌̎̂̊̽̂͗̍̃̂̑̓́͆̽̅̏̄̂̐͛͗̿̀͑̈́̅̂̿̋͆͐͐͌͗͌̃̚̕͘͘̕̚̕̚͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅͅR̸̡̨̢̨̡̢̨̡͉͉͚͉̯͚̺͔͇̘̜͙̺̦̲̺̘̖̞͙̣͍̫̤̥͚̼͈͉̠̖̟̞̖͖͚̫͔͚͓͇͙̰͉̟̺̯̩̻͍̝̤̳̭̱̹̬̯̼̹͇͓̲͕̯̠̮̝̯̩͖̘̣̪͇̳̿̃̋̀̓̈́͋̂͗̅͑̔̐͑̆͛̌̒͐̍̍̔̒͊͛̐̔̈̆͂̂́͌̉̂̅̐͌̏̅̕͘͜͠ͅͅṚ̷̡̧̛̛̛̖͇͔̰̟͚͈͕͉̘̥̘̞̫̜̙̥̘͔̘͕̫͎͇͇̠͍̻̰͖̜̲̅̎̈͋́̄͌͑̓͒̿͌̈́͐̓̅̔͆͂̎̈́͋̊̍͂̊̋́̎̐͑̇̒̆̽̈̍̐͌̑̀̅̅̇̀̓̓̈́̽́̔͛͗́̍͗́̊̍́̇̂͌̂͊͐̊̋͌̋̈͆͐̄̌̈́͂͋̆̉̑̾̔͛̑̏̆̏͂̏̇͆̄͛͑́̽̈́̓́̊̇̑͂̓͊͊̐̀̍̇͑̄͌̈́̏̎̅͛̂͆̾̉͗̚͘̕͘͘̕̕͜͜͜͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝R̷̡̢̢̡̧̛̛̛̛̛̞̟̘̯͕͕̩͕͙̯͎͈̖͖̺͕̭̱͚͓̹͔̖͉̠̱̫̰̗̗̫̫͈̤̗͇̳̩̭͍̼̱̜̼͉̩͚̂̃̆͐͑̉̑̅͌͊̊̑́̊̈̏̔͂̈͆́̈̿́̑̋̒̍͊̿̇̿̈́̌͐̀́͗̒̉̿̇̀̄̏̈̆̎̀̅̀̽̈́̀̃̅͊̅͆̉̾̋̉̓̍̍̄͊̓̔͆͆̇̇̒̌̉̂̿̄̂̀̀͐͐̓́̿̉̋̿͌̊̍̓̓̃̌͑̍́͗̀̈͑̍͐̿̋͊̋͛̈́̌̅̉͐̇́̓̽̆̑̌̏̈́̿͐̍͂́̅̀̈́̈́̆̓̀̓̆̆͛̈́̐͐̐̈́̃̄̆̽͒͗̐̚̚͘̚͘͘̚̕͘͘̚̚̚͘̚̚̚͜͝͠͝͝͝͝͝͝͠ͅͅŔ̶̢̨̢̨̡̨̡̧̧̡̨̧̨̢̧̧̨̛̛̛̛͈̯̜̣͖̼̥̠̹̲͈̯̬̖̪̭͔̺̣͉̩̭̯̞͔̪̗̼̼̙͉̪̖͍̰̠͎͎͎̰̩͇͓̰̪͚̥̩̖̝͇͔̳̮̝͕̘͕͕̦̳̦͉͔̫̻̰̝̳͖̫̺̪͇͈̩͖̭̘̩͉̜͔̣͕̺̙̣̼̰͚̘̠͙̫̗̲̖̭̺̫̼̲̱͇̞̺̺̖̱̖̟͖̯̤͎̪̳͔̦̹̞̬̳͍̭̳͔̯̖̠̖͉̱͍̜̗͍͚̟̬̹̩͇͉͓͍̮̯̥͕͍̹̫̭̭͎͈͉̝͌̏̇̈͌͗̽́́̔̾͆̍̅̽͗͗̈́̾̅̽͑̀̒̑̾̈́̂̋̓̎̑̐̐̓̉̅́́͒̓̓͂̄̈́̒́͋̋̎͐̉̒̈́͂͑̃̈́̾̌̌͊͗̐̉̆͊̅̈́͗̅͗̾̅̒̈́̀͗̿̿͒͋̍̍̍̍͆̅͋̿̏͂̿̔̆͂̿̕͘̚̚̚͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅR̵̢̢̡̧̢̨̨̧̡̢̢̧̧̧̧̡̢̧̢̢̡̡̡̧̡̢̡̨̨̨̨̡̢͓̻̪̰̻̤̬̞̝̜̙̞̝̘̗̮̫̭̣͖̮̰̱̥͚̩̞̹̺̖͉͉̜̮͕̳̪͇͚̩̜̯̰̪̪̞̮̭̭̦͇͙̮͔͓͕̗̰̱̺̠͇̮̲̤͇̰̹̝͕̝̣͍̜̜̮͎͖̳͎͎̪̲̮̳̝̰̲̺̼̳̙̗͕̪͚̥̤̦̜̳̞̹̰͙͉̪̭͔̦͈͙͍̖͚̰̭̫̟̭̫͓͚͔̠̘̱̤̖̠͔̠̩͍͍̺̰͙̟̰̳̻̠̗̩̟̭̺̜̦̪̥̬̞̹̟͔͔̱̬̥͍̬̞̰̳̙͖̗͎͓̥̰̬̖̘͚̦̙̝͚͙̟̩̱̟̱̟̗̙̜̠̼͉̗̹͇̱̺̝͍̲͎̭̘̤̬̠̖̗̻̞̦̤͙̩̯̦̮͚̫̤͍͇̼̩̭̼͔͍̺̤̖͒͜͜͜͜ͅͅͅͅͅͅͅK̵̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̛̠̘̞͕̝͖͛̇̄̆͌͐̈́̀̓̈͆̉̌͂͒̀̑̄͋͂̊̈̏̐͐̆͂̏͗́̈́̅͑́̉́̓̌̉̓́̋́͐́͐́̔͋͑͊̀̂̄͒͛͌̇̉͒̀̄̈́̔͋̐̈́̾̈̑̅̀͆́̀͊̂̀̑̊̋͊͛̌̏̈͌̐̊͐̋͋̍̈́̃̊̌͂̉̀͂͗̒́̔̀̔̈̃́̌̉̔̀̍̇̏̀͂̉̀̉̌̍̏͑͌͌͐̄̿̅̒̀̈́̓̓̐̈́̓̈͂̂͋̽̊͊͐͒̃̐̾̏̂̋̔̑̓̽̔̿̊͊̋̾̐̓͊̆͘͘̕̕͘͘̚̕͘̚̚̕̚͘̚̚͝͠͝͝͝͠͝͝͠͝͠K̵̨̡̨̢̧̡̛̛̛̛̛̛͉͍̟̩̹̫̳̳͙͕̝͔̣̥̼͕͖̝̰͚̱͚͉͉̳͙͙̞͍̬͈͉͚͉̟̦̦̥̮̟̮̮̲̏̃̉̅̎̔̽͊̃͂͆̍͗̇̎̇̿̈̐̍̿̓̑̓͌͒̾̀̔̔̃͌͑̐̿̀͒͒͂̈́̎͒̂̆͑̔̂͋̽͋̔͂̾͑͌̀̈́̌̎̇̽̅̒̄̅̎̏̒̈́̇͌̔́̾̾̽́̂͋͂̌̇̈̑͐̾̈́̽̂̏̌͌̾̂̒̆̐͌͒̉̋̀͒̾̈́̏́̀͑͌̀̑̒͑̀̐̓̒̈́̔̉́̆̿̽̈́́̏̅̈̔͊̔̊̑͗̓͗͑̃͋̿̈̉͊̈́̈́̎̋̐͊̇̌͊͊̈́̒͗̾̉̈́̽͋͐̀͆͗̈́͐̔̓͋͆̂̃̌̏͆̌̊͂͗̔̾̂͋̐̅̈́̓́̈́͑̀̾͗̅͋̾͒͗̐̃̆̒̂̒̈̈́̏̀̆̈̾̈̇͌̄͋́̌̔̑͂̚̚̚͘̕̕̕͘̕̚̚͜͜͝͠͠͠͝͠͠͝͝͝͝͝͝ͅ
I- I think I can take it from here!
I mean, you didn’t even mention the mixer icon
...with that weird-looking lopsided thing beside it!
But that’s just scratching the surface.
Come with me!
THERE’S A LOT MORE JANK IN THE SEA!
WHEE
W͠HE̷̶̕E̛È́ÈÈ
W̴̷̡͜͜H̨͢È̸͘E̸̛̕͠E̵͟͝E̴͟͟E̶҉̷͠E̕͢͟É̀E͜͢҉̧͡Ȩ̴̀Ę͟͏Ȩ̵
W̢ͭ͌͒́ͪͨ̂̔̈҉̙̯̗̯̰ͅH͈̗̱̙̥ͯ̿ͦͬ̚E̞̭͇̝ͮ͊̀͗͢͠Ȩ̡̝͔̥͍̳͉̱͇ͤ̀͌͗̀Ȩ͚̞̻̬̭̀̅͟Ḝ̴͓̝̹͚̖͇̈́͗̿̄̕E̷͇̙ͦͪͪͭ̈́͗ͥE̓ͥ͏̜̳͟͝ͅĒ̆ͫͪ҉͖̗̗͔̺̞̘E̐̒̒̽̉ͩͧ҉̣͓̮͢E̗͉̫̘̎ͮ̈͜͞É̗̦̺̤͚̀̐̈́ͯ̂̍E̹̲̜̻͇͋ͩE̶̴͈̱̥̯̹̖̮ͧͪḘ̣̺̪̦̘̽́͑͗̀̾͢ͅE͌͑̆̓̉҉̻̥̰͉̜Ė̝̂̆̐̋͜Ė҉̼̗̮̱͡ͅE̘͇̝̬̦̬̟̋͊͝ͅE̮͚̦̟͂̏̾Ȩ̫̺͂̑͜E̟̯̞̫̻̤͛ͭͣ͊́Ȩ̴̺̯̞̽ͥ͡E̡̺͕̦̘̯͕̹̞̝ͨͥͮ́͟͡E̷͙̞̺͙ͤ̈́͘
Wͫ͒͛̃҉̧̛̱̻̜̼͖͕Ḩ̮͍̱͙̜͇̤͎̰͛̑ͧ͗̾̎̎ͦͫ͜͠Ë́͗̈́̆͆҉͎͟Ẹ̳͑̌ͣ͋@̨̺̯̤͓̬̱͚̱͎͗ͪ̈́̌̉ͬ͑E͉̰̰͙͔̗ͦ̌͋̇ͬ̆ͧ͢͢È̝̤̙̗̗̺̺̚͞E̷͔͚̭͎ͭ̈́̃̂͐͒,̹͎̠̭ͭ̎́I̻͕̬̼̜̓;̷̨̦͍͓̼̑ͣͤ͋͂̑ͣ͗͢'̸̶̟̺̰͎͖͎̝̞̖ͯ̆͐ͮͣ/͋̔ͩ̓ͧ͊̋̌҉̢̹̗̠̬̙̩͙̬̲͘Ȇͫ͏̝̮̬͎E̥̣̤̯͚̪̮̝̬ͦ͝ ͨͤ̾͊̿̀҉̟̬̯̝E̛̛̯͖̭͓̥̰͙͒̆͐͡E͇̩͎̬͈̗͇̱ͣ̅̈ͮͣͧ̾̕E͙͍̝͕̫̼̒͛ͤͯͅ*̵ͭ̀҉̗̥̹(̼̮̭̳̰̖͓ͯ̑͊͛ͨ-̯̬̘̘͎̟̩̓͗͌̇̀̏̿̈(̟̣̘̆ͦ͒̏ͫ̋̈́ͩ́(͙̺̭̤̓̀͛͞Ẻ̘̹͔̤͙̟̎ͦ̄̎̉̐͛È̓̀̚҉͏̝̻̘͉̫̭Ę̠͓͈͇̺̘̉͗̆̕E̷͓̤̱̺͇͓̬̮ͤ̓ͥ̏ͫ͜Ê̞̯̺͖̤̥̩͐͂̎̑̎͝/̰͙̫͚͈͆/̷̛̮͉̞̥́̌̈́̏̚͡uͩ͏̸̛͔w̞̖̫͓̙̭͊ͤͩͥ̄͋͌ͣ͡ͅuͩ̏͊̕͏̻͙̗̤̀E̎ͯ͏͙̠͇͈̺͚̗̀E̓̈̈́ͫ̚҉̘̞͉̼͡E̢̝̦̰̫͚̹̝̎͑͆͆̒̅ͥ͆͡ͅ[̶̶̨͉͈̝̮̩̘̆ͭ̿ͯͪ[ͦͪ̽̓̓̏͝͏̫̻̹+̨̡͙̺̗̝̼̏̎ͨ͌ͨ̒E̸͆ͭ̈́̑̈́̔̏̉̊͡͏̣̞E̷̗͍̼̙͓ͯ̓̐̅͞E̡̧̖͓̤̹͚̮̯̫ͦ̍̆͛͂̅̽ͦ
Here at Dorico,
...we’ve made sure that our notation
system has the best of everything!
It’s powerful!
It’s advanced!
But it’s also covered in
JAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAANNNNK!
These durations are great.
You click on them and add them to the score.
And sometimes, they let you
click on as many as you want!
Oh wow!
Now I have ALL the notes!
Want to change this hairpin so it looks like this?
Well, just go down here,
...and turn on the switch that enables
the button that lets you do that.
Why does a button require a switch?
Well, it’s because...
Hold on a second...
Uh...
It didn’t change?
Hmm...
Oh, I see!
You forgot to tick the tickbox.
The tickbox enables the switch
...and the switch enables the button!
She swallowed the bird to catch the spider,
...she swallowed the spider to catch the fly.
I don’t know why she swallowed a fly.
Perhaps she has a
JANKY
BRAIN!
Say you want to turn off these split stems?
Just follow these three steps!
Turn on the switch that allows you to tick the tickbox.
Yeah, that again!
Tick the tickbox and watch nothing happen.
Untick the tickbox,
...which also does nothing!
Wanna edit THIS text?
N- No.
That's not advanced!
To do that,
...you have to go to your 'Piano' player,
...and roll down the thing,
...intuit that if you roll over this text,
...an arrow is gonna appear at the end of it.
Then click on the arrow to get a menu
that contains an option to edit the name!
Now this is what I call 'Advanced'!
Two sets of text controls with the
instrument names aligned to the right
FOR MAXIMUM VISIBILITY!
WHEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
That’s beautiful!
Entering Grace notes is easy!
I’ll show you how in three easy steps.
Press the 'Grace Note' button
and then select your duration.
Doing this turns off the 'Grace Note' button.
Press the 'Grace Note' button again.
Okay. Now they're both on.
So, let’s enter some notes,
...which you’ll observe are wrong.
Doing this turns off the 'Grace Note' button.
Just press the 'Grace Note' button a third time,
...and you can enter your grace notes.
There we go!
Now you have your grace notes.
And the grace note button has turned off again.
Ｌｏｖｅ ｔｈａｔ Ｊａｎｋ！
Let’s select this pizzicato marking!
And now we have a hairpin too for free!
Hairpins and pizzicato,
together at last!
Ah, that shouldn’t have happened.
Oh, I see your problem.
You didn’t check the tickbox on your Bluetack!
Let’s set the Steinberg Hub to
Want to tell the player to switch
to a different instrument?
Nothing here to do that.
Okay,
...I guess it must be in that area
dedicated to instruments and players?
No?
Okay.
Where do you think I should go to
tell the player to switch instruments?
What was that?
Down here,
...under this dropdown called
I- I- Is that really called 'Galley View'?
"Rig the tackles and breeches, lads!"
"She’s rounding to!"
"Man the fore-topsail and send the gunner aft!"
"Aye Aye Captain!"
Deleting bars is
eeeeeaaaaasy!
Just click on this grey rectangle
and select the 'Delete' button.
Want to delete multiple bars?
No!
You get nothing!
Wow, that tickbox switch is
really up there with the greats.
It’s up there with
Imagine if we combined all three together.
Oh, it’s more than just a dialog.
It’s a 'jankalog'!
Look, I even janked it onto a T-shirt for you to buy!
The link is in the description!
Seriously, this actually exists.
You miserable, janky, hack fraud!
Dorico may be advanced,
...but it’s also a little laggy!
Drag that octave marking over here!
Come on!
Come on, you can do it!
Come on.
Oh, how much longer...
Oh
Hurray!
Let’s take a moment to appreciate
this design innovation,
..with its ability to block the score,
...and its wonderfully chosen colour:
Light grey on white.
If you’re wondering how accessible
this is for people with poor eyesight,
...well...
The standard minimum contrast ratio is...
Now, if we test this colour...
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
That's...
That's, like, literally the worst accessibility
fail I’ve ever seen in my entire life!
That's-
That's too much-
That's too much jank.
Uh, y- you know...
If you open Dorico up on a Mac,
...it automatically sets your volume
to the maximum setting.
It really goes well with Dorico Beep.
Oh, j- jesus...
Oh, no...
I can't take this much jank!
What is-
What’s happening to me!?
Oh.
Now I am Dorico.
W- What are you doing?
Wh- What are you doing?
No.
That is not advanced.
No!
That is not advanced!
No! I won’t let you do that!
It will not be advanced!
And I am the god of advancement!
You must be advanced!
Do as I say!
YOU MUST BE ADVANCED!
Y̶O̶U̷ ̷M̷U̴S̴T̷ ̴B̷E̶ ̵A̴D̶V̷A̴N̴C̷E̵D̵!̵
Y̵̡̨̨̡̡͉̜̝͍͖̜̝͚̟̱̖̱̻̪̥̩̤̭̩͔̮̹͎̮͎̜̝̆̄͂͌̾͌͂͆̐̈́̃̂͐̈́̽͗͒̽͆͐̊̕̚̚͝ ̵̷̢̡̢̡̢̛̭̳̦͖̥͓͙̝̘̣͍̝̩̻͇͚̬͕̻̥̬͉̺̜͚͍̯͔͍̈̂̿̾̃̇̏̓̒̈̅̉́̉̀͊͒̈̈̅́̾̓͑̈́̉̈̓̒̊͑͂̕̕̕̚̕͢͜͠͝͠͝͝ͅǪ̴̹͖̙̩̯̦̗̗̼̗̑̆͋̔͗͌̉͂̽̇̔̄̄͒̾͐̌̈́̈́́͑̊̍̏͆̓̓͛͑͘ͅ ̷̛̝͓͇̟̺̬̼͇̲̮̟̖̳͇̌̇̑̒̓̇̈̆̾͐̈͊̽͆̏̎̎̍̌̔͛̊̔́̕̚͜͠͝ͅ҉̴̨̡̡̥̙͖͓̗͓̯̫͓͕͍͉̺͉̥̦͈͚̫͖̞̹͈̜̼͚͍̾͂̌̔̅͛̉͗̀̄̒͜͝͝Ư̸̝͖͓͚̻̙̞̄͗͋̈́́͗̿̀̈́̆̅́̈̌̋̊̓̋̊͘͝͠͝͠͝͠͝͠ ̵̧̛̛̭̤̺̗̻̰̺̮̪̹̖̘̞̤̘̯̌͑̓̂̒̈́̀̋̒̀͊̅̄̾̂̒̌͋̈́̎̌̋͘͜͜͠͝͝͠ͅ҉̵̡̧̱̣̲̬̥̦̘̪̖͓̘̻̹̖͈̭̤̻̱͓̭͕̦͇̔͗͛̂͂̿̈́̌́̈́͆͂͋͐͜͠ ̸̶̡̧̨̛̱̖̠̞͎̰̯̝͖̹̂̒̈́͗͛̈́͌̽̒͗̇͢͜͠ͅ ̷̧̧̨͙̦̖̼̳̬̩̭͑̀̎̈́͋̐̒̒M̶̢̧̢̡̩̣̫̬̰̩̤̭͔̠̻͇̖̟̣͇̘̘̪̹͉̀͛̆́̎̂ͅͅ ̴̨̳͇͍̼̱̳̭̜͚̠͔̻̗̥̖̬͇̗̣̦̦̹̲̭̭̣͇̺̯̗̾̋̄̍͌̄́͌͌͛̌͊͌͑͐͗̂̀̉̀̔͋̕͠͝Ù̴̺̝͚̥̜̮͚͙̟̦̹̳͖͖̠͕̞̱̘̙̝̈̐̕͠ ̶̧̻̮̝͉̹̲̰̞͚̥̮̭̥̗̫̣̯̞̟͎̪͎̜̑̎̉̐̀̍̀̾͊̊̇̕͘͜͝ͅS̸̢̧̱̰͓̟̱͔̭͈̫̖̤̘̤͑͛̓̽̑͜ͅ ̵̢̟͍̫͓̬̦͇̫͙̮́̅̊̇̈́́ͅŢ̸̳̲̦̫̜̖͙̯͕͕̦̠̮̖͔̠͔̜͚̩͔̀̋͛̋̓̉̀͑̋̿͑̈́͗́̈́̋̆̒̄̚̚͝ ̸̰͉̲̹͕̣̲̅̅́ ̷̤̬̐̔͛̊̍̏̄͛͆̎̿̾̅̔͊͂͒̕ ̸̨̬̦̖͇̫̭̠͉̯̖͓̘̗̥͕̥̘̯̭͖̞̐̈̔̅̐̄̾̀͛̄́̃̿͌̈́̄̾͐̑̂̽͘̚͜͝͠͠B̸̙̆̔͗̿̇̉͐̆̑̃̏̎̊͌̿̔͗͊́̆͗̚̚͠͝ ̵̢̨̰͔̻͚̱̝͉͇̌̎̆̉͐͑̎̃͐̓̔̅̎Ḝ̸̴͇͚̣̥͎̰̤̜̯̺̟̽̾̐́̄͛͑͗̽̎̆̍̿̇̽́͑̅͛͆͋̍͘̕̚͢ͅͅ ̸̝̥͙̭̗̙̹͓̼̺̩̯̹͔̦̳̞̯̟̻͎͓̬͉̘̜́̑̏̑̈́̌̏̋̇͘ ̵̧̨̧̧̡̨̛̛̳͔͓͇̭͎̘̭͇͕͇͍͈̼̫̣͎̮͕̽̑͒̐̊͋̄̒̋̐͊̆͆̇̎̿̅͆̈́͒̀͘̚͘͜͝͠ͅͅ ̴̢̨̨̨̡̖̝̟̻͎̪͉̭͔̟̥͖̱̘̤̗̞͉̙̯͎͂̒̈́̈́̀̋͐͛̈͛̔̿͑̌͒͐͜͝ͅͅȂ̴̧̨̡͔̥͙͙̖͍̦̥̬̣̳̼̖̭͈̮̭̙̦̜̬̻̺̾̊͑̚͝͠ͅ ̶̛̼̯̭͚͍͎̠̺̬͙̮̗͙̲̒͛̑̏̐͒̂̓̈́̈̔̆̊̊̑̑̿̋̀͗̄̀́̂̃̚̚͠͝ͅḐ̷͉̰̦̭̭̭̱̟̗̰̮͈͚͆́̄̈́̇̆̎͋͘͜͝ͅ ̸̢̡̨̨̡̛͈͔̰̤̠͓̝͇̘͔͖͖̦͙̖͙̮͈̗̠̥̞̠͒́͛͑̾͋̾̀̿͘͝V̵̧̧̛̗̺̲̘̦̲̳̝̪̗̳̮͕̻͍͎̥͚̩̰͇̂̓̑̄̔͑͒̀̉́͋́̂̀͌͋͐̀͠͠ ̶̢̢̧̛͇͉̤͇͍̳̲̜̥̬͓̥̺̼̝͇͚͔̟͓͉̭̞̻̮̣̼͒̒̂̈́͆͒̌̇̂͋̆̆̈́̈́͐͜͝ͅÂ̸̧̨̢̤̰̯͉͍̜̦͕̲̣̬̦͈̦̜͈͔̼͌̐̅̍̕ͅ ̵̨̜̺̻̝̥̻̬̺̳̜̞̺̞͔͓̭̟̦̖̣͍̠̮̠͕͙͍͔͑͊̂́͌̽̊̒͐̈̂̿̆̕ͅN̶̛̹̤̳͖̥̖̮̟̥̞͈̠̰̗̺̹̑̀́̀͊̽̋̌̃̇̓́̌̆̄̋̒̈́̇̚͝͠͝͠ͅͅ ̵̡͕̠̦̺̪̝̳͓͚̜͕̗̖̥̘̪̯̫̝̯̪̲̼͇̰̼͌̆̿̂͗̈́͜͜͜͝͝͝͝Ć̵̠̣̫͉̰̤̠̻͔̯ ̵̢̧̭͔̮̬͉͖̱̹̪̟̮̞̘̙̱̥͍̞͂̊̈̈́͗̈́͋́͗̋͆͜͝E̶͉̦̳̰͍̤̻͕̟̪̩͉͔̤͛̎̎̃̈̔̾͛̔̄͂̈́̃̽̇͒͒͌̑̇̽̀͂̏͌̈́̕͠͝͝͝ ̴̨̢̢̧̜̠͇̱͓̩̭̣̦͖͑͗̎̀̍͐ͅ҉̶̧̢̢̡̺͕̥̩̰͕͙̻̭̞͙̦̥̻̺͗̈́͑̒̂̂͆͒̽̎̃͗̽́̓̑͛̑̂̒̈́̇̕͝͝͠ͅ ̴̧̛̛͕̼̝̩̠̥͕͈̪͓̼̥͔̥̳͓̟̤̯̯̰̰̻̫̜̬͍͍̗̀͌̐̾̑̂͐̇͒͌̏̓͒̊̽͛͛̌̓͑́̂̇̃̑̈́̋̏͌̓ͅ҉̸̥̣̯̰̠̙̱̓́͐͊́̍̏̍͋͂D̷̨̢̧̡̛̩͇̺̙̗̺͇͖̙͖̦̗̪̬̯̬̄̐̍̀̓́̿̔͌͗͐̽́͜͜҉̴̢̢̛̮̹̹̘̖̗̉͑̑͌́̾̊͛̉̐̏͑̈́͒̂́͆̃̀͐̈̅̌̐̅̿̄͘͝ ̶̧̢̻̞̙͙̦̙̫̥̫̠̠͍̞̖͔̭̃̆͆̚͝͝ͅ!̸̷̨̧̨̨̛̛͓͖̙̲͎͙̣̖̠̟̱̘͉͎̩̝̠̥̜̺̜͇͉̺̟͙̰̹͎̼͈͍̼̠̞͚͐̀̒̄̓͆͑͋͂͛̊̈́̌̌̐͗̈́͑͗̃̓̓̈́̌͘̚̕͢͝͝ͅͅ
Y̵̡̢̡̡̢̡̢̥͈͙̥̼̭̫͎̝̘͎̭̪͉̬̬̣̗̠̗̲͕̺͉̫͕͚͈̼̞͕͔̹̺̅͜͜ͅͅͅ ̶̧̢̨̨̡̨̧̨̢̨̛͕̜̼̗̻͉̳̺̭̗͍̞͖͍̳͎͇͖̹͉͓̟̣̼̟̤͕̖̫͚͖̦̟͚̰͇̖͍̯̩̟̯͓̱̞̞̲̜͇̠̤̬̫͕̭̆́̀̄̓̅̿̔̍͑̐̔̉͒͐͛̾̈́͗̒̓̋̎͛̓̃͋͑͐̎̐̽͌̉̽̒̅́̇͐̋̏͊́́͊͂̈́̅͋̒͒̈́͂͋̄̏̒̾̾̈́̐̃͂̕͘̕͘̕̚͘͜͝͝͝ͅͅ ̵̛͕͔̆̓̏̆͌̍̐͋̒͊̀̌̈́̽̂͂͑̌̒͐͐͊̎̅͊͐̀̽͛̾͋̋́͌̈́̎̈́̂̈̄̊̾̃̄̿́̏͗͐̂̿̇͛͂̏̎̎͘̕͘͘͠͝͝͝͝͠͠ ̶̴̧̢̢̡̧̨̧̛͙̣͖̮̠̯̣̤̗̲̘̪̱̬̦͚̖̦͓͙̝̯̮̟̗̰͍͓͍͚̰͍̜̗̻̭̯͔͉̫̪͇̹̳̞̥̜̤̦̱͚̗̫͎̊̿͊͌̉͒͗͂̊̃̉̃͋͊̍̋̉̉͒͑͌̅̀̃͒̉̒͑͗̉͒͐̄́̔̽́̀̒̃͊̀̇͑̿̈́́̒̏̊̈́̽͋͊̃̔̑̊͂̓̌̔̌̌̉̓̽̓͐͛͌̿̈́̔̎̈́̈̏͛̓̈́͒̄̔̐̃̈́̉̈́̄͌͌̏́̃̾̑̓̂̓͆̽̓͑̑̈́̐̚͘̕͘̕̚̚̕͢͜͝͝Ǫ̴̴̢̡̡̢̨̨̨̢̡̢̨̛̛̖̤̻̭̟̹̟̟̩͎͙̝̞̩̗̠͙̣̟͎͙̹͉̩͎̥͉̳̱̮̘̩͖͈̹̲̠̲͕͚̭̹͙̼͚̪͈̠̭͙͔͈̙̘̘̜͉͙̝͎̟͖̥͈̗̦̠͕̯̼͍͈͈͎̱͍̞̬̩̺̯̞͈̙͚̜̺͎̤͚̏͑͗̀̈́̇̃͆̇̆̂̎̆̃͐̓̀͆̍́̇̈́͑̌̋̒͌̓̄͊̍͐̿̒͗͛̄̓͐͆͆́̃͂̍͑͂̋͂̏̈́͋͌̏̐͊̉́͂̀́̈̇́̌̔̐̃̒̄̈̀̄̓̀͗̍͋̄̾̋̋̍̓̊͋͐̑̐͊͋̒͒̐̿͛͌̀̽͊̃̄̿̈̿̑̇͆̊̎͊̎̈̋̒̌̾̈́̈͋̋͑͛̅̓̕̕̕̕̚͢͝͝͝͠͝͝͝͠ͅͅ҉̴̨̧̨̛̟̩̻̜̠͉͚͓̺͈̭͓̠̝̝͓̥͍͍̱̮̣̠̠̱̜̥͈̞͓̗͎̩̤̞̞͇͓̤̻̰̼̳̘̥͍̰̻̦̹̗̱͓̘̪̃̽̊̒̀̃̋̄̊̍̽̀̽̒̈́͒̊̏̉̐̍̈́̍̽͑͂̾́̐̀̅̔́̀͌̌̈͋̊̓̾̍̈́̇̕̕͜͜͝͝͝͝ͅͅ ̸̡̡̛̩̝̰͖̪͕̗̤͈̝̰̓̂͑͒͗͐̀̔̄̄͐̏͂̉͐́̋̇̅̔͊͑̂̃̓́͌͒̾̽̆́̑͐̑̕͜͝͠ ̷̢̨̧̨̡̧̱̯͉̟̺̦͕͈̙̮̫̻̻̦͔̪͎͎͓̜͙̣͕̳̼̝͉̝̘̭̲̻̳̞̪̦̯͎͎͕̪͚͚̪̺̳̬͉̦͖̱̦̳̩̪͚̞̮̺͓͓͖̰̳̬̟͎̘͉̍͐̌́̔̂͗̽͒̇̈́̿̂̀̉͐͂͗͊͂̈́͌͗̍̑̊́̿͑͒̂͗͆͒̓̎͗̀͒͛̾̎̓̓͆̍̏̃́̈̊̆͂̽̓̍̌͐̍͒́̅͛̀̽̒̀͛̂͘͜͜͜͠Ư̴̧̧̢̢̨̛̦̘̤̗͓̳̯̬̤̩͎̜̰͈̹̼̹̘̭̼̺̗͎̦̗̩̼̙̟̦͚͉͍͈͚͍͈̻͖͔̫͙̺̥̞̺͖͓̼̟̹͖͍̮͚̥̖̱̝̥̋̿̋̂̏͌̀̇̎̔̈́́̈́͌̄̍̀̆̉͂̈́͌̏͒̿͛̐̈́̀̇́͐̄͌͌̃̎͐̾̇͗̇̍̔̿̔̀̀̓̊͊͐͊̄̆̚̕̚͜͜͠͝͝͠͝͝ ̶̡̡̢̧̛̖̤̟̭͎̬̬̰͖̩͕̗̘̠̼̻̖̠͎̞̰̣̳̞̜̗͍̘̟̙̘͔̤̘̤̣͍̺̣͈͖̹̗͎̠̳͇̫͓̝̫̼̬͓͉̥͍̤̪̞̯͑͒̈́̑́̅̍̔͗̇̅̽̌̑̈͗̂̿͗́́̃͗̂̽̉͋͋ͅ ̴̛̠͓̜̟̱̼͈̮͙͈͎̥̹̝͑̓̈́̏̍̂͌̽͛̋̂̌́̅̆͆͐̅͠ ̸̡̡̨̧̡̧̛̘̪̞̻̗̺̩̯͔̻̭͚̪̫̜̬̻̮̯̞̦̪͕͈̙̥̣̩̰͉̼̬̲̘̈̆̃̐̀̂̐̓́̏̂̉̃͗̒̾̓̒̐̀̈́̄̑͒͐̿́̆̾́̓͊̂͗̏͗̑̽̔͌̓̓̂͊̇̋̇́̋͛̏̑́̿̏͌̓̑̈́̊̔͆̆̚͘̚̚̚͘̚̚͝͠ͅ ̴̡̡̢̨̨̜̣̙͖͈̫̯̯͉̪͖̖̟͍̗̪͓̦̜̓̋̓̈́̍͆̐̅̃̇̊̑͑͆̾͂̓̏́̒͌̌̆̈́̆̆̕̚͘͜͠͠͝ͅ ̸̨̨̨̡̡̧̛̝̟̱̰̟̠̺̮̞̯̟̖̺̻̜̳̹͔̙̰͔͙̤̻̹͕̱̟̭̜͉̣̂̑͐̓͋̈́̾̇̃́̀̆̽͆̃̓̑́̉̄̐̔̅̂̂̀̈́̍͑͋̈̆̈́͒́̑̎̃̅͐͂̑͒̂̄̍͐͊̉͘͘̚̚̚͘̚͜͝͝͝͠M̵̛̛̛̱͉͖̰̙̻̠͍̖̳̣̗̼̺̭̳̳͉͙͇̮̹͕̼͚̩̟̙͕̹̙̖͈̰̜̙͚̝͕͙͎͓̭̭̠̼͓̥̗̗͕̜͚̱̟̝̗͚̙̤͙͓̣͍̙̒̿̌̽̐̽̌̽̐̏̈́̅̐͂̂̄̓̄̾̉͑̃̀͋́͂̐̈̽̑̆̀́̾̃̈́̊͐̆̿̏̎̎̽̄͘̕͘͜͠͠͠͝ ̴̨̧̧̛͔̥̬͖͇̙͈̠͖̺̰̱̗͇͎̲̰̼͚̤͇͚͍̭̠́̀͊̅͋̋̒͗̆̎̇̆̇̈͐͑̅͋̆͐͆̑̿̽̑̈̾̆̈́̌̆͐͆̒̾̄͋͗̈́͊̏̍̎̕͘̚̚͜͝͠ͅ ̷̢̢̨̢̡̨̮̠̼̣̻̩̬͍̜̣̝̯̜̗͙̼̥̳̠͍̤̩̪͉̠̠̗͈͖̰̭͙̰̖͈̩̩͇̦̫͙̩͎̟̞͖̺̭̗̘̹͈̙̤̠͙̗̭̙͔̲̹̱͕̻͚̙̮̝̟͙͈̓̆͑̇̋̐̈́̔̏̏̎̍̈́͛̉̓͒̀̔͒̑̅̈́̄̋͂̌̑͛̀͆̅̏̾̊̔̚̕̚̕̕̕͜͜͜͜͜͝͝͠Ü̵̢̡̧̨̡̡̖̦̰̫̘͓̦̼̯̞̝͖̖̹̼̳͕̪̼͍͖̗̟̞̖̲̻̲̹̙͚̘̪͈̻͈̬̞̜͇͉̪̂́́́̎̾͆̈́̾̇͆̈́̊͐͊̔͑̂̍́́̿͌̔̽͑͌̉̎́̉̈́̈́̈́̔̓͑̌̋͌̆̀̐̈́̌̽̒̀̅̔͂̐̌̋̐̏̆͊͘͜͝͝͝͠ͅͅͅ ̶̧̨̡̡̡̡̡̮̮̟̤̬̩̩̭̭̪̼̱̪̬̰͙̺͉̯̜̣͕̞̺̯͍͚̝̰̺̮̘̪̼̘͓̠̟̝̣̖͛̊͊̓̀̃́͆̚̚ ̵̢̢̢̨̧̡͖̜͕̲̺̳̳͓̫͓̫̟̙̞̲͈̰͕̹̣̩̩͇̼̣̫̻̠̺̜̬̬̼̪̖̥̺͎̖̙̯͔̱̙͖̝̝͊͑͜ͅS̵̡̡̡̢̧̡̖̱̪̤͚͚͈̭͕͍̥̜̱͎̱̲͚̻̼̺̫̬̙͈̺͉̟̲̱̖͚̻̠̟̦̲̼̬̖͌̐̍̄̊̐̒̎̽͐͆͛̑͐̑̒͗͂̆͌͆͜͝͝͝ͅ ̴̛̫̜͙͒̉̄͗́͋͂͊̍͌͒̌̄̄͘ ̴̡̨̨͖̞̪̫̩̪͉̫͖̩̝͕̜̣̼̼̻̭̱͎̫̗̟͖͚͙͎̰̬̯̌͗̓̐̓̀͐̋́͒̊̍̒̐͑̈́̿̒̍̎̽̔̓͑̎̊̎̉́̇͘͘͝ͅͅT̴̡̨̛̞̯̠̟̤̪̺̺̗̤͉̙͍͙͚̖̖̖̻̲͓̘͇̳̳̲̟̘̠͚̰̘̊͌͆͋̋́̿͂̀̃̑͂̂̆̾͑̔̎͑́̃̒̈́͌͗̽̃͋͒͂̓̂̄̾̈́̈́̿̀̐̿̀͂̅̿͒̓̈́̀͘͘̚͜͝͠͝͠͠͠҉̷͕̬̩̣̱̤̪̝̟͓̯̱̻̞͖̜̙͕̘͙̹̥̼͍̙̗̄̔͗̊͌͗̃̾̎͆͂̑͂̈́͝͝͝ͅͅ ̸̢̡̧̢̮͚̬͓̩̪̭̟̤̰͚̭̞̻̗̲̗̙͈̯̭̮̖̪̝̙͔̰̬̟̇͑͒̌̓̊͆̾̎̎͌͒͊͌͋́̈́̒͛̇̃̍͂̈́̽̊̐̕̚͜͠͠ͅ ̵̨̢̨̢̨̧̡̧̧̢̧̢̢̨̛̛̛̛̛̫͍̫̰̩͎̳̯̥̘̫̠̮̣̞̝̖͔̗͈͈̘̱̖̖͍̫̜͖̮͍͇̝͉̠̫̰̼̗̘̪̬̟̭̰͓̲͚͉̻̗̰̮̩̱̩̱͖̣̤͉͍̤̯͇̹͐͂͊̂͋̐͛̒̓͑̔̈́̊͆̽̑̓͛̇́͋̈́̎̔̊̊̍̒̀̐́̏̓͐̑̀͆̊̊̏̋͊̏̑͑̉̈̀̔̏̄̃̀́̒̍͒̄̌͆̾̏͊̾̓̐͑̽͘͘̕̚͜͜͠͝͝͝͝ ̸̢̧̢̢̢̪͈̫͇̖̙̠̣͕̜̬̖̺̟̫̗̬̙̙̰̯͙͔͉̲̥̫̠͓̤͍̙̤͓̫̻̺͍̣̜͍̪̭̗͛̂͑̿̆̈́̈́̾̑̽̐͌̔̉͋̿͑͋̍̇̆̓̈́͑͑͌̆́̾̔͆͂̂͌̈́̇͌͛͂̈̌͊̑́̏̂͆̾̽̌̂̒͆̃͐̈́̋̆̽͗̓̑̒͊̕̚̕͘̚̕̚͜͠͝͠͝͠ ̶̧̧͎̭̼͓̰̲͈̠̯̗͈̰̯̘̼͈̺̺̱̞̼̪͎̲͈͍̪̼̦̥̟̲͈͍̦̖̺̙͎̙̖̗̬̘̖͍̺̪͓͚̳͓̹͓̗̹̻̙̊͑̽̿̀̂̾̈́̑́̑́́̂̏̀̉̈́̐̓̌͗̈́͋̾̊̏̒̉̈́̈́͋̽̈́̂̌̽̋̽̅̀̐̓͑̆̓̈́̽̒̒͒̀̓̃͒̀̓̕̕͘͜͜͝͝͠͝͝͝͝͠͝͝ͅ ̴̢̨̡̡̨̨̧̢̟̩̘̺̘̙̰̲̣̺̩͕̩̩̗͍͖̙̳͕̺͖̞͓̘̱̣̺̻͙̞͉̱̻̘̯̜̗̰̺̱̤͎͍̜̗͚͇̼̰̠͉̭̬̩͇͔̰̠̀̀̄͆̄͐͐͂͗̂̐̉̽͐̆̀̏̀̌̾̐͛̽̃͌͂̓̋̂́͛̐̃̏̿̾̄̓̔́͑̚̕͜͜͝͝ͅͅB̷̨̢̛̬̺̞͔̘̭̼͍̮͈̭͇̬̙̲̘̰̮̞͓͓̭̙̦̻̹͎̟̱̦̪̗͎̪̤̥̫̉̐̃̆̑̊̌͒̈̇̈́̑̉̀̅̎̈́̀͗͗̇̈͌̊̆̿̇̄̆̔̊͆́̄̈́̓̔̓̆̅͗͗́̈́̉͋̑̓͌̏͛͛̈́͆̍͋̄̈́͊̃̈́̒̎̇̀̊̏̃̈͆̏̅̕͘̕͜͜͠͝͠͝͝͠ͅ ̸̨̧̧̳̘̖͚͍̟̯͎͉̼̱̦̥̺̘̯͍̻̗̬̻̫͙̯͍̥̦͙̱͔̰͚̻̪̜̪̮̝̺̇ͅͅͅͅ ̵̧̨̧̮̩̺͇͓̦͙̝͖̙͙̦̺͈̘̩͈̩͓̮̫͍̹̜̦͎̲̬̙̠̜̀̆̔̿̿̽͆̑͛͋̋̄͊̑̇͋̂̐̑͂͗̃̓̀͗̾́̇́̏̇̓͒̀̽̎͌̋̾̌͑̏̀̓͐́̀̑̉̀͊̚̚͘͠҉̸̨̨̡̛̪͙̜͕̗͉̭̼̦̪͇̺̗̬̟̰͕͇͈̆̋͌͌͒̊̿̈̓̐͒͗̃͜Ȩ̶̡̧̛̛̫͓̰̙͈̰͙͙̰̬͎͇͚̦͉͈̭̾̊̽̅̿́̅͒͂̋̋̀̉̈́̎̒́͊̒͒̀̽͒͑̋̈́̈̔͐̎̍͌͒́̊̕̕͘͝͝͠͝͝ ̴̨̧̢̢̧̝̜͔̟̟͈͇̖̣͕̦̩̺̤̪͕̯̪͕̻̤̲̬͉̥̪̣͕͈̻̥͍̤̱͖̤̭̩̣͔͙̗͖̲͍̊͑̅̌̂̂̋͛͋̓͒̔̈́̌̃͗̃͋͑͒͊͂̊̄̇̏̅̀̓̈́̄̚͘̚͘͝͝ͅ ̵̨̡̨̨̡̨̧̛̛̛̤̮̟͚̙̫̯̼̭͚̦̖̺͓̖̹̹̣͍͇͉̞͓̲͔̯̙̩͈̰͉̩̤̳͓̲̻̙͕̬̼̲̞̙̖̘̣̭͓̼͓̼͓͍͚̉̾̀́̈́̇̆̓̎̑̅̈̓̐̏̂̾̂̓͂͋͛̐̃̆̋̅̎̔̇͂̏̓̾̈͋͂̄̈̊̈̇̄̈́̌͆̋̓̊̔̃̍́͂̉̐̔̆̆͂̏͌̈̓̐͂͗̚̚̕̕̕͘͜͜͝͠͠͝ ̵̢̡̧̢̬͖̫̮͓̯̪͚̻̗͉̞̗̼̰̯̭̞͚̺̹̟̻͍̥͈͈͒̀͛́͛̆̀͋͆͂̆̔̓̇́͆͆̊̋̿̈́̂͜͜͝͠҉̶̧̡̡̧̨̨̛̛̛̯͚̥̟̳̺̺̘̰̯͈͕̬̘̺̼͇̤̥̮͎͚̟͎̝̘̫̼͍̦͚̣̼̼͉̹̼̝̟̩̣̭̗̙̖̟̮͕͚̦̻̯̞̹͕̫̩̌̏̓̾̀́̽̈́͒̏͐́͋͑͗́̈́́̏̉̈́̈͑͌̆͗͊̊̈̿̿̃̿̈́̄̓̅͆͒̈́̋͐̔̓̊͒̌͌̇̒̊̀̀͋̀̓̽̀͐̒͐̈́̔̓̃̋̚͜͜͜͝͝͠ͅͅ ̵̨̧̡̢͈̠͇͓̠̺͉̳̝͔̦͍̼̳̥̫̱͂̈́̑̃͊̈́̑̆̆̔͊̀̒̑̉͛͒̾̇̽͆̀̽̑̀̾͌̅͋̃̈͂̅̑́̔̿̚̕͝͠͝͝ͅ҉̷̨̢̬̖̼̣͖́͛̎̎͝ ̷̧̡̨̧̛̛͇̣̪͎͕͉͍̪̣̬̬̪̦̮̰̗͍̯̦͇̗̟̻͔̤͇̙͕͉̳͚̝̅̎̀̐͐̉̽̅̽̀͊́̎͂̓̍̍̾̈́͑́̐̒̓̑̄̃͗͗̃͐͑͑́̊̅̽̌̿̑͌̌̀̾́͗̈́̀͑̌͛̍̐̌͑̅͘̕̚͘͘͝͠͠͝A̴̧̢̢̢̧̢̠̖̭͓̰̜̰̹͔̺͎̟̯̯̙͎̲̯̞͈̠̩͚̯̦̰͉̟̼͔̯̬̭̙͖͖̫͈̟̥̻͉̭̺͚̮͙͕̟͈̙̝̘̘͍̖͙͖̟͖̥͆́̐̈̈́̇͋̔̊́̅͂̊̂͑́̽̄̾͂́͐̈̀̅̈́̂̄͐̚͘̕͘͝͠ͅͅ ̷̶̧̧̨̧̧̡̨̡̨̧̧̢̧̛̛̛̩͈̼̗̬̜̼͖̝̩̝̙̯̟͔͎̫̬̺̖͉͇̫̟͔͍̻̗̜͙̭̟͍̪͔̭͙̬̦̫͎̞͇̩̠̮̤͓̺̣͖̝͕͇̝͈̝̩̗̹̤̥͈̟̣̗̳͇̙̭̙̱̯̫͙̳̦͕͚̰̹̞̠̺̼͔̲͉͕͈͎̖͈̦͇̣̘̜͍̮̯͖̬̘̟̱͇̙͔̙̻͕̲̺̜͖̐̍͛͌̎́͌̓̐͌̊̀͛͌͆̈́̽̉̓̽̇̐̌̄̂͂̀̾̊̀̑̍̽̀̌̆͋͐̐̅͒͒̿͆̎̍̽̓̃́̀̅́͐͗͋̂͒̂͗̈́̅̊̌͆̏̆̈́̈̂͒̓͑̇̔͐͋̀͑̽̐̈́̒͒́̀̒́̂̏̀̆̃̂͗̐̈̆̂͛̆̓̐̌̈́͗̾̈̐̈́͂͂̊̿̑̒̈̓͐͋́͆͂͒̓͐̃̈́͋̀͑͘̚̚̚̚̕̕͢͜͝͝͠͠͠͝͠͝͝͝͠ͅͅͅͅͅͅ ̷̢̨̢̺̗̱͉̳̬̩̹̲̯͈̞̺̳̗̫̜͈̱̦͈̼̜͇̰̞̬̠̳̜͈̠͔͑̂̈́́̈́̔͘͠ͅ҉̶̡̛̣͍̳̻͕̤̬͉̜̮͙̞̥̮͍̮͙͚̦̻̺̟̫͔͓̟̥̥͎̙̤͉̲̺͕̞͈̹̗͇̘̏̂̋̑̉̆̽̒̏̓̆̇̔́͆̔͋͛̽̽̑̿̍̓̅́̀̀̌̉̈́̋́̕͠͠͠͠͝ͅͅͅḌ̸̛̛͈̦̲̲̟̝̘̳̯̹̰̤̆͛͂̀͌̐͌͒̾́̍̀̋̀́͐̇̽̎͌́̎̐̈́̔͗̈́̃̅́̅̋̽̀̾͑͌̌̊̐̈̐͌͆̀̈́̈̂͋̇̚̚͝͝͝ ̷̡̨̧̥͔̯͚̪̠̟̪͙͎͎̺̩͔͉̬̝̯͔̼̥̟͎̮̜̼̳̘͓͇͙̥̤̥̬̼̗̿̂͂̈̒̽̂̉̊͆̂̐́̌͐̂̊̀̒̌̑̿́̐̈́͒̂͑̾͌̆͆̄̾͐̎̄̀͂̊̂͛̅͋̀͐͑̍̄́͌̚̚̕̕̕̕͘͘͘͝͠͝͠ͅ ̶̢̡̧̧̢̡̛͖̩̗̱̣͉̤̫͉͓͕̗̳̟̱̲̱̟͖̗̦̻̟̺̺̤̥̰̼͖̙̺̭̻̤̝̜̺͇͔͖̬̪͎̜̲̰͚̺̬̗̝͇͚͚͖̜̙̟̻̙̬̹̝̓͑̌͌̆̾̀̉͛̈́̇̊̃̒͂͋̽͂̿͂̃̄͗̏́͑̇̽̓̎͗̐̀̅͛̐͊̃̑̕̚͘̕͜͠͠͝͝͝ͅ҉̶̢̧̢̡̧̧̨̡̛͕̲̝̦̤̯̤̥̖̱̻̘͇̦͖͖̮͚̞̻͈̘̱̝̳̹͎̰̤͎̹̻̳̼͈̬̩̬̮̪̖̻͇̥̟̜͎͙̼̪̦͖͚͖̥͚̭̮̯͕̗̝͉̣͔̠̥͈̘̼͊̇̈́̏́̔̎̒̀̿̅̒͘͜͠͝͝͠V̸̡̨̨̹͕͇̟͙̦̜̬̠̳̗̟͙͈͕̪͙̻͓̠̯̦̠̠̮́̑̈̀̍͋͛͋̃͊͂̎͛͊͌̈́̽̅̎̈́͛̈́̈͛͌̇̾̆̉̊̈͑̄͐̆̽͗͌̑̉̏̎͂͊̈́̅̋̒͂͂̈́̀̀͒̈́̈́̃̑̿́͌̏̐̾̄̚̚̕͠͠͝͠͠͠ ̸̨̨̧̢̡̢̬̙̗͕̹̪̗͔̗̘̖̪̼̰͚͔͖̤̩͉͈̠̗̘̫̯̠͕̦͚͓̞̹̼̣̱̻̩̝̣̤̻͉͔̺̫̺̤̝͈̖̝̙̝̣̲̣̜̖̟̹̣̥̗̞̥̹͉̩͉͖̤̈́́̿̍̌̿̈̽̆̄͑͗̋͜͜͜͜͠ͅͅͅͅ ̴̨̛̛̤̦̗̄͑̆̋̈̾̒̾͊̓̈̋̆̅̿͌̈́́̑̏̔̾́̒͆͗̉͂̓́̒̏̉̽̎̑͑́̍̍̃̓́̋͐̀͂͌̎̓̆̄̓͌͒̋͘̚̚͜͠A̸̢̡̡̧̡̧̟̤̤̱͔͓͍͍͎͍͖͔͎͙͈̙͓̻͈͙̣̳̰͍͕̣̹̝͓͍̳̥̜͚͓̙͓̻͔̪̘̳̹͉̺̫͓͙̣̮͇̠̗̞̲̩̟̲̠̯̼͍̜̜̣͔̖̩̜̱̰͒͆̈́̄́͊͒̾̓͒̐͗̀҉̷̡̨̧̢̨̧̢̡̛͚͖̟͈̲̳͇͉͔̲̗̝͓̫̭̫̫͍̫̼̝̦̹͈͔̪̮̖͈̻̖͙̄̌͛̂͊͗͋̈́̆̐͆̈͂̓͊̊̾̾̿̌͗̄̾̒͋̀̿̽̓͂̓̉͆̀̋͛͛̿̈́̿͐́͑̄̋͋͌̋̇̈́̐́͆͌̓̈̓͗̑̄͂̒͒̂̾͂̒͊̕͘͜͠͝͝ ̵̴̡̢̢̧̛̛̯͙͖͍͚̲͍̖͚̻̪̗͙͖͙͇͈̜̤͉̺͎̞̖͙͎̪͈͍̖̗͍͓̻̼̖̼̺̜̭͕͕̫̦͚̮͔̻̭̲̓̃̀̾͌́̒̂̈̓́͌̃̃̀̇̄̽̽̎͆̈́̈́̈̊͋̔͊͗̄́̅͑̽̓̈́̃̄̈́̽̐͗̈́͑̏̆͗̔̅͋̓̆̀͘̚̚͘͘̕͘͜͢͝͝͝͝ ̵̢̢̢̛͎̳̼͚̝͙͉͔̮̦̜̖̬̭̗͎͓͚̟̮͓̳͎̜̱͕̳̮͙̥̙̹̤̟̙̭̱̖͕̳̝͍͖̯̙̙̝̰̳̰̗͊̓̌̍̀͌̌̿̒̇̅̍̅͗̈́́̉̎̐͌̿̋͐̀̂̉́͐̓͛̿̌̒̽͒̊̔̈͋̈́̑͑̊̽̾̍̓͋̈́̋͊̆̑̾̒̚͘͘͘̕͠͝ͅŅ̵̢̢̛̛̛̛̛̛̭̘͔̖̜̞̘̯̫̖̙͇͎͙̥͓̻͔̣̺̣͇̘̺̆̈̄͊̀̐̈́̍̅̅̆̃̀̈̓͛̎̈́̏͒̈́͆̃̉̔̈́̾̽̊̈̈́̓̓͗̽̄̑̀͊͊̏̆̋͋̏̇̋̓͛̏̌̆̐̿̊̚͝͝͝ͅ ̸̡̧͕͔̬̘̻͍̩̮̳͖̟̙̱̍̊̑̔͊̇̃͌̒͊͋̅̒́̒̂̇̇̽̉̉̀̆́̆̀̽̕̚ ̸̰̜̱͚̪̜̯͎̪̯̪̠̳͕͚̺̟̝͕͖͖̮̳̼̎̃̓͐̓̈́̀̀̇̈̒́͗͋͛͆͑̔̇͐̀͛̊̏͂͗̏̊̇͋͋̒̌̆̍̂͒͘͘̚̚͜͝ͅC̸̡̡̢̨̦̣̼̮̺̗͎̞̯̗͈͔̮͔͉̠̟̮̱͖͔͖̻͓̘̗͈̝̦̭̱̠͍̤͍̮͎̳̹͉̮̟̭̩̯̲̯̻̻̜͖̺̮̹̙̝̑͊̑̔͗̀͌̔̃͌̕͜ͅͅ ̴̧̨̢̨̛̰̮̖̣̥͕̯̗͔̥̬̰̩̟̻̤̦̮͔̭̼̝̻̹̲̪̰̰͇̼̱̞̥̥̙̱̯̭̦͔̼̺̦̬̜̖̩̺͓͙̼̞̼͍̻͖̦̫̻̤̞͈̤̲̼͔͉͚͚̻͎̜̪̖̱̼̼͛̃̈́̒̈́̿̊̋̐̈́̓̈̐̐͋̂͗͒̽͐̽̑͑̎̀̈́̓͒̽́͌̍́̐̓̍̌̕̚͘͘͘͜͜͜͝͝͝͠ͅ ̵̷̡̧̢̧̧̨̛̲͇̳̩̹̯̺̮̦̩͖̝̖͎̞͍̝͖͇̫̣̞͉̳̗̦̠̼̟͈̬̠͙͙͕͈̬̮̘͔̹̫̬͍͕̤̗̟̝̼̼̝͙̫̲͇̣̬̜̦͔̘̞͎̤͕̹̩̪̗͇̱̞̤̭̫͇͉̠̪̼̙̜͇̟̲͚͎̬̟͎͍̰͔̥̰̞͍̳̟̲͎̬̖̮͈̳̱̣͑̍̐͋̀͐͐̃͂̎̇͐͊̇̀͗͆̿͒̍̈́̈̑̈̉͑͒̀̉̓̾̄̏̈́̓̊͐̌̉̍̒͒̐̉̾̏̌̾͆́͊̉̅̉͊́̏͂́̈̀͂͗̆́̐̑͗̽̐̉̋͐̉̈́̂́̌͒̓̌͛̉̈́̊́̋̾̀͂̆̐͒̐͑͋͗̄̅̈́̏̒̕͘̕̕͘̚̕̚͜͢͠͝͝͠͝ͅͅͅͅͅͅ҉̵̨̡̨̢̨̨̨̢̛̛̛͍̙̥̭̮̲̦̫̗̻̦̩̗̮̳͔̗͓̬̦̤̘̞̥͈͉͙̠̻̘̱̦͙̟͕̯̺̫̫͖̰͖̘̠̘͚͖̠͐̒͐̅͂̿̋͌̉̃̌͌̎̔̒͐͊̓̃̊̓̈̈̌̄̾̂̈́̃̂̅̕̚͘͜͜͜͜͝͝͝͝͝ͅÊ̷̢̟̱̳͚̮̱̮̠̘̲͉̥̿̆̊̀̈́̍̈̀͜ͅ ̶̛̛̛̼̺̩͔̪̼̥̺̂́͆̐̉͆̌̀́̊́̀͆̄͗̔̌̿́̈́̄͆̀͂̃͗̇̆̒̒̐͛̈́̐͐̓̂̓̾́̓̍͂̏́̿͂͆̐̉̿̒͘̚̚̕̕̕̚͘͝͝͠͝ ̵̨̨͈̜̳̳̯̮͔̻̹̤͇̤͇̘̞̫̻̟̫̞͈̮͍͍̤̭̫̠̞͍̥͍̤͉̭̺̰̱̣̙̳̦́̌͋̅͛̎̏̀͊͒͛̿̕͜͜D̵̴̢̢̡̧̡̢̡̧̡̡̡̛̛̛̛̻̜̼͚̝̫̦̫͇̟̝̰͕̠̞̖͔̹͚͓̱͇̹͉̘̖̬̝͔̥̦̯̟̳͍̳̱̥͖̱̰̜̼̻͖̞̣̬͕̖͈͖̠̙̲̺̘͍̘͕̭̦͈̫̰͇̻̟̬̬͖͔̠͚̪̩͇̦͕̟͇͚̤̲̲̻̣̗̮̺̯͖̰̰̖̮̤̪͔̠̲̬̼͓̹̼̹͖̞̬̙̣̰̝͔̙͍͍͉̪̲̫̣͎̱̠̥̝͙͓̟̩̫̥̬̱̪̯̙̀̊̀̿͛̽̉̎̈͂̍̿̃͋̎̽̈́͂͐̍́̆͗̒̆̃̈̽̋̃͒͌́̑̈́̏͊͛͒̽͂͂̓̀̌̂̌̐̐̊̽̽̀̈́̇͗̓̿̀̓́̌͆̅̆̔̏͐̀͋̈̑̊̈̌̈̊̒͗́̎̉̉̈́̃͌͂̏̂̉̊̉̔̊͑̈̏͘͘͘̚͘̕̕̕͜͜͜͢͜͜͠͠͝͠͠ͅͅ!̴̡̢̢̛̛̲͕̟̫̘͕͎͕̰̞̬͔̗̹̘̭̽͗̒̀̈́̅̆͂̋͒̀̈́́̀̇̏̔͆̄͊̂͋̈́́̂͆̐̅̇̀̆̿̇̏͐̈̓̔͋̀̃̍̿̽͆́̃̄̀̔̔̄͐͐͑̉̉̀̃̑̋͊̔͒͗̌̇͆̈́̍́̄̕̚͠͝͝͝͝͝͠͝͝ͅͅ҉̵̡̨̛̻̲̫̗̱̳̭͉͇̖̗̪͍̳̮̬͚͚̻̖̬̙̯͇̺̭̭͉̥͍̀̉͛́͐̊́̈́̏͒̿̍̐̊͒̃̒̀͂́͋̑̾͐̿̀̒̅͗͐͒́̾̈̍͆̑̿̀̈́͋̾̏͑̽̍̿̆̋͆̋̏́̍́̍̚̕͘͜͠͠͝͝ͅ ̷̡̡̨̢̛̛̛̛̱̗̰̦̯̞̗̝̱͍̭̗͖̬͍͕͙̜͈̞̱͈̪͖̥̝̪͕͔͇̟͇̣̺̮̘̬̬̈́̒́̑̅̍͗̿̃̅̿̃͒́́͂̏̒̈́͌̿̆́̿̈́̂̏̉̏̅̇̑̾̾̏̇̃̇̈́͊͛͑͐̆̂͊̔͗́͆̾̉̇̈́̃̒͑͛́͘̕̚̚̚̚͜͝͝͠͝ͅ
So, yeah. Dorico is really impressive. I like it.
Um,
...sorry if I kind of maybe misled
you there with that last bit.
I suppose you probably thought I was
going to conclude otherwise, well...
...I guess I’m not surprised.
I didn’t expect this video to lurch
from praise to criticism so much.
I mean, on the positive side,
it does a lot of stuff extremely well.
It looks great.
It features a lot of attention to detail
and its engraving is fantastic.
It also has tons of new ideas
...and has really made an impressive
attempt to solve long-standing problems.
And with that in mind,
...I think this is actually one of the big
‘thank you’s we all owe to the Dorico team.
Thanks for forcing everyone
else to have to up their game!
From spending a lot of time looking through their
forum posts and engagement on social media,
...the impression I get is of a very
professional and engaged team.
Daniel, in particular, is super disciplined in the face
of sometimes less than reasonable comments,
...and other times, he’s just pleasant by default.
I mean, look at this.
A user recently tweeted:
Now, I know a lot of people who would either ignore this,
...or curtly ask the person to be a little more specific.
But, Daniel replies:
I don’t know why I like this so much.
It just seemed above and beyond to me.
Oh Daniel,
...I could just give you a big kiss.
So, to the big question:
If I was commissioned tomorrow to write a score,
...which of the two apps would I choose?
Sibelius or Dorico?
Now, I’m not going to lie.
I’ve written this paragraph three times in 6 months.
At first, it was
‘Sibelius, hands down’
...because writing is so much faster.
And then, as I begun finishing music in Dorico
...and seeing how well the parts
and layouts were handled,
...I thought, ‘Well that claws back a bit of time',
...'Hmm, it’s neck and neck now’,
And then I was actually commissioned
to write a new piece,
...and I limited myself to these two options,
...and the choice is just obvious:
Sibelius,
...despite the fact that I was
actively using Dorico every day.
And the reason?
It’s just more permissive
...and allows me to get lost in the writing process.
But as I said,
...it’s close.
Really close.
...and I could easily change my
mind in about 6 months' time.
For me right now,
...the deciding factor is that Sibelius
lets me write how I want to write,
...whereas with Dorico,
...I have to write the way Dorico wants me to write.
And this is not the conclusion I wanted to come to.
I’ve been following the Dorico story for ages..
I love how much detail and passion
they’ve shown for their product,
...and I have enormous respect for them.
But this isn’t a straight ‘no’,
...it's an 'almost'.
Regarding the things I don’t like,
...not everyone is going to agree.
And for some, Dorico already makes sense,
...and it has won a few die-hard admirers.
For those who think I overly focus on first-time usage:
As a designer, I have a particular dislike for
apps that are made with the expectation that
...new users should spend an enormous
amount of time coming to terms with it.
The reality of modern life is that we are now
required to keep learning software all the time.
It’s overwhelming,
...and a designer’s job should be to try and
reduce that pain as much as possible.
Think about those who are only
at the beginning of their journey.
It sucks when you’re just starting out
...and your initial experience of trying to
write some music is insanely technical.
A lot of young students have got in contact with me
...to express how demotivating
their experience of Sibelius was.
And if Dorico took over in the classroom now,
...I think that would mean yet another
generation going through the same thing.
But, why not find out for yourself and get their free trial?
If you’ve got this far in the video,
...you’ll most likely have a much easier
time of it than the people I tested.
Let me know if they’ve fixed that eLicenser issue yet!
And my final thought to all people
in music software is this:
Consistency is important, absolutely,
...but interface design is as much an art as a science,
...and it’s okay to sometimes break your own rules.
If not, then your super rational system
may translate into a frustrating experience.
And the only way out of this
...is to focus on rigorous user-testing.
If the app is communicating well,
...you’ll see that reflected in how people use it.
And when your system produces
an unfortunate interaction oddity,
...like having one mode for moving things horizontally
and another for moving them up or down,
...it’s dangerous to take the attitude
...that the oddity is actually rational because
it fits the system and the system is rational.
Instead, come up with a clever exception.
There’s no god of interface design watching over us.
We’re not honor-bound to always
be 100% organisationally pure.
These users aren’t robots,
...they’re creative musicians,
...and half of them are mad!
Get mad, Dorico!
Get all up in everyone’s face!
They made you redundant.
They thought they could do without you!
But you’ll show them.
You’re going to make them pay for what they did!
The next time Sibelius crashes,
...it’ll be forever!